<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2015-11-30" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB09507</drugbank-id>
  <name>Ferumoxsil</name>
  <description/>
  <cas-number>171544-35-7</cas-number>
  <unii>6HJV9H13XS</unii>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
    <group>experimental</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication/>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action/>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="ban/usan/usp">Ferumoxsil</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Siloxane-coated superparamagnetic iron oxide</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>Gastromark</name>
      <labeller>Mallinckrodt</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>0019-1120</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2010-07-23</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2013-02-28</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Suspension</dosage-form>
      <strength>105 mg/600mL</strength>
      <route>Oral</route>
      <fda-application-number>NDA020410</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Lumirem</name>
      <company/>
    </international-brand>
  </international-brands>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>Gastromark</name>
      <ingredients>Ferumoxsil</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Colloids</category>
      <mesh-id>D003102</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Complex Mixtures</category>
      <mesh-id>D045424</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Compounds used in a research, industrial, or household setting</category>
      <mesh-id>D020313</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Contrast Media</category>
      <mesh-id>D003287</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Ferric Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D005290</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Ferrosoferric Oxide</category>
      <mesh-id>D052203</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Ferrous Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D005296</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Investigative Techniques</category>
      <mesh-id>D008919</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Iron Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D058085</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Macromolecular Substances</category>
      <mesh-id>D046911</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Magnetic Resonance Imaging Contrast Media</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Magnets</category>
      <mesh-id>D059346</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Metal Nanoparticles</category>
      <mesh-id>D053768</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Minerals</category>
      <mesh-id>D008903</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nanoparticles</category>
      <mesh-id>D053758</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nanostructures</category>
      <mesh-id>D049329</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Organometallic Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D009942</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Organosilicon Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D017646</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Pharmaceutical Preparations</category>
      <mesh-id>D004364</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Polymers</category>
      <mesh-id>D011108</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Silicon Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D017655</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Superparamagnetic Contrast Media</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Suspension</form>
      <route>Oral</route>
      <strength>105 mg/600mL</strength>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes>
    <atc-code code="V08CB01">
      <level code="V08CB">Superparamagnetic contrast media</level>
      <level code="V08C">MAGNETIC RESONANCE IMAGING CONTRAST MEDIA</level>
      <level code="V08">CONTRAST MEDIA</level>
      <level code="V">VARIOUS</level>
    </atc-code>
  </atc-codes>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06782</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dimercaprol</name>
      <description>Dimercaprol may increase the nephrotoxic activities of Ferumoxsil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00535</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefdinir</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Cefdinir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08826</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deferiprone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Deferiprone can be decreased when it is combined with Ferumoxsil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08930</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dolutegravir</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dolutegravir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06210</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eltrombopag</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Eltrombopag resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01235</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levodopa</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Levodopa can be decreased when combined with Ferumoxsil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00451</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levothyroxine</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Levothyroxine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00968</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methyldopa</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Methyldopa resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00859</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penicillamine</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Penicillamine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00166</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lipoic acid</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Lipoic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moxifloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Moxifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00365</drugbank-id>
      <name>Grepafloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Grepafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00467</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enoxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Enoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00487</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pefloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pefloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00537</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ciprofloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ciprofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00685</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trovafloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Trovafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00779</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nalidixic acid</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Nalidixic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rosoxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rosoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00827</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cinoxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Cinoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00978</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lomefloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Lomefloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01044</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gatifloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Gatifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01059</drugbank-id>
      <name>Norfloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Norfloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01137</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levofloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Levofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01155</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemifloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Gemifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01165</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ofloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sparfloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sparfloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01405</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temafloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Temafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04576</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fleroxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Fleroxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05488</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m ciprofloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Technetium Tc-99m ciprofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06160</drugbank-id>
      <name>Garenoxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Garenoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06600</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nemonoxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Nemonoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08972</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flumequine</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Flumequine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11404</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enrofloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Enrofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11443</drugbank-id>
      <name>Orbifloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Orbifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11491</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sarafloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sarafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11511</drugbank-id>
      <name>Difloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Difloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11774</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pazufloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pazufloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11892</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prulifloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Prulifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11943</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delafloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Delafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13261</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sitafloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sitafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13627</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxolinic acid</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Oxolinic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13772</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rufloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rufloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13823</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pipemidic acid</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pipemidic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00254</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxycycline</name>
      <description>Doxycycline can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00256</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lymecycline</name>
      <description>Lymecycline can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00453</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clomocycline</name>
      <description>Clomocycline can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxytetracycline</name>
      <description>Oxytetracycline can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00618</drugbank-id>
      <name>Demeclocycline</name>
      <description>Demeclocycline can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00759</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetracycline</name>
      <description>Tetracycline can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00931</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metacycline</name>
      <description>Metacycline can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01017</drugbank-id>
      <name>Minocycline</name>
      <description>Minocycline can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12035</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sarecycline</name>
      <description>Sarecycline can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12455</drugbank-id>
      <name>Omadacycline</name>
      <description>Omadacycline can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13092</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meclocycline</name>
      <description>Meclocycline can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penimepicycline</name>
      <description>Penimepicycline can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06824</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triethylenetetramine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ferumoxsil can be decreased when it is combined with Triethylenetetramine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00085</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pancrelipase</name>
      <description>Pancrelipase can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01370</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aluminium</name>
      <description>Aluminium can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01377</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium oxide</name>
      <description>Magnesium oxide can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01390</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium bicarbonate</name>
      <description>Sodium bicarbonate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06723</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aluminum hydroxide</name>
      <description>Aluminum hydroxide can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06724</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium carbonate</name>
      <description>Calcium carbonate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08938</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magaldrate</name>
      <description>Magaldrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09104</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium hydroxide</name>
      <description>Magnesium hydroxide can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09281</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium trisilicate</name>
      <description>Magnesium trisilicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09481</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium carbonate</name>
      <description>Magnesium carbonate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13249</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium silicate</name>
      <description>Magnesium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13280</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aluminium acetoacetate</name>
      <description>Aluminium acetoacetate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13322</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrotalcite</name>
      <description>Hydrotalcite can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13486</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium peroxide</name>
      <description>Magnesium peroxide can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Almasilate</name>
      <description>Almasilate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13626</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aluminium glycinate</name>
      <description>Aluminium glycinate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13650</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aloglutamol</name>
      <description>Aloglutamol can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13829</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium silicate</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14517</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aluminium phosphate</name>
      <description>Aluminium phosphate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pantoprazole</name>
      <description>Pantoprazole can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00448</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lansoprazole</name>
      <description>Lansoprazole can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00736</drugbank-id>
      <name>Esomeprazole</name>
      <description>Esomeprazole can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01129</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rabeprazole</name>
      <description>Rabeprazole can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05351</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexlansoprazole</name>
      <description>Dexlansoprazole can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13762</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexrabeprazole</name>
      <description>Dexrabeprazole can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15246</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salvianolic acid A</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00334</drugbank-id>
      <name>Olanzapine</name>
      <description>Olanzapine can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00501</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cimetidine</name>
      <description>Cimetidine can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00585</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nizatidine</name>
      <description>Nizatidine can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00863</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ranitidine</name>
      <description>Ranitidine can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00927</drugbank-id>
      <name>Famotidine</name>
      <description>Famotidine can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00940</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methantheline</name>
      <description>Methantheline can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01069</drugbank-id>
      <name>Promethazine</name>
      <description>Promethazine can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01142</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxepin</name>
      <description>Doxepin can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06216</drugbank-id>
      <name>Asenapine</name>
      <description>Asenapine can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08805</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metiamide</name>
      <description>Metiamide can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08806</drugbank-id>
      <name>Roxatidine acetate</name>
      <description>Roxatidine acetate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12770</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lafutidine</name>
      <description>Lafutidine can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12884</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lavoltidine</name>
      <description>Lavoltidine can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13760</drugbank-id>
      <name>Niperotidine</name>
      <description>Niperotidine can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00282</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pamidronic acid</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pamidronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00399</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zoledronic acid</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Zoledronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00630</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alendronic acid</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Alendronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00710</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibandronate</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ibandronate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00720</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clodronic acid</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Clodronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00884</drugbank-id>
      <name>Risedronic acid</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Risedronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01077</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etidronic acid</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Etidronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01133</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiludronic acid</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Tiludronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06255</drugbank-id>
      <name>Incadronic acid</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02369</drugbank-id>
      <name>3-Aza-2,3-Dihydrogeranyl Diphosphate</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of 3-Aza-2,3-Dihydrogeranyl Diphosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02423</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiopyrophosphate</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Thiopyrophosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02552</drugbank-id>
      <name>Geranyl Diphosphate</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Geranyl Diphosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04160</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pyrophosphoric acid</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pyrophosphoric acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05143</drugbank-id>
      <name>OXI-4503</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07841</drugbank-id>
      <name>Geranylgeranyl diphosphate</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Geranylgeranyl diphosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09147</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric pyrophosphate</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferric pyrophosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09413</drugbank-id>
      <name>Monopotassium phosphate</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Monopotassium phosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09414</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dipotassium phosphate</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dipotassium phosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09449</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium phosphate, monobasic</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sodium phosphate, monobasic resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11348</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium Phosphate</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Calcium Phosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11493</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium tripolyphosphate</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sodium tripolyphosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13995</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric pyrophosphate citrate</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferric pyrophosphate citrate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14481</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium phosphate dihydrate</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Calcium phosphate dihydrate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14523</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phosphate ion</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Phosphate ion resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09139</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m oxidronate</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Technetium Tc-99m oxidronate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00338</drugbank-id>
      <name>Omeprazole</name>
      <description>The absorption of Ferumoxsil can be decreased when combined with Omeprazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00190</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbidopa</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Carbidopa resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers/>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>