<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-09-11" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB04682</drugbank-id>
  <name>Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol</name>
  <description/>
  <cas-number>9036-19-5</cas-number>
  <unii/>
  <average-mass>1527.9007</average-mass>
  <monoisotopic-mass>1526.953507826</monoisotopic-mass>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>experimental</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication/>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action/>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Adrenal Cortex Hormones</category>
      <mesh-id>D000305</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Compounds used in a research, industrial, or household setting</category>
      <mesh-id>D020313</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Contraceptive Agents, Female</category>
      <mesh-id>D003271</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Contraceptive Agents, Male</category>
      <mesh-id>D003272</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Hormonal Contraceptives for Systemic Use</category>
      <mesh-id>D003270</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Spermatocidal Agents</category>
      <mesh-id>D013089</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries>
    <pdb-entry>1ytz</pdb-entry>
  </pdb-entries>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00673</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aprepitant</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Aprepitant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01276</drugbank-id>
      <name>Exenatide</name>
      <description>Exenatide can cause a decrease in the absorption of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01041</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thalidomide</name>
      <description>Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol may increase the thrombogenic activities of Thalidomide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00089</drugbank-id>
      <name>Capromab pendetide</name>
      <description>Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol may decrease effectiveness of Capromab pendetide as a diagnostic agent.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00302</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tranexamic acid</name>
      <description>Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol may increase the thrombogenic activities of Tranexamic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00349</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clobazam</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Clobazam.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00400</drugbank-id>
      <name>Griseofulvin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Griseofulvin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00588</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluticasone propionate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Fluticasone propionate can be increased when it is combined with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01108</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trilostane</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Trilostane can be increased when it is combined with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04630</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aldosterone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Aldosterone can be increased when it is combined with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09091</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tixocortol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tixocortol can be increased when it is combined with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09378</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluprednisolone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Fluprednisolone can be increased when it is combined with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11529</drugbank-id>
      <name>Melengestrol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Melengestrol can be increased when it is combined with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13223</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluocortin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Fluocortin can be increased when it is combined with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13491</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluperolone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Fluperolone can be increased when it is combined with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13664</drugbank-id>
      <name>Formocortal</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Formocortal can be increased when it is combined with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13856</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluclorolone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Fluclorolone can be increased when it is combined with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14541</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrocortisone cypionate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Hydrocortisone cypionate can be increased when it is combined with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00873</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loteprednol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Loteprednol can be increased when it is combined with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14643</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylprednisolone aceponate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Methylprednisolone aceponate can be increased when it is combined with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01234</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexamethasone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Dexamethasone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00180</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flunisolide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Flunisolide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00394</drugbank-id>
      <name>Beclomethasone dipropionate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Beclomethasone dipropionate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00443</drugbank-id>
      <name>Betamethasone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Betamethasone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00591</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluocinolone acetonide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Fluocinolone acetonide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00620</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triamcinolone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Triamcinolone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00635</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Prednisone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00741</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrocortisone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Hydrocortisone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00764</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mometasone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Mometasone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00860</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisolone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Prednisolone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00959</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylprednisolone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Methylprednisolone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01222</drugbank-id>
      <name>Budesonide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Budesonide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01285</drugbank-id>
      <name>Corticotropin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Corticotropin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01380</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cortisone acetate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Cortisone acetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01384</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paramethasone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Paramethasone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08906</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluticasone furoate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Fluticasone furoate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08970</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluprednidene</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Fluprednidene.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08971</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluocortolone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Fluocortolone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09383</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meprednisone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Meprednisone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11487</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexamethasone isonicotinate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Dexamethasone isonicotinate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11750</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clobetasol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Clobetasol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11921</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deflazacort</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Deflazacort.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13003</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cortivazol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Cortivazol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednylidene</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Prednylidene.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13728</drugbank-id>
      <name>Halometasone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Halometasone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13843</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cloprednol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Cloprednol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13867</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluticasone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Fluticasone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14512</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mometasone furoate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Mometasone furoate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14538</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrocortisone aceponate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Hydrocortisone aceponate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14539</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrocortisone acetate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Hydrocortisone acetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14545</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrocortisone succinate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Hydrocortisone succinate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14631</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisolone phosphate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Prednisolone phosphate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14633</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisolone hemisuccinate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Prednisolone hemisuccinate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14634</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluprednidene acetate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Fluprednidene acetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14644</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylprednisolone hemisuccinate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Methylprednisolone hemisuccinate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14646</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisone acetate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Prednisone acetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14652</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clocortolone acetate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Clocortolone acetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14659</drugbank-id>
      <name>Melengestrol acetate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Melengestrol acetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14669</drugbank-id>
      <name>Betamethasone phosphate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Betamethasone phosphate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14681</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cortisone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Cortisone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00687</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fludrocortisone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Fludrocortisone can be increased when it is combined with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01410</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ciclesonide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ciclesonide can be increased when it is combined with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00559</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bosentan</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Bosentan.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00564</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbamazepine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Carbamazepine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00319</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piperacillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Piperacillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00415</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ampicillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Ampicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00417</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenoxymethylpenicillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Phenoxymethylpenicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00578</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbenicillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Carbenicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00713</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxacillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Oxacillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00739</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hetacillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Hetacillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00895</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benzylpenicilloyl polylysine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Benzylpenicilloyl polylysine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00948</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mezlocillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Mezlocillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01000</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclacillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Cyclacillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01053</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benzylpenicillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Benzylpenicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01060</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amoxicillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Amoxicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01061</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azlocillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Azlocillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01147</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cloxacillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Cloxacillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01163</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amdinocillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Amdinocillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01602</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bacampicillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Bacampicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01603</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meticillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Meticillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01604</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pivampicillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Pivampicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01605</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pivmecillinam</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Pivmecillinam.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01607</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ticarcillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Ticarcillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08795</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azidocillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Azidocillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09319</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carindacillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Carindacillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09320</drugbank-id>
      <name>Procaine benzylpenicillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Procaine benzylpenicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12127</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sultamicillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Sultamicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12343</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temocillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Temocillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13300</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epicillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Epicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13337</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pheneticillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Pheneticillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13506</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carfecillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Carfecillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13660</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propicillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Propicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13686</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clometocillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Clometocillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13693</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulbenicillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Sulbenicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13739</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penamecillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Penamecillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13814</drugbank-id>
      <name>Talampicillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Talampicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13816</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aspoxicillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Aspoxicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13836</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metampicillin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Metampicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00001</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lepirudin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Lepirudin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00006</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bivalirudin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Bivalirudin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00009</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alteplase</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Alteplase can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00013</drugbank-id>
      <name>Urokinase</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Urokinase can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00015</drugbank-id>
      <name>Reteplase</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Reteplase can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00029</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anistreplase</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Anistreplase can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00031</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenecteplase</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Tenecteplase can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00054</drugbank-id>
      <name>Abciximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Abciximab can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00055</drugbank-id>
      <name>Drotrecogin alfa</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Drotrecogin alfa can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00086</drugbank-id>
      <name>Streptokinase</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Streptokinase can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00261</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anagrelide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Anagrelide can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00266</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dicoumarol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Dicoumarol can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00278</drugbank-id>
      <name>Argatroban</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Argatroban can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00407</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ardeparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ardeparin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00498</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenindione</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Phenindione can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00569</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fondaparinux</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Fondaparinux can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00682</drugbank-id>
      <name>Warfarin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Warfarin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00686</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentosan polysulfate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Pentosan polysulfate can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00945</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetylsalicylic acid</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Acetylsalicylic acid can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00946</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenprocoumon</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Phenprocoumon can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00975</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dipyridamole</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Dipyridamole can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01088</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iloprost</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Iloprost can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01109</drugbank-id>
      <name>Heparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Heparin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01225</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enoxaparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Enoxaparin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01240</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epoprostenol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Epoprostenol can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01418</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acenocoumarol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Acenocoumarol can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03410</drugbank-id>
      <name>4-hydroxycoumarin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of 4-hydroxycoumarin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04665</drugbank-id>
      <name>Coumarin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Coumarin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04898</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ximelagatran</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ximelagatran can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04925</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desmoteplase</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Desmoteplase can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04932</drugbank-id>
      <name>Defibrotide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Defibrotide can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05099</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ancrod</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ancrod can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05229</drugbank-id>
      <name>Beraprost</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Beraprost can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05254</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fibrinolysin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Fibrinolysin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06209</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prasugrel</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Prasugrel can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06228</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rivaroxaban</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Rivaroxaban can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06271</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulodexide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sulodexide can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06294</drugbank-id>
      <name>Semuloparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Semuloparin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06406</drugbank-id>
      <name>Idraparinux</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Idraparinux can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06441</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cangrelor</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Cangrelor can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06543</drugbank-id>
      <name>Astaxanthin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Astaxanthin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06605</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apixaban</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Apixaban can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06635</drugbank-id>
      <name>Otamixaban</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Otamixaban can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06679</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amediplase</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Amediplase can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06695</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dabigatran etexilate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Dabigatran etexilate can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06754</drugbank-id>
      <name>Danaparoid</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Danaparoid can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06779</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dalteparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Dalteparin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06822</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tinzaparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Tinzaparin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07767</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferulic acid</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ferulic acid can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08496</drugbank-id>
      <name>(R)-warfarin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of (R)-warfarin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08794</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethyl biscoumacetate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ethyl biscoumacetate can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08813</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nadroparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Nadroparin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08814</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triflusal</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Triflusal can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08816</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ticagrelor</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ticagrelor can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08994</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ditazole</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ditazole can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09030</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vorapaxar</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Vorapaxar can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09075</drugbank-id>
      <name>Edoxaban</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Edoxaban can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09125</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium citrate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Potassium citrate can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09154</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium citrate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sodium citrate can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09255</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dextran</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Dextran can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09258</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bemiparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Bemiparin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09259</drugbank-id>
      <name>Reviparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Reviparin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09260</drugbank-id>
      <name>Parnaparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Parnaparin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09261</drugbank-id>
      <name>Certoparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Certoparin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11095</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desirudin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Desirudin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11154</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zinc citrate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Zinc citrate can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11166</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antithrombin Alfa</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Antithrombin Alfa can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11312</drugbank-id>
      <name>Protein C</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Protein C can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11598</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antithrombin III human</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Antithrombin III human can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11984</drugbank-id>
      <name>Letaxaban</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Letaxaban can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12289</drugbank-id>
      <name>Darexaban</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Darexaban can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12364</drugbank-id>
      <name>Betrixaban</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Betrixaban can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12598</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nafamostat</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Nafamostat can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12726</drugbank-id>
      <name>Monteplase</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Monteplase can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12831</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gabexate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Gabexate can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13136</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluindione</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Fluindione can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13149</drugbank-id>
      <name>Protein S human</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Protein S human can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13199</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brinase</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Brinase can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13275</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clorindione</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Clorindione can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13347</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diphenadione</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Diphenadione can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13451</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tioclomarol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Tioclomarol can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13616</drugbank-id>
      <name>Melagatran</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Melagatran can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13646</drugbank-id>
      <name>Saruplase</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Saruplase can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14055</drugbank-id>
      <name>(S)-Warfarin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of (S)-Warfarin can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14094</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tocopherylquinone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Tocopherylquinone can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14598</drugbank-id>
      <name>Edetate calcium disodium anhydrous</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Edetate calcium disodium anhydrous can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14600</drugbank-id>
      <name>Edetate disodium anhydrous</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Edetate disodium anhydrous can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14726</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dabigatran</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Dabigatran can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00688</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mycophenolate mofetil</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Mycophenolate mofetil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01024</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mycophenolic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Mycophenolic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00607</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nafcillin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Nafcillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00307</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bexarotene</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Bexarotene.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00625</drugbank-id>
      <name>Efavirenz</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Efavirenz.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00745</drugbank-id>
      <name>Modafinil</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Modafinil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06414</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etravirine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Etravirine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06442</drugbank-id>
      <name>Avasimibe</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Avasimibe.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08912</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dabrafenib</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Dabrafenib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14240</drugbank-id>
      <name>Echinacea</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Echinacea.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04908</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flibanserin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol is combined with Flibanserin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09065</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cobicistat</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Cobicistat.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09101</drugbank-id>
      <name>Elvitegravir</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Elvitegravir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00432</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trifluridine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when used in combination with Trifluridine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00301</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flucloxacillin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Flucloxacillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00485</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dicloxacillin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Dicloxacillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00082</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pegvisomant</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Pegvisomant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00091</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclosporine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Cyclosporine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00136</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcitriol</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Calcitriol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00197</drugbank-id>
      <name>Troglitazone</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Troglitazone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00316</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetaminophen</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Acetaminophen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00338</drugbank-id>
      <name>Omeprazole</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Omeprazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00342</drugbank-id>
      <name>Terfenadine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Terfenadine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00357</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aminoglutethimide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Aminoglutethimide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00363</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clozapine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Clozapine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00396</drugbank-id>
      <name>Progesterone</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Progesterone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00439</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cerivastatin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Cerivastatin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00448</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lansoprazole</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Lansoprazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00454</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meperidine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Meperidine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00468</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Quinine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00503</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ritonavir</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Ritonavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00531</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclophosphamide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Cyclophosphamide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00533</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rofecoxib</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Rofecoxib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00570</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vinblastine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Vinblastine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00603</drugbank-id>
      <name>Medroxyprogesterone acetate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Medroxyprogesterone acetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00624</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Testosterone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00636</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clofibrate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Clofibrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00675</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tamoxifen</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Tamoxifen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00769</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrocortamate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Hydrocortamate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00773</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etoposide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Etoposide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Estradiol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00812</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenylbutazone</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Phenylbutazone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00857</drugbank-id>
      <name>Terbinafine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Terbinafine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00898</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethanol</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Ethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00957</drugbank-id>
      <name>Norgestimate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Norgestimate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01011</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metyrapone</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Metyrapone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01030</drugbank-id>
      <name>Topotecan</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Topotecan.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01032</drugbank-id>
      <name>Probenecid</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Probenecid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01083</drugbank-id>
      <name>Orlistat</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Orlistat.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01115</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nifedipine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Nifedipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01132</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pioglitazone</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Pioglitazone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01138</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfinpyrazone</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Sulfinpyrazone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01181</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ifosfamide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Ifosfamide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01201</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rifapentine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Rifapentine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01221</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketamine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Ketamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01229</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paclitaxel</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Paclitaxel.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01333</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefradine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Cefradine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01352</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aprobarbital</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Aprobarbital.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01394</drugbank-id>
      <name>Colchicine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Colchicine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01609</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deferasirox</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Deferasirox.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metamizole</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Metamizole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04905</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tesmilifene</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Tesmilifene.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04920</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clevidipine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Clevidipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06273</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tocilizumab</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Tocilizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06636</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isavuconazonium</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Isavuconazonium.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06708</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lumefantrine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Lumefantrine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06717</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosaprepitant</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Fosaprepitant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06739</drugbank-id>
      <name>Seratrodast</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Seratrodast.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08881</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vemurafenib</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Vemurafenib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08905</drugbank-id>
      <name>Formestane</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Formestane.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08911</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trametinib</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Trametinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09054</drugbank-id>
      <name>Idelalisib</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Idelalisib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09330</drugbank-id>
      <name>Osimertinib</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Osimertinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11633</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isavuconazole</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Isavuconazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11642</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pitolisant</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Pitolisant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12267</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brigatinib</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Brigatinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13874</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enasidenib</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Enasidenib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13943</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone cypionate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Testosterone cypionate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13944</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone enanthate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Testosterone enanthate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13946</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone undecanoate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Testosterone undecanoate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13952</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol acetate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Estradiol acetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13953</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol benzoate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Estradiol benzoate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13954</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol cypionate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Estradiol cypionate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13955</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol dienanthate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Estradiol dienanthate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13956</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol valerate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Estradiol valerate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14568</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ivosidenib</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Ivosidenib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00834</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mifepristone</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Mifepristone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00477</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorpromazine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Chlorpromazine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00602</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ivermectin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Ivermectin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00333</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methadone</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Methadone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00163</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vitamin E</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Vitamin E.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00701</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amprenavir</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Amprenavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00648</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mitotane</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Mitotane.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01045</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rifampicin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Rifampicin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01220</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rifaximin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Rifaximin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Midostaurin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Midostaurin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08899</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enzalutamide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Enzalutamide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09280</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lumacaftor</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Lumacaftor.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11753</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rifamycin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Rifamycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11901</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apalutamide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Apalutamide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rifabutin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Rifabutin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01645</drugbank-id>
      <name>Genistein</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Genistein.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04911</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oritavancin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Oritavancin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06413</drugbank-id>
      <name>Armodafinil</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Armodafinil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08909</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glycerol phenylbutyrate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Glycerol phenylbutyrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09036</drugbank-id>
      <name>Siltuximab</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Siltuximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09078</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lenvatinib</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Lenvatinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11586</drugbank-id>
      <name>Asunaprevir</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Asunaprevir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11767</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sarilumab</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Sarilumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11823</drugbank-id>
      <name>Esketamine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Esketamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12015</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alpelisib</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Alpelisib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11560</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lesinurad</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Lesinurad.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00254</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxycycline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Doxycycline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00256</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lymecycline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Lymecycline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00453</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clomocycline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Clomocycline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00560</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tigecycline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Tigecycline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxytetracycline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Oxytetracycline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00618</drugbank-id>
      <name>Demeclocycline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Demeclocycline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00759</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetracycline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Tetracycline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00931</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metacycline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Metacycline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01017</drugbank-id>
      <name>Minocycline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Minocycline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01301</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rolitetracycline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Rolitetracycline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12035</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sarecycline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Sarecycline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12329</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eravacycline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Eravacycline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12455</drugbank-id>
      <name>Omadacycline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Omadacycline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13092</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meclocycline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Meclocycline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penimepicycline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Penimepicycline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00252</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenytoin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Phenytoin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00312</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentobarbital</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Pentobarbital.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00776</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxcarbazepine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Oxcarbazepine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00794</drugbank-id>
      <name>Primidone</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Primidone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01174</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenobarbital</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Phenobarbital.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01320</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosphenytoin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Fosphenytoin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00273</drugbank-id>
      <name>Topiramate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Topiramate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00949</drugbank-id>
      <name>Felbamate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Felbamate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06201</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rufinamide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Rufinamide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09119</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eslicarbazepine acetate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Eslicarbazepine acetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14575</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eslicarbazepine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Eslicarbazepine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00241</drugbank-id>
      <name>Butalbital</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Butalbital.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00418</drugbank-id>
      <name>Secobarbital</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Secobarbital.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00474</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methohexital</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Methohexital.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00599</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiopental</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Thiopental.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00754</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethotoin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Ethotoin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00849</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylphenobarbital</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Methylphenobarbital.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01154</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiamylal</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Thiamylal.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01351</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amobarbital</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Amobarbital.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01355</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hexobarbital</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Hexobarbital.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01483</drugbank-id>
      <name>Barbital</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Barbital.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08883</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perampanel</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Perampanel.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09001</drugbank-id>
      <name>Barbexaclone</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Barbexaclone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00186</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lorazepam</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Lorazepam.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00230</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pregabalin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Pregabalin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00313</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valproic acid</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Valproic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00347</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimethadione</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Trimethadione.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00463</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metharbital</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Metharbital.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00532</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mephenytoin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Mephenytoin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00555</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lamotrigine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Lamotrigine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00593</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethosuximide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Ethosuximide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00617</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paramethadione</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Paramethadione.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00628</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clorazepic acid</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Clorazepic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00653</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium sulfate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Magnesium sulfate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00697</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tizanidine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Tizanidine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00740</drugbank-id>
      <name>Riluzole</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Riluzole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00819</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetazolamide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Acetazolamide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00829</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diazepam</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Diazepam.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00832</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phensuximide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Phensuximide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00837</drugbank-id>
      <name>Progabide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Progabide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00906</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiagabine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Tiagabine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00909</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zonisamide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Zonisamide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00962</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zaleplon</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Zaleplon.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00996</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gabapentin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Gabapentin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01068</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clonazepam</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Clonazepam.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01080</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vigabatrin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Vigabatrin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01121</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenacemide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Phenacemide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01202</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levetiracetam</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Levetiracetam.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01215</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estazolam</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Estazolam.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01511</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delorazepam</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Delorazepam.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitrazepam</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Nitrazepam.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02207</drugbank-id>
      <name>7-Nitroindazole</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with 7-Nitroindazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04165</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valpromide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Valpromide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04841</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flunarizine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Flunarizine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04953</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ezogabine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Ezogabine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05246</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methsuximide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Methsuximide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05541</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brivaracetam</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Brivaracetam.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lacosamide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Lacosamide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06458</drugbank-id>
      <name>Remacemide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Remacemide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06470</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clomethiazole</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Clomethiazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06512</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deramciclane</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Deramciclane.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06527</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tramiprosate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Tramiprosate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06554</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gaboxadol</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Gaboxadol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08329</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulthiame</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Sulthiame.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08954</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ifenprodil</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Ifenprodil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09011</drugbank-id>
      <name>Beclamide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Beclamide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09061</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cannabidiol</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Cannabidiol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09117</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paraldehyde</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Paraldehyde.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09118</drugbank-id>
      <name>Stiripentol</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Stiripentol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11400</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doramectin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Doramectin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11549</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiletamine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Tiletamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11859</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brexanolone</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Brexanolone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11868</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etiracetam</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Etiracetam.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12131</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vinpocetine</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Vinpocetine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12338</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carisbamate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Carisbamate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13362</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pheneturide</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Pheneturide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13396</drugbank-id>
      <name>Neocitrullamon</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Neocitrullamon.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13437</drugbank-id>
      <name>Medazepam</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Medazepam.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13455</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenibut</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Phenibut.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13799</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethadione</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Ethadione.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14050</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cannabidivarin</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Cannabidivarin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15203</drugbank-id>
      <name>JNJ-26489112</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with JNJ-26489112.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06119</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cenobamate</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with Cenobamate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01323</drugbank-id>
      <name>St. John's Wort</name>
      <description>The metabolism of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when combined with St. John's Wort.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00222</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glimepiride</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Glimepiride can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00414</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetohexamide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Acetohexamide can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00672</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorpropamide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Chlorpropamide can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00839</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolazamide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Tolazamide can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01016</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glyburide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Glyburide can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01067</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glipizide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Glipizide can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01120</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gliclazide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Gliclazide can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01124</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolbutamide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Tolbutamide can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01251</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gliquidone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Gliquidone can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01289</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glisoxepide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Glisoxepide can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08962</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glibornuride</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Glibornuride can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13406</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbutamide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Carbutamide can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13675</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metahexamide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Metahexamide can be decreased when used in combination with Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05521</drugbank-id>
      <name>Telaprevir</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be decreased when it is combined with Telaprevir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08873</drugbank-id>
      <name>Boceprevir</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol can be increased when it is combined with Boceprevir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06480</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prucalopride</name>
      <description>Prucalopride may increase the excretion rate of Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol which could result in a lower serum level and potentially a reduction in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06404</drugbank-id>
      <name>Human C1-esterase inhibitor</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of thromboembolism can be increased when Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol is combined with Human C1-esterase inhibitor.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09228</drugbank-id>
      <name>Conestat alfa</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of thromboembolism can be increased when Octylphenoxy polyethoxyethanol is combined with Conestat alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <calculated-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>1.31</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logS</kind>
      <value>-6.4</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Water Solubility</kind>
      <value>5.53e-04 g/l</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>2.78</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>89-[4-(2,4,4-trimethylpentan-2-yl)phenoxy]-3,6,9,12,15,18,21,24,27,30,33,36,39,42,45,48,51,54,57,60,63,66,69,72,75,78,81,84,87-nonacosaoxanonaoctacontan-1-ol</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Traditional IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>89-[4-(2,4,4-trimethylpentan-2-yl)phenoxy]-3,6,9,12,15,18,21,24,27,30,33,36,39,42,45,48,51,54,57,60,63,66,69,72,75,78,81,84,87-nonacosaoxanonaoctacontan-1-ol</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Weight</kind>
      <value>1527.9007</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Monoisotopic Weight</kind>
      <value>1526.953507826</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>SMILES</kind>
      <value>CC(C)(C)CC(C)(C)C1=CC=C(OCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCOCCO)C=C1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Formula</kind>
      <value>C74H142O31</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChI</kind>
      <value>InChI=1S/C74H142O31/c1-73(2,3)70-74(4,5)71-6-8-72(9-7-71)105-69-68-104-67-66-103-65-64-102-63-62-101-61-60-100-59-58-99-57-56-98-55-54-97-53-52-96-51-50-95-49-48-94-47-46-93-45-44-92-43-42-91-41-40-90-39-38-89-37-36-88-35-34-87-33-32-86-31-30-85-29-28-84-27-26-83-25-24-82-23-22-81-21-20-80-19-18-79-17-16-78-15-14-77-13-12-76-11-10-75/h6-9,75H,10-70H2,1-5H3</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChIKey</kind>
      <value>WEGJDERSZWOWIB-UHFFFAOYSA-N</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polar Surface Area (PSA)</kind>
      <value>297.13</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Refractivity</kind>
      <value>395.97</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polarizability</kind>
      <value>187.66</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rotatable Bond Count</kind>
      <value>93</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Acceptor Count</kind>
      <value>31</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Donor Count</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest acidic)</kind>
      <value>15.12</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest basic)</kind>
      <value>-2.7</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Physiological Charge</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Number of Rings</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Bioavailability</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rule of Five</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Ghose Filter</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>MDDR-Like Rule</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
  </calculated-properties>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Compound</resource>
      <identifier>14123494</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>46505911</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChemSpider</resource>
      <identifier>25056961</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PDB</resource>
      <identifier>DR6</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets>
    <target>
      <id>BE0003566</id>
      <name>Troponin C, skeletal muscle</name>
      <organism>Humans</organism>
      <actions/>
      <references>
        <articles>
          <article>
            <ref-id>A1991</ref-id>
            <pubmed-id>10592235</pubmed-id>
            <citation>Berman HM, Westbrook J, Feng Z, Gilliland G, Bhat TN, Weissig H, Shindyalov IN, Bourne PE: The Protein Data Bank. Nucleic Acids Res. 2000 Jan 1;28(1):235-42.</citation>
          </article>
        </articles>
        <textbooks/>
        <links/>
        <attachments/>
      </references>
      <known-action>unknown</known-action>
      <polypeptide id="P02585" source="Swiss-Prot">
        <name>Troponin C, skeletal muscle</name>
        <general-function>Calcium ion binding</general-function>
        <specific-function>Troponin is the central regulatory protein of striated muscle contraction. Tn consists of three components: Tn-I which is the inhibitor of actomyosin ATPase, Tn-T which contains the binding site for tropomyosin and Tn-C. The binding of calcium to Tn-C abolishes the inhibitory action of Tn on actin filaments.</specific-function>
        <gene-name>TNNC2</gene-name>
        <locus>20q12-q13.11</locus>
        <cellular-location/>
        <transmembrane-regions/>
        <signal-regions/>
        <theoretical-pi>3.81</theoretical-pi>
        <molecular-weight>18121.895</molecular-weight>
        <chromosome-location>20</chromosome-location>
        <organism ncbi-taxonomy-id="9606">Humans</organism>
        <external-identifiers>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>HUGO Gene Nomenclature Committee (HGNC)</resource>
            <identifier>HGNC:11944</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>GenBank Gene Database</resource>
            <identifier>X07898</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>GenBank Protein Database</resource>
            <identifier>36729</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>UniProtKB</resource>
            <identifier>P02585</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>UniProt Accession</resource>
            <identifier>TNNC2_HUMAN</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
        </external-identifiers>
        <synonyms/>
        <amino-acid-sequence format="FASTA">&gt;lcl|BSEQ0012479|Troponin C, skeletal muscle
MTDQQAEARSYLSEEMIAEFKAAFDMFDADGGGDISVKELGTVMRMLGQTPTKEELDAII
EEVDEDGSGTIDFEEFLVMMVRQMKEDAKGKSEEELAECFRIFDRNADGYIDPEELAEIF
RASGEHVTDEEIESLMKDGDKNNDGRIDFDEFLKMMEGVQ</amino-acid-sequence>
        <gene-sequence format="FASTA">&gt;lcl|BSEQ0012480|Troponin C, skeletal muscle (TNNC2)
ATGACGGACCAGCAGGCTGAGGCCAGGTCCTACCTCAGCGAAGAGATGATCGCTGAGTTC
AAGGCTGCCTTTGACATGTTTGATGCTGATGGTGGTGGGGACATCAGCGTCAAGGAGTTG
GGCACGGTGATGAGGATGCTGGGCCAGACACCCACCAAGGAGGAGCTGGACGCCATCATC
GAGGAGGTGGATGAGGACGGCAGCGGCACCATCGACTTCGAGGAGTTCTTGGTCATGATG
GTGCGCCAGATGAAAGAGGACGCGAAAGGGAAGAGCGAGGAGGAGCTGGCCGAGTGCTTC
CGCATCTTCGACAGGAATGCAGACGGCTACATCGACCCGGAGGAGCTGGCTGAGATTTTC
AGGGCCTCCGGGGAGCACGTGACGGACGAGGAGATCGAATCTCTGATGAAAGACGGCGAC
AAGAACAACGACGGCCGCATTGACTTCGACGAGTTCCTGAAGATGATGGAGGGCGTGCAG
TAA</gene-sequence>
        <pfams>
          <pfam>
            <identifier>PF13499</identifier>
            <name>EF-hand_7</name>
          </pfam>
          <pfam>
            <identifier>PF13833</identifier>
            <name>EF-hand_8</name>
          </pfam>
        </pfams>
        <go-classifiers>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>component</category>
            <description>cytosol</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>component</category>
            <description>troponin complex</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>function</category>
            <description>calcium ion binding</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>muscle filament sliding</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>regulation of muscle contraction</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>skeletal muscle contraction</description>
          </go-classifier>
        </go-classifiers>
      </polypeptide>
    </target>
  </targets>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>