<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2019-05-20" updated="2019-11-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB15246</drugbank-id>
  <name>Salvianolic acid A</name>
  <description>Salvianolic acid A is under investigation in clinical trial NCT03908242 (Phase I Study of Continuous Administration of Salvianolic Acid A Tablet).</description>
  <cas-number>96574-01-5</cas-number>
  <unii>51622542XO</unii>
  <average-mass>494.452</average-mass>
  <monoisotopic-mass>494.121296908</monoisotopic-mass>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A182489</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>2173008</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Murakami S, Kijima H, Isobe Y, Muramatsu M, Aihara H, Otomo S, Li LN, Ai CB: Effect of salvianolic acid A, a depside from roots of Salvia miltiorrhiza, on gastric H+,K(+)-ATPase. Planta Med. 1990 Aug;56(4):360-3. doi: 10.1055/s-2006-960982.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication/>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action/>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>4-Nitrophenylphosphatase, antagonists &amp; inhibitors</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Acids, Carbocyclic</category>
      <mesh-id>D000146</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Cinnamates</category>
      <mesh-id>D002934</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Drugs, Chinese Herbal</category>
      <mesh-id>D004365</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Enzyme Inhibitors</category>
      <mesh-id>D004791</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Gastric Acid Lowering Agents</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Hydroxy Acids</category>
      <mesh-id>D006880</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06616</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bosutinib</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Bosutinib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01066</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefditoren</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Cefditoren can be decreased when it is combined with Salvianolic acid A.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06695</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dabigatran etexilate</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dabigatran etexilate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08912</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dabrafenib</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dabrafenib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01254</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dasatinib</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dasatinib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00530</drugbank-id>
      <name>Erlotinib</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Erlotinib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01167</drugbank-id>
      <name>Itraconazole</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Itraconazole resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09027</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ledipasvir</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ledipasvir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00422</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylphenidate</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause an increase in the absorption of Methylphenidate resulting in an increased serum concentration and potentially a worsening of adverse effects.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06701</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexmethylphenidate</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause an increase in the absorption of Dexmethylphenidate resulting in an increased serum concentration and potentially a worsening of adverse effects.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04868</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nilotinib</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Nilotinib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06589</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pazopanib</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pazopanib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08931</drugbank-id>
      <name>Riociguat</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Riociguat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00451</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levothyroxine</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Levothyroxine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09020</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bisacodyl</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Bisacodyl can be decreased when used in combination with Salvianolic acid A.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00178</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ramipril</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ramipril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00492</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosinopril</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Fosinopril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00519</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trandolapril</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Trandolapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00542</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benazepril</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Benazepril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00584</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enalapril</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Enalapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00691</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moexipril</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Moexipril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00722</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lisinopril</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Lisinopril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00790</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perindopril</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Perindopril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00881</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinapril</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Quinapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00886</drugbank-id>
      <name>Omapatrilat</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Omapatrilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01180</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rescinnamine</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rescinnamine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01197</drugbank-id>
      <name>Captopril</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Captopril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01340</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cilazapril</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Cilazapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01348</drugbank-id>
      <name>Spirapril</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Spirapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08836</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temocapril</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Temocapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imidapril</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Imidapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13166</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zofenopril</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Zofenopril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13312</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delapril</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Delapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14125</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benazeprilat</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Benazeprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14207</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosinoprilat</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Fosinoprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ramiprilat</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ramiprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14209</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trandolaprilat</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Trandolaprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14210</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moexiprilat</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Moexiprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perindoprilat</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Perindoprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14217</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinaprilat</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Quinaprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14231</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinoline Yellow WS</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Quinoline Yellow WS resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00688</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mycophenolate mofetil</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Mycophenolate mofetil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01024</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mycophenolic acid</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Mycophenolic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01344</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolevamer</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Tolevamer can be decreased when used in combination with Salvianolic acid A.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00847</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cysteamine</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Cysteamine can be decreased when combined with Salvianolic acid A.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01026</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketoconazole</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ketoconazole resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06799</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methenamine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Methenamine can be decreased when used in combination with Salvianolic acid A.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00503</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ritonavir</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ritonavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00701</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amprenavir</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Amprenavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00932</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tipranavir</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Tipranavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Darunavir</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Darunavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01319</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosamprenavir</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Fosamprenavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01601</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lopinavir</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Lopinavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11586</drugbank-id>
      <name>Asunaprevir</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Asunaprevir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00220</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nelfinavir</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Nelfinavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00224</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indinavir</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Indinavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01232</drugbank-id>
      <name>Saquinavir</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Saquinavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Raltegravir</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause an increase in the absorption of Raltegravir resulting in an increased serum concentration and potentially a worsening of adverse effects.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09073</drugbank-id>
      <name>Palbociclib</name>
      <description>The absorption of Palbociclib can be decreased when combined with Salvianolic acid A.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01112</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefuroxime</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Cefuroxime can be decreased when it is combined with Salvianolic acid A.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01045</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rifampicin</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rifampicin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01043</drugbank-id>
      <name>Memantine</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A may decrease the excretion rate of Memantine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00391</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulpiride</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sulpiride can be increased when used in combination with Salvianolic acid A.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00244</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mesalazine</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Mesalazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prussian blue</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Prussian blue resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09146</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iron sucrose</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Iron sucrose resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09501</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric ammonium citrate</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferric ammonium citrate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09507</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferumoxsil</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09508</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferumoxides</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxides resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11171</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric sulfate</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferric sulfate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11210</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous bisglycinate</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferrous bisglycinate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11417</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gleptoferron</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Gleptoferron resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iron isomaltoside 1000</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Iron isomaltoside 1000 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12821</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perflubutane</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Perflubutane resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13257</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous sulfate anhydrous</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferrous sulfate anhydrous resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13381</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium feredetate</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sodium feredetate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13423</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric hydroxide</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferric hydroxide resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13569</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous chloride</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferrous chloride resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13949</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric cation</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferric cation resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14488</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous gluconate</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferrous gluconate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14489</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous succinate</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferrous succinate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14491</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous fumarate</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferrous fumarate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14520</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetraferric tricitrate decahydrate</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Tetraferric tricitrate decahydrate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14695</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric oxyhydroxide</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferric oxyhydroxide resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00893</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iron Dextran</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Iron Dextran resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01592</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iron</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Iron resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09147</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric pyrophosphate</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferric pyrophosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00705</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delavirdine</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Delavirdine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gefitinib</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Gefitinib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01072</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atazanavir</name>
      <description>Salvianolic acid A can cause a decrease in the absorption of Atazanavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <calculated-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>3.58</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logS</kind>
      <value>-4.8</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Water Solubility</kind>
      <value>8.67e-03 g/l</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>4.74</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>(2R)-3-(3,4-dihydroxyphenyl)-2-{[(2E)-3-{2-[(1E)-2-(3,4-dihydroxyphenyl)ethenyl]-3,4-dihydroxyphenyl}prop-2-enoyl]oxy}propanoic acid</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Traditional IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>(2R)-14-fluoro-2-methyl-6,9,10,19-tetraazapentacyclo[14.2.1.0^{2,6}.0^{8,18}.0^{12,17}]nonadeca-1(18),8,12(17),13,15-pentaen-11-one</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Weight</kind>
      <value>494.452</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Monoisotopic Weight</kind>
      <value>494.121296908</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>SMILES</kind>
      <value>OC(=O)[C@@H](CC1=CC(O)=C(O)C=C1)OC(=O)\C=C\C1=C(/C=C/C2=CC(O)=C(O)C=C2)C(O)=C(O)C=C1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Formula</kind>
      <value>C26H22O10</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChI</kind>
      <value>InChI=1S/C26H22O10/c27-18-7-2-14(11-21(18)30)1-6-17-16(4-9-20(29)25(17)33)5-10-24(32)36-23(26(34)35)13-15-3-8-19(28)22(31)12-15/h1-12,23,27-31,33H,13H2,(H,34,35)/b6-1+,10-5+/t23-/m1/s1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChIKey</kind>
      <value>YMGFTDKNIWPMGF-UCPJVGPRSA-N</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polar Surface Area (PSA)</kind>
      <value>184.98</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Refractivity</kind>
      <value>130.37</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polarizability</kind>
      <value>48.67</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rotatable Bond Count</kind>
      <value>9</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Acceptor Count</kind>
      <value>9</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Donor Count</kind>
      <value>7</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest acidic)</kind>
      <value>3.14</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest basic)</kind>
      <value>-6.3</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Physiological Charge</kind>
      <value>-1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Number of Rings</kind>
      <value>3</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Bioavailability</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rule of Five</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Ghose Filter</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>MDDR-Like Rule</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
  </calculated-properties>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEBI</resource>
      <identifier>9017</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>KEGG Compound</resource>
      <identifier>C10492</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChemSpider</resource>
      <identifier>4445105</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>BindingDB</resource>
      <identifier>50414250</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEMBL</resource>
      <identifier>CHEMBL457077</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>