<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2007-10-21" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB04923</drugbank-id>
  <name>rhThrombin</name>
  <description>rhThrombin (recombinant human thrombin) is being developed by ZymoGenetics, Inc. as a general aid to achieving hemostasis during surgery. ZymoGenetics is developing rhThrombin, a recombinant form of human thrombin that is not derived from animal or human blood, as an aid to controlling bleeding during surgery. Thrombin is used in more than 1 million surgeries each year in the United States. Currently, only thrombin derived from bovine blood is available in the U.S. as a stand-alone thrombin product. Bovine-derived thrombin has been associated with the development of antibodies that may cross-react with human blood proteins and in some cases these antibodies appear to be related to serious bleeding complications. The production of recombinant proteins is not dependent on the availability of blood from animals or human donors and can be scaled-up to meet market demand.</description>
  <cas-number>1270043-60-1</cas-number>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A2965</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17660072</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Chapman WC, Singla N, Genyk Y, McNeil JW, Renkens KL Jr, Reynolds TC, Murphy A, Weaver FA: A phase 3, randomized, double-blind comparative study of the efficacy and safety of topical recombinant human thrombin and bovine thrombin in surgical hemostasis. J Am Coll Surg. 2007 Aug;205(2):256-65. Epub 2007 Jun 27.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A2966</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>16971028</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Heffernan JK, Ponce RA, Zuckerman LA, Volpone JP, Visich J, Giste EE, Jenkins N, Boster D, Pederson S, Knitter G, Palmer T, Wills M, Early RJ, Rogge MC: Preclinical safety of recombinant human thrombin. Regul Toxicol Pharmacol. 2007 Feb;47(1):48-58. Epub 2006 Sep 12.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in blood (blood forming organ disorders, unspecified) and hemorrhage.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>Plasma-derived bovine thrombin is used as a topical agent to improve surgical hemostasis, but development of antibodies to bovine hemostatic proteins has been associated with increased bleeding and thrombotic complications. rhThrombin has a superior immunogenicity profile compared with bovine thrombin (1.5% versus 22%, respectively, p&lt;0.0001; antibodies developed to the products, as defined by seroconversion or significant change in titer units).  Characterization of the binding antibodies demonstrated none of the anti-rhThrombin antibodies neutralized human plasma thrombin.&#13;
&#13;
</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>The potent hemostatic properties of thrombin derive from its ability to activate platelets directly to aggregate and adhere to damaged vessels and to catalyze the formation simultaneously of a fibrin matrix. Application of exogenous thrombin bypasses the physiological process of generating a thrombin burst by directly initiating the terminal reactions of blood clot formation. rhThrombin rapidly binds to endogenous inhibitors following either i.v. or s.c. administration.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life>Approximately 15 hours (measured in non-human primates).</half-life>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Recombinant thrombin</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Recothrom</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">rhThrombin</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">rThrombin</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers/>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>