<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-11-18" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05929</drugbank-id>
  <name>GPI-0100</name>
  <description>GPI-0100 is Avantogen’s lead adjuvanat-immunopotentiator, a key component of vaccines for boosting the immune response.&#13;
The GPI-0100 adjuvant, which has been shown to significantly enhance the immune response with a variety of vaccines, has been shown to have good overall performance characteristics on safety and efficacy. </description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3909</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>15837210</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Slovin SF, Ragupathi G, Fernandez C, Jefferson MP, Diani M, Wilton AS, Powell S, Spassova M, Reis C, Clausen H, Danishefsky S, Livingston P, Scher HI: A bivalent conjugate vaccine in the treatment of biochemically relapsed prostate cancer: a study of glycosylated MUC-2-KLH and Globo H-KLH conjugate vaccines given with the new semi-synthetic saponin immunological adjuvant GPI-0100 OR QS-21. Vaccine. 2005 May 2;23(24):3114-22.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in breast cancer, kidney cancer, leukemia (myeloid), melanoma, neuroblastoma, ovarian cancer, and prostate cancer.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>A proprietary semi-synthetic saponin derivative, GPI-0100 acts by up-regulating the body's immune system and stimulating both humoral and an effective T-cell immunity with CTL production. Compared with other immune stimulatory saponins, GPI-0100 has superior stability and safety profile, making it an ideal candidate for the development of novel therapeutics or preventive vaccines.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Carbohydrates</category>
      <mesh-id>D002241</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Glycosides</category>
      <mesh-id>D006027</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910317</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>