<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2008-03-19" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB06415</drugbank-id>
  <name>Calfactant</name>
  <description>Calfactant is a sterile, non-pyrogenic lung surfactant intended for intratracheal instillation. It is an off-white suspension of an extract of natural surfactant from calf lungs suspended in 0.9% saline. Each milliliter of calfactant contains 35mg of phospholipids (including 26 mg phosphatidylcholine of which 16 mg is disaturated phosphatidylcholine) and 0.65mg of proteins including surfactant-associated proteins B and C.&#13;
&#13;
Calfactant is approved for use in the United States of America. It is used to prevent or treat respiratory distress syndrome in premature infants with lung surfactant deficiency. Calfactant has been shown to decrease the incidence of respiratory distress syndrome, mortality due to respiratory distress syndrome, and air leaks associated with respiratory distress syndrome in clinical trials. It adsorbs to the air:fluid interface in the lungs and works to reduce surface tension, in a manner similar to endogenous pulmonary surfactant.</description>
  <cas-number>183325-78-2</cas-number>
  <unii>Q4K217VGA9</unii>
  <state>liquid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A6832</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>11585026</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Willson D: Calfactant. Expert Opin Pharmacother. 2001 Sep;2(9):1479-93.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A6833</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>16061594</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Bloom BT, Clark RH: Comparison of Infasurf (calfactant) and Survanta (beractant) in the prevention and treatment of respiratory distress syndrome. Pediatrics. 2005 Aug;116(2):392-9.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A6834</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>15671432</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Willson DF, Thomas NJ, Markovitz BP, Bauman LA, DiCarlo JV, Pon S, Jacobs BR, Jefferson LS, Conaway MR, Egan EA: Effect of exogenous surfactant (calfactant) in pediatric acute lung injury: a randomized controlled trial. JAMA. 2005 Jan 26;293(4):470-6.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A6835</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>15201857</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Attar MA, Becker MA, Dechert RE, Donn SM: Immediate changes in lung compliance following natural surfactant administration in premature infants with respiratory distress syndrome: a controlled trial. J Perinatol. 2004 Oct;24(10):626-30.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A6836</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>23300398</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Nguyen TN, Cunsolo SM, Gal P, Ransom JL: Infasurf and curosurf: theoretical and practical considerations with new surfactants. J Pediatr Pharmacol Ther. 2003 Apr;8(2):97-114. doi: 10.5863/1551-6776-8.2.97.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A6837</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>9934915</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Willson DF, Zaritsky A, Bauman LA, Dockery K, James RL, Conrad D, Craft H, Novotny WE, Egan EA, Dalton H: Instillation of calf lung surfactant extract (calfactant) is beneficial in pediatric acute hypoxemic respiratory failure. Members of the Mid-Atlantic Pediatric Critical Care Network. Crit Care Med. 1999 Jan;27(1):188-95.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A6838</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>19436610</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Logan JW, Moya FR: Animal-derived surfactants for the treatment and prevention of neonatal respiratory distress syndrome: summary of clinical trials. Ther Clin Risk Manag. 2009 Feb;5(1):251-60. Epub 2009 Mar 26.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A6839</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25855884</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Willson DF, Truwit JD, Conaway MR, Traul CS, Egan EE: The Adult Calfactant in Acute Respiratory Distress Syndrome Trial. Chest. 2015 Aug;148(2):356-64. doi: 10.1378/chest.14-1139.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A6840</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>20063159</pubmed-id>
        <citation>McPherson C, Gal P, Ransom JL, Carlos RQ, Dimaguila MA, Smith M, Davonzo C, Wimmer JE Jr: Indomethacin pharmacodynamics are altered by surfactant: a possible challenge to current indomethacin dosing guidelines created before surfactant availability. Pediatr Cardiol. 2010 May;31(4):505-10. doi: 10.1007/s00246-009-9628-6. Epub 2010 Jan 10.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference>Notter RH, Wang Z, Egan EA, Holm BA: Component-specific surface and physiological activity in bovine-derived lung surfactants. Chem Phys Lipids. 2002 Jan;114(1):21-34. [Pubmed](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/11841823).</synthesis-reference>
  <indication>Calfactant is indicated for prophylaxis therapy to prevent respiratory distress syndrome (RDS) in premature infants &lt;29 weeks of gestational age with low lung surfactant and at high risk for RDS. Calfactant therapy is also indicated for the treatment of respiratory distress syndrome in infants 72 hours or less of age with RDS confirmed by clinical and radiologic findings and requiring endotracheal intubation.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>Pulmonary surfactant is an endogenous substance produced in the lungs that functions to decrease surface tension at the air:fluid interface on the alveolar surface. In premature infants with pulmonary surfactant deficiency, surface tension can increase to the point where sections of lung collapse and respiratory distress syndrome (RDS) develops. Calfactant adsorbs rapidly to the surface of the alveolar air:fluid interface and modifies surface tension to a minimum of less than 3 mN/m. It acts in a manner similar to natural lung surfactant, thus preventing or treating respiratory distress syndrome.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity>Carcinogenesis and animal reproduction studies have not been performed with calfactant. A single mutagenicity study produced a negative Ames assay. Overdose with calfactant has not yet been reported, but it is recommended that in the case of an overdose ventilation should be supported until all excess fluid is cleared from the lungs. Cyanosis, bradycardia and airway obstruction have been reported with administration of calfactant.</toxicity>
  <metabolism>Endogenous lung surfactant is produced and excreted by Type II alveolar pneumocytes to form a surface monolayer across the alveoli through adsorption. Through repeated contraction and expansion of an alveolus, this monolayer degrades and the surfactant is taken back up into the Type II alveolar pneumocyte for re-packaging. No human studies on the metabolism of calfactant have been completed, but it is likely metabolized through a similar mechanism to endogenous pulmonary surfactant.</metabolism>
  <absorption>Calfactant is administered directly to the lung lumen surface where it acts. No human studies on absorption have been completed.</absorption>
  <half-life>Half time clearance from the lung lumen was reported as 12 hours in a study of normal rabbits. </half-life>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination>No human studies on elimination of calfactant have been completed.</route-of-elimination>
  <volume-of-distribution>No human studies on the distribution of calfactant have been performed.</volume-of-distribution>
  <clearance>No human studies on the metabolism and elimination of calfactant have been performed.</clearance>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Bovactant</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Calf lung surfactant extract (CLSE)</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="usan">Calfactant</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>Bles</name>
      <labeller>Bles Biochemicals Inc</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>02245464</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2002-02-05</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Suspension</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Endotracheal</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Infasurf</name>
      <labeller>ONY Biotech Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>61938-456</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2011-07-21</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Suspension</dosage-form>
      <strength>35.7 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Endotracheal</route>
      <fda-application-number>NDA020521</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Neosurf</name>
      <labeller>Cipla Ltd</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>02288621</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on/>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Suspension</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Endotracheal</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>Infasurf</name>
      <ingredients>Calfactant</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Bles</name>
      <ingredients>Calfactant</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Neosurf</name>
      <ingredients>Calfactant</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Alveolar Surface Tension Reduction</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Bradycardia-Causing Agents</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Complex Mixtures</category>
      <mesh-id>D045424</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Pulmonary Surfactants</category>
      <mesh-id>D011663</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Respiratory System Agents</category>
      <mesh-id>D019141</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Surface-Active Agents</category>
      <mesh-id>D013501</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Surfactant Activity</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Suspension</form>
      <route>Endotracheal</route>
      <strength/>
    </dosage>
    <dosage>
      <form>Suspension</form>
      <route>Endotracheal</route>
      <strength>35.7 mg/1mL</strength>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <fda-label>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/fda_labels/DB06415.pdf?1454790347</fda-label>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09063</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceritinib</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Ceritinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09083</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ivabradine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Ivabradine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08877</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ruxolitinib</name>
      <description>Ruxolitinib may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00104</drugbank-id>
      <name>Octreotide</name>
      <description>Octreotide may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00187</drugbank-id>
      <name>Esmolol</name>
      <description>Esmolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00195</drugbank-id>
      <name>Betaxolol</name>
      <description>Betaxolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00211</drugbank-id>
      <name>Midodrine</name>
      <description>Midodrine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00230</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pregabalin</name>
      <description>Pregabalin may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metoprolol</name>
      <description>Metoprolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00270</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isradipine</name>
      <description>Isradipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00335</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atenolol</name>
      <description>Atenolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00343</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diltiazem</name>
      <description>Diltiazem may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00347</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimethadione</name>
      <description>Trimethadione may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00373</drugbank-id>
      <name>Timolol</name>
      <description>Timolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00381</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amlodipine</name>
      <description>Amlodipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00390</drugbank-id>
      <name>Digoxin</name>
      <description>Digoxin may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00393</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nimodipine</name>
      <description>Nimodipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00401</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nisoldipine</name>
      <description>Nisoldipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00436</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bendroflumethiazide</name>
      <description>Bendroflumethiazide may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00489</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sotalol</name>
      <description>Sotalol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00528</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lercanidipine</name>
      <description>Lercanidipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00555</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lamotrigine</name>
      <description>Lamotrigine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00568</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cinnarizine</name>
      <description>Cinnarizine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00571</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propranolol</name>
      <description>Propranolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00575</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clonidine</name>
      <description>Clonidine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00593</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethosuximide</name>
      <description>Ethosuximide may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00598</drugbank-id>
      <name>Labetalol</name>
      <description>Labetalol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00612</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bisoprolol</name>
      <description>Bisoprolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00622</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nicardipine</name>
      <description>Nicardipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00633</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexmedetomidine</name>
      <description>Dexmedetomidine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00653</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium sulfate</name>
      <description>Magnesium sulfate may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00661</drugbank-id>
      <name>Verapamil</name>
      <description>Verapamil may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00674</drugbank-id>
      <name>Galantamine</name>
      <description>Galantamine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00697</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tizanidine</name>
      <description>Tizanidine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00708</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sufentanil</name>
      <description>Sufentanil may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00802</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alfentanil</name>
      <description>Alfentanil may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00813</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fentanyl</name>
      <description>Fentanyl may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00825</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levomenthol</name>
      <description>Levomenthol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00836</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loperamide</name>
      <description>Loperamide may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00843</drugbank-id>
      <name>Donepezil</name>
      <description>Donepezil may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00866</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alprenolol</name>
      <description>Alprenolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00899</drugbank-id>
      <name>Remifentanil</name>
      <description>Remifentanil may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00909</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zonisamide</name>
      <description>Zonisamide may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00960</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pindolol</name>
      <description>Pindolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00968</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methyldopa</name>
      <description>Methyldopa may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00989</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rivastigmine</name>
      <description>Rivastigmine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01018</drugbank-id>
      <name>Guanfacine</name>
      <description>Guanfacine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01023</drugbank-id>
      <name>Felodipine</name>
      <description>Felodipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01054</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitrendipine</name>
      <description>Nitrendipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01074</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perhexiline</name>
      <description>Perhexiline may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01115</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nifedipine</name>
      <description>Nifedipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01118</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amiodarone</name>
      <description>Amiodarone may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01136</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carvedilol</name>
      <description>Carvedilol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01158</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bretylium</name>
      <description>Bretylium may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01182</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propafenone</name>
      <description>Propafenone may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01193</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acebutolol</name>
      <description>Acebutolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01203</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nadolol</name>
      <description>Nadolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01244</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bepridil</name>
      <description>Bepridil may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01295</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bevantolol</name>
      <description>Bevantolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01297</drugbank-id>
      <name>Practolol</name>
      <description>Practolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01359</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penbutolol</name>
      <description>Penbutolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01388</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mibefradil</name>
      <description>Mibefradil may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01580</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxprenolol</name>
      <description>Oxprenolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04743</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nimesulide</name>
      <description>Nimesulide may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04825</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prenylamine</name>
      <description>Prenylamine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04838</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclandelate</name>
      <description>Cyclandelate may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04841</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flunarizine</name>
      <description>Flunarizine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04842</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluspirilene</name>
      <description>Fluspirilene may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04846</drugbank-id>
      <name>Celiprolol</name>
      <description>Celiprolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04855</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dronedarone</name>
      <description>Dronedarone may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04861</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nebivolol</name>
      <description>Nebivolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04897</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lucinactant</name>
      <description>Lucinactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04920</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clevidipine</name>
      <description>Clevidipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05246</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methsuximide</name>
      <description>Methsuximide may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05885</drugbank-id>
      <name>Seletracetam</name>
      <description>Seletracetam may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06152</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nylidrin</name>
      <description>Nylidrin may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lacosamide</name>
      <description>Lacosamide may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06283</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ziconotide</name>
      <description>Ziconotide may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06446</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dotarizine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Dotarizine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06663</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pasireotide</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Pasireotide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06712</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nilvadipine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Nilvadipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06726</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bufuralol</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Bufuralol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06761</drugbank-id>
      <name>Beractant</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Beractant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06791</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lanreotide</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Lanreotide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tranilast</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Tranilast.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08807</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bopindolol</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Bopindolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08808</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bupranolol</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Bupranolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08838</drugbank-id>
      <name>Agmatine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Agmatine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08865</drugbank-id>
      <name>Crizotinib</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Crizotinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08868</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fingolimod</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Fingolimod.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08895</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tofacitinib</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Tofacitinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08896</drugbank-id>
      <name>Regorafenib</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Regorafenib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08952</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indenolol</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Indenolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08980</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fendiline</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Fendiline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08992</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eperisone</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Eperisone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09013</drugbank-id>
      <name>Befunolol</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Befunolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09089</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimebutine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Trimebutine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09090</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pinaverium</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Pinaverium.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09113</drugbank-id>
      <name>Poractant alfa</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09204</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arotinolol</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Arotinolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09216</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolfenamic acid</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Tolfenamic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09227</drugbank-id>
      <name>Barnidipine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Barnidipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09229</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aranidipine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Aranidipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09230</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azelnidipine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Azelnidipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09231</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benidipine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Benidipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09232</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cilnidipine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Cilnidipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09234</drugbank-id>
      <name>Darodipine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Darodipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09235</drugbank-id>
      <name>Efonidipine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Efonidipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09236</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lacidipine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Lacidipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09238</drugbank-id>
      <name>Manidipine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Manidipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09239</drugbank-id>
      <name>Niguldipine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Niguldipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09240</drugbank-id>
      <name>Niludipine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Niludipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09351</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levobetaxolol</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Levobetaxolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11770</drugbank-id>
      <name>Talinolol</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Talinolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11785</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anisodamine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Anisodamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11960</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carboxyamidotriazole</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Carboxyamidotriazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12092</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naftopidil</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Naftopidil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12093</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetrahydropalmatine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Tetrahydropalmatine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12131</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vinpocetine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Vinpocetine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12212</drugbank-id>
      <name>Landiolol</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Landiolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12752</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bucindolol</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Bucindolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12923</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gallopamil</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Gallopamil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13443</drugbank-id>
      <name>Esatenolol</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Esatenolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13488</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bencyclane</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Bencyclane.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13500</drugbank-id>
      <name>Otilonium</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Otilonium.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13508</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cloranolol</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Cloranolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13530</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mepindolol</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Mepindolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13725</drugbank-id>
      <name>Terodiline</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Terodiline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13757</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epanolol</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Epanolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13766</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lidoflazine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Lidoflazine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13775</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tertatolol</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Tertatolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13791</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penfluridol</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Penfluridol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13835</drugbank-id>
      <name>Caroverine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Caroverine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13950</drugbank-id>
      <name>WIN 55212-2</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of WIN 55212-2.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13961</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fish oil</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Fish oil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14063</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexverapamil</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Dexverapamil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14064</drugbank-id>
      <name>Emopamil</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Emopamil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14065</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lomerizine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Lomerizine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14066</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetrandrine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Tetrandrine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14068</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexniguldipine</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Dexniguldipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11732</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lasmiditan</name>
      <description>Lasmiditan may increase the bradycardic activities of Calfactant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910351</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>KEGG Drug</resource>
      <identifier>D03317</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Wikipedia</resource>
      <identifier>Calfactant</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEMBL</resource>
      <identifier>CHEMBL1201447</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links>
    <external-link>
      <resource>RxList</resource>
      <url>http://www.rxlist.com/infasurf-drug.htm</url>
    </external-link>
    <external-link>
      <resource>PDRhealth</resource>
      <url>http://www.everydayhealth.com/drugs/calfactant</url>
    </external-link>
    <external-link>
      <resource>Drugs.com</resource>
      <url>http://www.drugs.com/mtm/calfactant.html</url>
    </external-link>
  </external-links>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>