<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2007-11-18" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05671</drugbank-id>
  <name>AC-100</name>
  <description>AC-100 is a novel synthetic peptide derived from an endogenous human protein produced by bone and dental cells (a fragment from matrix extracellular phosphoglycoprotein). It is being developed by Acologix, Inc.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3721</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>16530063</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Goldberg M, Lacerda-Pinheiro S, Jegat N, Six N, Septier D, Priam F, Bonnefoix M, Tompkins K, Chardin H, Denbesten P, Veis A, Poliard A: The impact of bioactive molecules to stimulate tooth repair and regeneration as part of restorative dentistry. Dent Clin North Am. 2006 Apr;50(2):277-98, x.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3722</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>15040834</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Hayashibara T, Hiraga T, Yi B, Nomizu M, Kumagai Y, Nishimura R, Yoneda T: A synthetic peptide fragment of human MEPE stimulates new bone formation in vitro and in vivo. J Bone Miner Res. 2004 Mar;19(3):455-62. Epub 2003 Dec 29.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3723</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>15153459</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Liu H, Li W, Gao C, Kumagai Y, Blacher RW, DenBesten PK: Dentonin, a fragment of MEPE, enhanced dental pulp stem cell proliferation. J Dent Res. 2004 Jun;83(6):496-9.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in periodontal disease.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>In animal models, AC-100 promoted cartilage regeneration. In the study, goats with an osteochondral femoral condylar (knee cartilage) defect were used to evaluate the effects of AC-100 on cartilage regeneration. Cylindrical defects were created in the knee cartilage and were filled with a collagen sponge containing AC-100 at two different doses or a collagen sponge soaked in saline (control group). Post-operative treatments included intra-articular injections of the test articles into the operated knee joint at weeks one, two and three post surgery. Cartilage regeneration was evaluated in one group after 84 days and 168 days in another group. The results demonstrated that the application of AC-100 dose dependently promoted cartilage defect repair. The groups treated with the higher dosage of AC-100 had greater healing outcome scores than the saline control groups. As there was no evidence of an inflammatory response, AC-100 demonstrated a favorable safety profile in the study.</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>In several preclinical models, AC-100 has demonstrated potent and selective dental tissue and bone formation activity, however the exact mechanism is not known. One study (PMID:15153459) showed that AC-100 enhances dental pulp stem cell (DPSC) proliferation by down-regulating P16, accompanied by up-regulation of ubiquitin protein ligase E3A and human ubiquitin-related protein SUMO-1. Enhanced cell proliferation required intact RGD and SGDG motifs in the peptide. This study shows that AC-100 can promote DPSC proliferation, with a potential role in pulp repair. </mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Dentonin</name>
      <company/>
    </international-brand>
  </international-brands>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences>
    <sequence format="FASTA">&gt;Matrix extracellular phosphoglycoprotein (242-264)
TDLQERGDNDISPFSGDGQPFKD</sequence>
  </sequences>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910188</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>