<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2008-03-19" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB06361</drugbank-id>
  <name>rsPSMA Vaccine</name>
  <description>Prostate-specific membrane antigen (PSMA) is an ∼100 kDa transmembrane glycoprotein that is abundantly and preferentially expressed in prostate cancer, including recurrent and hormone-refractory cases. rsPSMA Vaccine is a subunit vaccine based on a novel rsPSMA protein that represents the entire extracellular domain of PSMA (Schulke et al., PNAS 100:12590, 2003). The vaccine comprises purified rsPSMA protein formulated with Alhydrogel® adjuvant. In preclinical studies, rsPSMA elicited high-titer antibodies that strongly cross-reacted with prostate cancer cells. [L1039]</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L1039</ref-id>
        <title>Recombinant soluble prostate-specific membrane antigen (rsPSMA) vaccine</title>
        <url>http://ascopubs.org/doi/10.1200/jco.2004.22.14_suppl.2584</url>
      </link>
    </links>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in prostate cancer.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>rsPSMA vaccine with Alhydrogel demonstrated safety and tolerability in addition to the induction of high-titer PSMA-specific antibodies (Abs) by ELISA with specificity directed to cell-surface, native PSMA as indicated by FACS analysis using cells expressing PSMA.&#13;
&#13;
Like native, cell-surface PSMA, the rsPSMA protein was discovered to form a noncovalent dimer, and only the dimeric form of rsPSMA was enzymatically active and capable of inducing high levels of antibodies that cross-react with PSMA-expressing tumor cells. The findings provide important proof-of-concept for our rsPSMA vaccine</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Recombinant soluble prostate-specific membrane antigen (rsPSMA) vaccine</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">rsPSMA</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers/>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>