<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2007-11-18" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05512</drugbank-id>
  <name>MM-093</name>
  <description>MM-093 is a recombinant version of human alpha-fetoprotein (hAFP), an immunomodulatory serum protein normally produced at very high levels by the fetus and present in low levels in the blood of adults and children. Research on AFP suggests that it may play a role in modulating the immune system of the mother in order to protect the developing fetus during pregnancy. The presence of hAFP in the pregnant mother’s blood has long been associated with remission of many autoimmune diseases, including rheumatoid arthritis, psoriasis and multiple sclerosis, during the third trimester of pregnancy. Current studies are assessing MM-093’s potential to improve the treatment of autoimmune disease.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3667</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>18041671</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Dudich E: MM-093, a recombinant human alpha-fetoprotein for the potential treatment of rheumatoid arthritis and other autoimmune diseases. Curr Opin Mol Ther. 2007 Dec;9(6):603-10.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in autoimmune diseases, psoriasis and psoriatic disorders, and rheumatoid arthritis.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>M-093 (Merrimack Pharmaceuticals, Cambridge, Massachusetts, USA) is a non-glycosylated version of human AFP produced by recombinant DNA technology in a transgenic goat expression system.. hAFP is an immunomodulatory serum protein normally produced at very high levels by the fetus and present in low levels in the blood of adults and children. Research on AFP suggests that it may play a role in modulating the immune system of the mother in order to protect the developing fetus during pregnancy. The presence of hAFP in the pregnant mother’s blood has long been associated with remission of many autoimmune diseases, including rheumatoid arthritis, psoriasis and multiple sclerosis, during the third trimester of pregnancy. Current studies are assessing MM-093’s potential to improve the treatment of autoimmune disease.</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>One study states that AFP suppresses autologous lymphocyte proliferation and that improvements in experimental arthritis and autoimmune thyroiditis were associated with significantly reduced numbers of CD4 and CD8 splenocytes, total thymocytes and CD4 thymocytes. This suggests that AFP modulates T cell development and immune responses. </mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences>
    <sequence format="FASTA">&gt;&gt;Q4QR90|Q4QR90_RAT Alpha-fetoprotein - Rattus norvegicus (Rat).
MKQPATMKWSASISFLLLLNFAEPRVLHTNEFGIESTLDSSQCPTEKNMFNVATIVVAQF
VQDATKAEVNKMSSDALAAMKENTGDGCLENQLSVFLDEICHETELFNKYGFSGCCNQSG
VERHQCLLARKKTAPDSVPPFHFPETAESCPAYEENRAMSINTFIYDVSKRNPFLYAPTI
LYLAAQYDKAVPACCKADNMEECFQTKRASMAKELREGSMLNEHVCAVIRKFGSRNLQAV
LIIKLSQKFPKANITEIRKLALDVAHIHEQCCHGNAMECLQDGESVMTHICSQQEILSSK
TAECCKLPTIELGYCIIHAENGDKPEGLTLNPSEFLGDRNFAQFSSEEKLLFMASFLHEY
SRNHPNLPVSVILKTAKSYQEILEKCSQSETPSKCQDNMEEELQKHIQESQALAKQSCDL
YQKLGPYYLQNLFLIGYTRKAPQLTSAELIDLTGKMVSIASMCCQLSEEKRSACGEGLAD
IYIGHLCLRHEANPVNSGINHCCSSSYSNRRLCITSFLRDETYVPPPFSEDKFIFHKDLC
QAQGRALQTMKQELLINLVKQKPEMTEEQHAAVTADFSGLLEKCCKDQDQEACFAKEGPK
LISKTREALGV</sequence>
  </sequences>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910182</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>