<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2016-10-20" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB11661</drugbank-id>
  <name>Eptacog alfa pegol (activated)</name>
  <description>Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) has been used in trials studying the prevention and treatment of Haemophilia A, Haemophilia B, Congenital Bleeding Disorder, Haemophilia B With Inhibitors, and Haemophilia A With Inhibitors.</description>
  <cas-number>944130-77-2</cas-number>
  <unii>3Q26I70P3I</unii>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication/>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action/>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Activated Recombinant Human Factor VII, Long Acting</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Pegylated agents</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00008</drugbank-id>
      <name>Peginterferon alfa-2a</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Peginterferon alfa-2a.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00019</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pegfilgrastim</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Pegfilgrastim.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00022</drugbank-id>
      <name>Peginterferon alfa-2b</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Peginterferon alfa-2b.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00059</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pegaspargase</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Pegaspargase.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00061</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pegademase</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Pegademase.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00082</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pegvisomant</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Pegvisomant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01839</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propylene glycol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Propylene glycol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03394</drugbank-id>
      <name>Heptaethylene glycol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Heptaethylene glycol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04895</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pegaptanib</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Pegaptanib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05202</drugbank-id>
      <name>Egaptivon pegol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Egaptivon pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05321</drugbank-id>
      <name>PEG-uricase</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with PEG-uricase.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05860</drugbank-id>
      <name>Peginterferon alfacon-1</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Peginterferon alfacon-1.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06022</drugbank-id>
      <name>GlycoPEG-GCSF</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with GlycoPEG-GCSF.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06293</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pegnivacogin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Pegnivacogin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06325</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pegpleranib</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Pegpleranib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06611</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pegsunercept</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Pegsunercept.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06811</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polidocanol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Polidocanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08894</drugbank-id>
      <name>Peginesatide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Peginesatide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08904</drugbank-id>
      <name>Certolizumab pegol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Certolizumab pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09107</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methoxy polyethylene glycol-epoetin beta</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Methoxy polyethylene glycol-epoetin beta.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09122</drugbank-id>
      <name>Peginterferon beta-1a</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Peginterferon beta-1a.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pegloticase</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Pegloticase.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09287</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polyethylene glycol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Polyethylene glycol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09329</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antihemophilic Factor (Recombinant), PEGylated</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Antihemophilic Factor (Recombinant), PEGylated.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11077</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polyethylene glycol 400</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Polyethylene glycol 400.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11567</drugbank-id>
      <name>Insulin peglispro</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eptacog alfa pegol (activated) can be decreased when used in combination with Insulin peglispro.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11707</drugbank-id>
      <name>Olaptesed Pegol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Olaptesed Pegol can be decreased when used in combination with Eptacog alfa pegol (activated).</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12258</drugbank-id>
      <name>Abicipar Pegol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Abicipar Pegol can be decreased when used in combination with Eptacog alfa pegol (activated).</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12578</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lexaptepid Pegol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Lexaptepid Pegol can be decreased when used in combination with Eptacog alfa pegol (activated).</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12814</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cepeginterferon alfa-2B</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Cepeginterferon alfa-2B can be decreased when used in combination with Eptacog alfa pegol (activated).</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12839</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pegvaliase</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Pegvaliase can be decreased when used in combination with Eptacog alfa pegol (activated).</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12842</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pegamotecan</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Pegamotecan can be decreased when used in combination with Eptacog alfa pegol (activated).</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13200</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lipegfilgrastim</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Lipegfilgrastim can be decreased when used in combination with Eptacog alfa pegol (activated).</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13933</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nonacog beta pegol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Nonacog beta pegol can be decreased when used in combination with Eptacog alfa pegol (activated).</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14700</drugbank-id>
      <name>Damoctocog alfa pegol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Damoctocog alfa pegol can be decreased when used in combination with Eptacog alfa pegol (activated).</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14712</drugbank-id>
      <name>Elapegademase</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Elapegademase can be decreased when used in combination with Eptacog alfa pegol (activated).</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347911224</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>