<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-10-21" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB04943</drugbank-id>
  <name>LX201</name>
  <description>LX201 is a silicone matrix ocular implant that provides sustained release of cyclosporine A (CsA) locally to the eye over the course of one year. LX201 is implanted subconjunctivally (beneath the transparent membrane covering the white of the eye) in a minimally invasive procedure. The implant is being developed clinically for the prevention of rejection in corneal transplantation. It is being developed by Lux Biosciences, Inc.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in eye disorders/infections and transplant (rejection).</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>LX201 is a sustained release silicone implant containing 30% cyclosporine A (CsA) by weight. The LX201 implant releases the cyclosporine at steady doses over the course of a year. Local delivery of CsA through LX201 potentially offers significant benefits in the treatment of corneal transplantation due to: (i) increased safety resulting from the absence of systemic toxicity of CsA, in particular of renal toxicity as, based on animal studies, LX201 does not produce measurable systemic levels; (ii) increased efficacy as, based on animal studies, LX201 can establish continuous and relatively high therapeutic levels of CsA – higher than could be established by tolerable oral doses - at or near the transplanted cornea; and (iii) increased patient compliance as the implant is hardly perceptible by the patient and dosing cannot be missed throughout the first year after transplantation.</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>LX201 provides a delivery mechanism for cyclosporine. Cyclosporine binds to cyclophillin. The complex then inhibits calcineurin which is normally responsible for activating transcription of interleukin 2. Cyclosporine also inhibits lymphokine production and interleukin release.&#13;
</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347909854</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>