<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2007-10-21" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB04969</drugbank-id>
  <name>NV1020</name>
  <description>NV1020, a genetically engineered herpes simplex virus, is a novel anticancer therapeutic.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>liquid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3095</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17536976</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Israyelyan AH, Melancon JM, Lomax LG, Sehgal I, Leuschner C, Kearney MT, Chouljenko VN, Baghian A, Kousoulas KG: Effective treatment of human breast tumor in a mouse xenograft model with herpes simplex virus type 1 specifying the NV1020 genomic deletion and the gBsyn3 syncytial mutation enabling high viral replication and spread in breast cancer cells. Hum Gene Ther. 2007 May;18(5):457-73.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3096</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17117895</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Gutermann A, Mayer E, von Dehn-Rothfelser K, Breidenstein C, Weber M, Muench M, Gungor D, Suehnel J, Moebius U, Lechmann M: Efficacy of oncolytic herpesvirus NV1020 can be enhanced by combination with chemotherapeutics in colon carcinoma cells. Hum Gene Ther. 2006 Dec;17(12):1241-53.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3097</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17107303</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Kemeny N, Brown K, Covey A, Kim T, Bhargava A, Brody L, Guilfoyle B, Haag NP, Karrasch M, Glasschroeder B, Knoll A, Getrajdman G, Kowal KJ, Jarnagin WR, Fong Y: Phase I, open-label, dose-escalating study of a genetically engineered herpes simplex virus, NV1020, in subjects with metastatic colorectal carcinoma to the liver. Hum Gene Ther. 2006 Dec;17(12):1214-24.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3098</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>12386832</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Bennett JJ, Delman KA, Burt BM, Mariotti A, Malhotra S, Zager J, Petrowsky H, Mastorides S, Federoff H, Fong Y: Comparison of safety, delivery, and efficacy of two oncolytic herpes viruses (G207 and NV1020) for peritoneal cancer. Cancer Gene Ther. 2002 Nov;9(11):935-45.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3099</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>12091817</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Ebright MI, Zager JS, Malhotra S, Delman KA, Weigel TL, Rusch VW, Fong Y: Replication-competent herpes virus NV1020 as direct treatment of pleural cancer in a rat model. J Thorac Cardiovasc Surg. 2002 Jul;124(1):123-9.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3100</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>11344122</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Cozzi PJ, Malhotra S, McAuliffe P, Kooby DA, Federoff HJ, Huryk B, Johnson P, Scardino PT, Heston WD, Fong Y: Intravesical oncolytic viral therapy using attenuated, replication-competent herpes simplex viruses G207 and Nv1020 is effective in the treatment of bladder cancer in an orthotopic syngeneic model. FASEB J. 2001 May;15(7):1306-8.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Intended for the treatment of various forms of cancer.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>Cancer-killing viruses, so-called oncolytic viruses are specific herpes simplex viruses, or HSVs, generally known as the cause of cold sores. These viruses are used, however, in a modified and "disarmed" form in order to make them utilizable as a therapeutic agent in humans. This is achieved by switching off certain genes that normally enable the virus to multiply in healthy cells, which would destroy these cells. As a result of this genetic modification, the HSVs are able to reproduce in tumor cells solely, since only these offer an environment that compensates for the loss of the removed viral genes. Consequently, the virus is able to replicate in the tumor cells, selectively destroying them without harming healthy tissue.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347909865</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>