<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2007-10-21" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB04987</drugbank-id>
  <name>P113D</name>
  <description>P113D is a novel 12 amino-acid antimicrobial peptide drug derived from histatins, which are compounds found naturally in human saliva. It is being pursued as a potential treatment for cystic fibrosis by Demegen, Inc.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>For the potential treatment of cystic fibrosis and bacterial infections.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>P113D has demonstrated activity against CF patient clinical isolates of bacteria that are resistant to traditional antibiotics. The compound is stable and maintains activity in sputum of CF patients. P113 was determined to be the smallest histatin fragment which retained antimicrobial activity equivalent to that of the parent compound. Interestingly, synthesizing P113 with D-amino acids gave rise P113D, a compound that was impervious to enzymatic degradation and maintained the antimicrobial activity of the parent compound. P113D also has very potent in vitro activity against a variety of Gram negative and positive bacteria including &lt;i&gt;P. aeruginosa&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;S. aureus&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;H. influenzae&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;S. typhimurium&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;E. coli&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;S. epidermidis&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;S. mutans&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;S. sobrinus&lt;/i&gt;. In the case of &lt;i&gt;P. aeruginosa&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;S. aureus&lt;/i&gt;, antibacterial activity has been demonstrated against a variety of CF patient clinical isolates which are resistant to traditional antibiotics. &lt;i&gt;P. aeruginosa&lt;/i&gt; isolates that produce thick alginate secretions (mucoid phenotype) are also susceptible to killing by P113D.</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>For both bacteria and fungi such as &lt;i&gt;Candida albicans&lt;/i&gt;, P113D has been shown to kill cells as opposed to simply inhibiting their growth. It has been demonstrated that P113D acts by binding to the cell surface and increasing the permeability of both the outer and inner membranes of the cells of Gram negative bacteria, killing them within seconds. </mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347909876</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>