<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2017-06-23" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB13209</drugbank-id>
  <name>Bismuth subnitrate</name>
  <description>Bismuth subnitrate, also referred to as bismuth oxynitrate or bismuthyl nitrate, is a highly water-soluble crystalline compound that has been used as a treatment for duodenal ulcers and anti-diarrheic agent [A33012]. The use of bismuth substrate as an active ingredient in over-the-counter antacids is approved by the FDA.</description>
  <cas-number>1304-85-4</cas-number>
  <unii>H19J064BA5</unii>
  <average-mass>1461.98</average-mass>
  <monoisotopic-mass>1461.87284</monoisotopic-mass>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A33012</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>14530870</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Kondo Y, Himeno S, Satoh M, Naganuma A, Nishimura T, Imura N: Citrate enhances the protective effect of orally administered bismuth subnitrate against the nephrotoxicity of cis-diamminedichloroplatinum. Cancer Chemother Pharmacol. 2004 Jan;53(1):33-8. doi: 10.1007/s00280-003-0706-9. Epub 2003 Oct 7.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A33013</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>2129809</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Pugh S, Lewin MR: Mechanism of action of Roter (bismuth subnitrate) in patients with duodenal ulcer disease and healthy volunteers. J Gastroenterol Hepatol. 1990 Jul-Aug;5(4):382-6.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A33014</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>7733075</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Forne M, Viver JM, Espinos JC, Coll I, Tresserra F, Garau J: Impact of colloidal bismuth subnitrate in the eradication rates of Helicobacter pylori infection-associated duodenal ulcer using a short treatment regimen with omeprazole and clarithromycin: a randomized study. Am J Gastroenterol. 1995 May;90(5):718-21.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A33021</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>2682129</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Slikkerveer A, de Wolff FA: Pharmacokinetics and toxicity of bismuth compounds. Med Toxicol Adverse Drug Exp. 1989 Sep-Oct;4(5):303-23.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L2733</ref-id>
        <title>BISMUTH SUBNITRATE - National Library of Medicine HSDB Database - Toxnet</title>
        <url>https://toxnet.nlm.nih.gov/cgi-bin/sis/search/a?dbs+hsdb:@term+@DOCNO+1608</url>
      </link>
    </links>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Indicated for over-the-counter use as an antacid. </indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>Bismuth subnitrate acts as an antacid that exert protective effects on the gastric mucosa [A33012]. In a double-blind endoscopically controlled study, bismuth substrate was demonstrated to be effective for symptomatic relief in duodenal ulcers [A33013]. In the alcohol model of mucosal injury in the rat, bismuth substrate was shown to be cytoprotective [A33013]. In a randomized clinical study consisting of patients with _H. pylori_-associated duodenal ulcer, adjunctive use of colloidal bismuth subnitrate in a short treatment regimen with omeprazole and clarithromycin resulted in improved eradication rate of _H. pylori_ [A33014]. </pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>Based on the findings of a clinical investigation in patients with duodenal ulcer disease and healthy volunteers receiving oral bismuth subnitrate tablets, the protective effects of bismuth subnitrate may be secondary to endogenous mucosal prostaglandin (PGE2) production, which is one of the deficient factors observed in peptic ulcer disease [A33013]. Antacid neutralizing activity of bismuth subnitrate was demonstrated to have a significant postprandial effect on gastric pH [A33013]. </mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity>Reported oral dose range for moderate toxicity or possibly lethal toxicity in humans is 0.5-5 g/kg [L2733]. Nephropathy, encephalopathy, osteoarthropathy, gingivitis, stomatitis and colitis have been attributed to bismuth toxicity in humans [A33021]. </toxicity>
  <metabolism>No pharmacokinetic data available. </metabolism>
  <absorption>Bismuth subnitrate may undergo minimal gastrointestinal absorption which may be potentiated with concomitant administration of sulfhydryl compounds [L2733] when dissolved in citrate buffer solution [A33012]. Approximately 0.2% of orally administered bismuth is absorbed systematically from the gastrointestinal tract with the peak plasma concentration typically occurring within 1 hour [L2733]. </absorption>
  <half-life>The distribution half-life of bismuth is approximately 1 to 4 hours, and the elimination half-life is 5 to 11 days [L2733].</half-life>
  <protein-binding>Upon accumulation in the kidneys, bismuth may bind to a bismuth-metal binding protein in the kidney [A33021]. </protein-binding>
  <route-of-elimination>Bismuth may undergo both urinary and faecal excretion, however the exact proportion contributed by each route is still unknown [A33021]. </route-of-elimination>
  <volume-of-distribution>Bismuth has been shown to accumulate preferentially in the kidneys [A33012]. </volume-of-distribution>
  <clearance>No pharmacokinetic data available. </clearance>
  <classification>
    <description>This compound belongs to the class of inorganic compounds known as post-transition metal nitrates. These are inorganic compounds in which the largest oxoanion is nitrate, and in which the heaviest atom not in an oxoanion is a post-transition metal.</description>
    <direct-parent>Post-transition metal nitrates</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Inorganic compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Mixed metal/non-metal compounds</superclass>
    <class>Post-transition metal oxoanionic compounds</class>
    <subclass>Post-transition metal nitrates</subclass>
    <alternative-parent>Inorganic hydrides</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Inorganic oxides</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Inorganic salts</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Post-transition metal salts</alternative-parent>
    <substituent>Inorganic hydride</substituent>
    <substituent>Inorganic oxide</substituent>
    <substituent>Inorganic post-transition metal salt</substituent>
    <substituent>Inorganic salt</substituent>
    <substituent>Post-transition metal nitrate</substituent>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Bismuth hydroxide nitrate oxide</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Bismuth nitrate, basic</synonym>
    <synonym language="latin" coder="">Bismuthum subnitricum</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>Hemorro-dol Sup</name>
      <labeller>Produits Francais Labs Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>00540919</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1981-12-31</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>1997-05-30</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Suppository</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Rectal</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>true</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>Hemorro-dol Sup</name>
      <ingredients>Balsam of Peru + Belladonna + Benzocaine + Bismuth subcarbonate + Bismuth subnitrate + Boric acid + Ephedrine + Zinc oxide</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Alimentary Tract and Metabolism</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Antacids</category>
      <mesh-id>D000863</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Bismuth containing drugs</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Drugs for Acid Related Disorders</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Drugs for Peptic Ulcer and Gastro-Oesophageal Reflux Disease (Gord)</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Elements</category>
      <mesh-id>D004602</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Elements, Radioactive</category>
      <mesh-id>D004603</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Gastric Acid Lowering Agents</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Gastrointestinal Agents</category>
      <mesh-id>D005765</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Isotopes</category>
      <mesh-id>D007554</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Metals</category>
      <mesh-id>D008670</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Metals, Heavy</category>
      <mesh-id>D019216</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Neurotoxic agents</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Radioisotopes</category>
      <mesh-id>D011868</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Suppository</form>
      <route>Rectal</route>
      <strength/>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes>
    <atc-code code="A02BX12">
      <level code="A02BX">Other drugs for peptic ulcer and gastro-oesophageal reflux disease (GORD)</level>
      <level code="A02B">DRUGS FOR PEPTIC ULCER AND GASTRO-OESOPHAGEAL REFLUX DISEASE (GORD)</level>
      <level code="A02">DRUGS FOR ACID RELATED DISORDERS</level>
      <level code="A">ALIMENTARY TRACT AND METABOLISM</level>
    </atc-code>
  </atc-codes>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06616</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bosutinib</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Bosutinib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01066</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefditoren</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Cefditoren can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06695</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dabigatran etexilate</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dabigatran etexilate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08912</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dabrafenib</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dabrafenib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01254</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dasatinib</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dasatinib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00530</drugbank-id>
      <name>Erlotinib</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Erlotinib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01167</drugbank-id>
      <name>Itraconazole</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Itraconazole resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09027</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ledipasvir</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ledipasvir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00422</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylphenidate</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause an increase in the absorption of Methylphenidate resulting in an increased serum concentration and potentially a worsening of adverse effects.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04868</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nilotinib</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Nilotinib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06589</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pazopanib</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pazopanib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08931</drugbank-id>
      <name>Riociguat</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Riociguat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00451</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levothyroxine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Levothyroxine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01344</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolevamer</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tolevamer is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09020</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bisacodyl</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Bisacodyl can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00178</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ramipril</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ramipril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00492</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosinopril</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Fosinopril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00519</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trandolapril</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Trandolapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00542</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benazepril</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Benazepril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00584</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enalapril</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Enalapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00691</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moexipril</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Moexipril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00722</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lisinopril</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Lisinopril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00790</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perindopril</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Perindopril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00881</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinapril</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Quinapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00886</drugbank-id>
      <name>Omapatrilat</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Omapatrilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01180</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rescinnamine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rescinnamine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01197</drugbank-id>
      <name>Captopril</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Captopril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01340</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cilazapril</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Cilazapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01348</drugbank-id>
      <name>Spirapril</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Spirapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08836</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temocapril</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Temocapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imidapril</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Imidapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13166</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zofenopril</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Zofenopril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13312</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delapril</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Delapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14125</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benazeprilat</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Benazeprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14207</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosinoprilat</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Fosinoprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ramiprilat</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ramiprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14209</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trandolaprilat</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Trandolaprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14210</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moexiprilat</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Moexiprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perindoprilat</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Perindoprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14217</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinaprilat</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Quinaprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14231</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinoline Yellow WS</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Quinoline Yellow WS resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01416</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefpodoxime</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Cefpodoxime can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00908</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinidine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may decrease the excretion rate of Quinidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00437</drugbank-id>
      <name>Allopurinol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Allopurinol can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Raltegravir</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Raltegravir can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00688</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mycophenolate mofetil</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Mycophenolate mofetil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01024</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mycophenolic acid</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Mycophenolic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00847</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cysteamine</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Cysteamine can be decreased when combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01026</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketoconazole</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ketoconazole resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01294</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bismuth subsalicylate</name>
      <description>Bismuth subsalicylate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09275</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bismuth subcitrate potassium</name>
      <description>Bismuth subcitrate potassium may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13909</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bismuth subgallate</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subgallate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13910</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valproate bismuth</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Valproate bismuth.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00372</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiethylperazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Thiethylperazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00420</drugbank-id>
      <name>Promazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Promazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00433</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prochlorperazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Prochlorperazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00477</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorpromazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Chlorpromazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00508</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triflupromazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Triflupromazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00623</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluphenazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Fluphenazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00679</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thioridazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Thioridazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00680</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moricizine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Moricizine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00831</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trifluoperazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Trifluoperazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00850</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perphenazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Perphenazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00933</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mesoridazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Mesoridazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01063</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetophenazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Acetophenazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01069</drugbank-id>
      <name>Promethazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Promethazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01246</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alimemazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Alimemazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01403</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methotrimeprazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Methotrimeprazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01608</drugbank-id>
      <name>Periciazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Periciazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01614</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acepromazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Acepromazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aceprometazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Aceprometazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01621</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pipotiazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pipotiazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01622</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thioproperazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Thioproperazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05687</drugbank-id>
      <name>BL-1020</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of BL-1020 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09000</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyamemazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Cyamemazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09241</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylene blue</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Methylene blue resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11540</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propiopromazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Propiopromazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12710</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Perazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Butaperazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Butaperazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13382</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorproethazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Chlorproethazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13420</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiazinam</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Thiazinam resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13784</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dixyrazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dixyrazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14651</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perphenazine enanthate</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Perphenazine enanthate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06799</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methenamine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Methenamine can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00254</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxycycline</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Doxycycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00256</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lymecycline</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Lymecycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00453</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clomocycline</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Clomocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxytetracycline</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Oxytetracycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00618</drugbank-id>
      <name>Demeclocycline</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Demeclocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00759</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetracycline</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Tetracycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00931</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metacycline</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Metacycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01017</drugbank-id>
      <name>Minocycline</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Minocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12035</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sarecycline</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sarecycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12455</drugbank-id>
      <name>Omadacycline</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Omadacycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13092</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meclocycline</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Meclocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penimepicycline</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Penimepicycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06824</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triethylenetetramine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Triethylenetetramine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01098</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rosuvastatin</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rosuvastatin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00282</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pamidronic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Pamidronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00399</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zoledronic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Zoledronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00630</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alendronic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Alendronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00710</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibandronate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ibandronate can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00720</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clodronic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Clodronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00884</drugbank-id>
      <name>Risedronic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Risedronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01077</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etidronic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Etidronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01133</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiludronic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tiludronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06255</drugbank-id>
      <name>Incadronic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00182</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amphetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amphetamine can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00191</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phentermine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Phentermine can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00852</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pseudoephedrine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Pseudoephedrine can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00865</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benzphetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Benzphetamine can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00937</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diethylpropion</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Diethylpropion can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01255</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lisdexamfetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Lisdexamfetamine can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01365</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mephentermine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Mephentermine can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01442</drugbank-id>
      <name>MMDA</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of MMDA can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01454</drugbank-id>
      <name>Midomafetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Midomafetamine can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01467</drugbank-id>
      <name>2,5-Dimethoxy-4-ethylamphetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of 2,5-Dimethoxy-4-ethylamphetamine can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01484</drugbank-id>
      <name>4-Bromo-2,5-dimethoxyamphetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of 4-Bromo-2,5-dimethoxyamphetamine can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01509</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenamfetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tenamfetamine can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01556</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorphentermine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Chlorphentermine can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01566</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylenedioxyethamphetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Methylenedioxyethamphetamine can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01576</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dextroamphetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Dextroamphetamine can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01577</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metamfetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Metamfetamine can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09480</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iofetamine I-123</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Iofetamine I-123 can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12080</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ritobegron</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ritobegron can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13108</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mephedrone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Mephedrone can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13624</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methoxyphenamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Methoxyphenamine can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13703</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gepefrine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Gepefrine can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13940</drugbank-id>
      <name>2,5-Dimethoxy-4-ethylthioamphetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of 2,5-Dimethoxy-4-ethylthioamphetamine can be increased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00316</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetaminophen</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Acetaminophen resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09288</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propacetamol</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Propacetamol resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00653</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium sulfate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium sulfate can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01377</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium oxide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium oxide can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01378</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium cation</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium cation can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01638</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sorbitol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sorbitol can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09104</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium hydroxide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium hydroxide can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09281</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium trisilicate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium trisilicate can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09287</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polyethylene glycol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Polyethylene glycol can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09413</drugbank-id>
      <name>Monopotassium phosphate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Monopotassium phosphate can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09414</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dipotassium phosphate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Dipotassium phosphate can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09449</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium phosphate, monobasic</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sodium phosphate, monobasic can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09462</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glycerin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Glycerin can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09472</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium sulfate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sodium sulfate can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09481</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium carbonate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium carbonate can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09484</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium fluorophosphate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sodium fluorophosphate can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11110</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium citrate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium citrate can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11189</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium glycinate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium glycinate can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12942</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lactitol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Lactitol can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13486</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium peroxide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium peroxide can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13526</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentaerithrityl</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Pentaerithrityl can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13707</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium tartrate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sodium tartrate can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14482</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium ascorbate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sodium ascorbate can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14499</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium sulfate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Potassium sulfate can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14502</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium phosphate, dibasic</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sodium phosphate, dibasic can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14503</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium phosphate, monobasic, unspecified form</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sodium phosphate, monobasic, unspecified form can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14504</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium phosphate, dibasic, unspecified form</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sodium phosphate, dibasic, unspecified form can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14513</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00537</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ciprofloxacin</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ciprofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00220</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nelfinavir</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Nelfinavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00224</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indinavir</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Indinavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00503</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ritonavir</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ritonavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00701</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amprenavir</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Amprenavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00932</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tipranavir</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Tipranavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01232</drugbank-id>
      <name>Saquinavir</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Saquinavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Darunavir</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Darunavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01319</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosamprenavir</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Fosamprenavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01601</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lopinavir</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Lopinavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11586</drugbank-id>
      <name>Asunaprevir</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Asunaprevir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08864</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rilpivirine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rilpivirine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00581</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lactulose</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Lactulose can be decreased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09073</drugbank-id>
      <name>Palbociclib</name>
      <description>The absorption of Palbociclib can be decreased when combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06701</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexmethylphenidate</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dexmethylphenidate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12147</drugbank-id>
      <name>Erdafitinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Bismuth subnitrate is combined with Erdafitinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00390</drugbank-id>
      <name>Digoxin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Digoxin can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13401</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metildigoxin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Metildigoxin can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13691</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetyldigoxin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Acetyldigoxin can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00788</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naproxen</name>
      <description>Naproxen can cause a decrease in the absorption of Bismuth subnitrate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01611</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydroxychloroquine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Hydroxychloroquine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01112</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefuroxime</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Cefuroxime can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00608</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chloroquine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Chloroquine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09101</drugbank-id>
      <name>Elvitegravir</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Elvitegravir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00996</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gabapentin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Gabapentin can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08872</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gabapentin enacarbil</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Gabapentin enacarbil can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00424</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hyoscyamine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Hyoscyamine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01045</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rifampicin</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rifampicin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00657</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mecamylamine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may decrease the excretion rate of Mecamylamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01043</drugbank-id>
      <name>Memantine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may decrease the excretion rate of Memantine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00391</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulpiride</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sulpiride can be increased when used in combination with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00244</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mesalazine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Mesalazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00091</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclosporine</name>
      <description>Cyclosporine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00202</drugbank-id>
      <name>Succinylcholine</name>
      <description>Succinylcholine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00206</drugbank-id>
      <name>Reserpine</name>
      <description>Reserpine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00246</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ziprasidone</name>
      <description>Ziprasidone may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00260</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cycloserine</name>
      <description>Cycloserine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00321</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amitriptyline</name>
      <description>Amitriptyline may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00344</drugbank-id>
      <name>Protriptyline</name>
      <description>Protriptyline may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00361</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vinorelbine</name>
      <description>Vinorelbine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00363</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clozapine</name>
      <description>Clozapine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00408</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loxapine</name>
      <description>Loxapine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00409</drugbank-id>
      <name>Remoxipride</name>
      <description>Remoxipride may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00444</drugbank-id>
      <name>Teniposide</name>
      <description>Teniposide may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00450</drugbank-id>
      <name>Droperidol</name>
      <description>Droperidol may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00458</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imipramine</name>
      <description>Imipramine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00502</drugbank-id>
      <name>Haloperidol</name>
      <description>Haloperidol may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00531</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclophosphamide</name>
      <description>Cyclophosphamide may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00540</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nortriptyline</name>
      <description>Nortriptyline may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00541</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vincristine</name>
      <description>Vincristine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00543</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amoxapine</name>
      <description>Amoxapine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00649</drugbank-id>
      <name>Stavudine</name>
      <description>Stavudine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00726</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimipramine</name>
      <description>Trimipramine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00734</drugbank-id>
      <name>Risperidone</name>
      <description>Risperidone may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00875</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flupentixol</name>
      <description>Flupentixol may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00898</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethanol</name>
      <description>Ethanol may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00900</drugbank-id>
      <name>Didanosine</name>
      <description>Didanosine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00924</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclobenzaprine</name>
      <description>Cyclobenzaprine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01100</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pimozide</name>
      <description>Pimozide may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01142</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxepin</name>
      <description>Doxepin may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01151</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desipramine</name>
      <description>Desipramine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01190</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clindamycin</name>
      <description>Clindamycin may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01199</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tubocurarine</name>
      <description>Tubocurarine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01229</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paclitaxel</name>
      <description>Paclitaxel may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01238</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aripiprazole</name>
      <description>Aripiprazole may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01239</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorprothixene</name>
      <description>Chlorprothixene may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01242</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clomipramine</name>
      <description>Clomipramine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01245</drugbank-id>
      <name>Decamethonium</name>
      <description>Decamethonium may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01267</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paliperidone</name>
      <description>Paliperidone may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01356</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium cation</name>
      <description>Lithium cation may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01598</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imipenem</name>
      <description>Imipenem may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01618</drugbank-id>
      <name>Molindone</name>
      <description>Molindone may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01623</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiothixene</name>
      <description>Thiothixene may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01624</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zuclopenthixol</name>
      <description>Zuclopenthixol may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01627</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lincomycin</name>
      <description>Lincomycin may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04836</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amineptine</name>
      <description>Amineptine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04842</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluspirilene</name>
      <description>Fluspirilene may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04872</drugbank-id>
      <name>Osanetant</name>
      <description>Osanetant may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04888</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bifeprunox</name>
      <description>Bifeprunox may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04946</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iloperidone</name>
      <description>Iloperidone may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05316</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pimavanserin</name>
      <description>Pimavanserin may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06016</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cariprazine</name>
      <description>Cariprazine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06144</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sertindole</name>
      <description>Sertindole may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06216</drugbank-id>
      <name>Asenapine</name>
      <description>Asenapine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06288</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amisulpride</name>
      <description>Amisulpride may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08815</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lurasidone</name>
      <description>Lurasidone may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08922</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perospirone</name>
      <description>Perospirone may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08927</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amperozide</name>
      <description>Amperozide may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08996</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dimetacrine</name>
      <description>Dimetacrine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09016</drugbank-id>
      <name>Butriptyline</name>
      <description>Butriptyline may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09128</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brexpiprazole</name>
      <description>Brexpiprazole may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09154</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium citrate</name>
      <description>Sodium citrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09167</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dosulepin</name>
      <description>Dosulepin may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09223</drugbank-id>
      <name>Blonanserin</name>
      <description>Blonanserin may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09224</drugbank-id>
      <name>Melperone</name>
      <description>Melperone may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09225</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zotepine</name>
      <description>Zotepine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09226</drugbank-id>
      <name>RP-5063</name>
      <description>RP-5063 may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09286</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pipamperone</name>
      <description>Pipamperone may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09289</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tianeptine</name>
      <description>Tianeptine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09307</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxaprotiline</name>
      <description>Oxaprotiline may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11376</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azaperone</name>
      <description>Azaperone may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11537</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pirlimycin</name>
      <description>Pirlimycin may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12093</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetrahydropalmatine</name>
      <description>Tetrahydropalmatine may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12273</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ecopipam</name>
      <description>Ecopipam may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12401</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bromperidol</name>
      <description>Bromperidol may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12518</drugbank-id>
      <name>Raclopride</name>
      <description>Raclopride may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12693</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ritanserin</name>
      <description>Ritanserin may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12867</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benperidol</name>
      <description>Benperidol may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12930</drugbank-id>
      <name>Opipramol</name>
      <description>Opipramol may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12958</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prothipendyl</name>
      <description>Prothipendyl may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13025</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiapride</name>
      <description>Tiapride may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13114</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amitriptylinoxide</name>
      <description>Amitriptylinoxide may increase the neurotoxic activities of Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13225</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dibenzepin</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Dibenzepin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13246</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinupramine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Quinupramine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13256</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clothiapine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Clothiapine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13273</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sultopride</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Sultopride.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13384</drugbank-id>
      <name>Melitracen</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Melitracen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13403</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxypertine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Oxypertine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13411</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lofepramine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Lofepramine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13496</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iprindole</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Iprindole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13523</drugbank-id>
      <name>Veralipride</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Veralipride.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13552</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trifluperidol</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Trifluperidol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13554</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moperone</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Moperone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13557</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiopropazate</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Thiopropazate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13584</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gallamine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Gallamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13598</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diethyl ether</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Diethyl ether.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13665</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluanisone</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Fluanisone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13676</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mosapramine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Mosapramine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13782</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imipramine oxide</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Imipramine oxide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13791</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penfluridol</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Penfluridol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13841</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clopenthixol</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Clopenthixol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14185</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aripiprazole lauroxil</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Aripiprazole lauroxil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00781</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polymyxin B</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate may increase the neurotoxic activities of Polymyxin B.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00705</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delavirdine</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Delavirdine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gefitinib</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Gefitinib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01072</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atazanavir</name>
      <description>Bismuth subnitrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Atazanavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <calculated-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>0.84</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>pentabismuth(3+) ion nonahydroxide tetranitrate oxidandiide</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Traditional IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>pentabismuth(3+) ion nonahydroxide tetranitrate oxidandiide</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Weight</kind>
      <value>1461.98</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Monoisotopic Weight</kind>
      <value>1461.87284</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>SMILES</kind>
      <value>[OH-].[OH-].[OH-].[OH-].[OH-].[OH-].[OH-].[OH-].[OH-].[O--].[Bi+3].[Bi+3].[Bi+3].[Bi+3].[Bi+3].[O-][N+]([O-])=O.[O-][N+]([O-])=O.[O-][N+]([O-])=O.[O-][N+]([O-])=O</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Formula</kind>
      <value>Bi5H9N4O22</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChI</kind>
      <value>InChI=1S/5Bi.4NO3.9H2O.O/c;;;;;4*2-1(3)4;;;;;;;;;;/h;;;;;;;;;9*1H2;/q5*+3;4*-1;;;;;;;;;;-2/p-9</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChIKey</kind>
      <value>QGWDKKHSDXWPET-UHFFFAOYSA-E</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polar Surface Area (PSA)</kind>
      <value>66.2</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Refractivity</kind>
      <value>8.35</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polarizability</kind>
      <value>3.28</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rotatable Bond Count</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Acceptor Count</kind>
      <value>3</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Donor Count</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest basic)</kind>
      <value>-9.9</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Physiological Charge</kind>
      <value>-1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Number of Rings</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Bioavailability</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rule of Five</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Ghose Filter</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>MDDR-Like Rule</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
  </calculated-properties>
  <experimental-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>Water Solubility</kind>
      <value>Insoluble</value>
      <source>MSDS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Melting Point</kind>
      <value>Decomposes at 260</value>
      <source>MSDS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Boiling Point</kind>
      <value>Decomposes at 260</value>
      <source>MSDS</source>
    </property>
  </experimental-properties>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEBI</resource>
      <identifier>31293</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>KEGG Compound</resource>
      <identifier>C13102</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>KEGG Drug</resource>
      <identifier>D01642</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChemSpider</resource>
      <identifier>32699716</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Wikipedia</resource>
      <identifier>Bismuth_oxynitrate</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>