<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2007-11-18" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05306</drugbank-id>
  <name>Alferminogene tadenovec</name>
  <description>Alferminogene tadenovec, Cardium’s lead product candidate, is being developed for the potential treatment of myocardial ischemia that gives rise to angina symptoms associated with coronary heart disease. Alferminogene tadenovec represents a new therapeutic class of biologics designed to promote angiogenesis and thereby improve blood flow following a one-time intracoronary administration from a standard cardiac infusion catheter.</description>
  <cas-number>473553-86-5</cas-number>
  <unii/>
  <state>liquid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3356</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>14563572</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Grines CL, Watkins MW, Mahmarian JJ, Iskandrian AE, Rade JJ, Marrott P, Pratt C, Kleiman N: A randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled trial of Ad5FGF-4 gene therapy and its effect on myocardial perfusion in patients with stable angina. J Am Coll Cardiol. 2003 Oct 15;42(8):1339-47.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3357</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17825712</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Henry TD, Grines CL, Watkins MW, Dib N, Barbeau G, Moreadith R, Andrasfay T, Engler RL: Effects of Ad5FGF-4 in patients with angina: an analysis of pooled data from the AGENT-3 and AGENT-4 trials. J Am Coll Cardiol. 2007 Sep 11;50(11):1038-46. Epub 2007 Aug 24.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3358</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>14615023</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Grines C, Rubanyi GM, Kleiman NS, Marrott P, Watkins MW: Angiogenic gene therapy with adenovirus 5 fibroblast growth factor-4 (Ad5FGF-4): a new option for the treatment of coronary artery disease. Am J Cardiol. 2003 Nov 7;92(9B):24N-31N.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in angina, coronary artery disease, and heart disease.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>Alferminogene tadenovec holds the potential to promote a disease-modifying improvement by leveraging the body’s natural healing processes in response to myocardia ischemia (insufficient blood flow and myocardial oxygen supply).  Angiogenesis, the growth of new collateral blood vessels, is a natural biologic response to repeated myocardial ischemia.  These newly formed vessels provide alternate routes of blood flow and oxygen delivery to parts of the patient’s heart downstream from a blockage in a coronary artery. In many patients however, including those with recurrent angina, coronary collateral vessel formation is insufficient to meet the heart’s needs during stress. Currently available anti-anginal drugs, which may provide symptomatic relief, are generally designed to alter the oxygen demand of the heart muscle or dilate vessels to temporarily relieve angina. Alferminogene tadenovec is designed to promote the heart’s natural response of collateral growth and to increase blood flow in the microcirculation.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Ad5FGF-4</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="inn/usan">Alferminogene tadenovec</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products/>
  <international-brands>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Generx</name>
      <company/>
    </international-brand>
  </international-brands>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Antianginal Agents</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Vasodilating Agents</category>
      <mesh-id>D014665</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13967</drugbank-id>
      <name>Patent Blue</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Alferminogene tadenovec can be decreased when used in combination with Patent Blue.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910068</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>