<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2015-09-22" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB09113</drugbank-id>
  <name>Poractant alfa</name>
  <description>Poractant alfa is a pulmonary surfactant marketed as Curosurf in the United States and Canada. It is used to treat Respiratory Distress Syndrome (RDS) in premature infants with an endogenous pulmonary surfactant deficiency. Poractant alfa is an extract of natural porcine lung surfactant consisting of 99% polar lipids (mainly phospholipids) and 1% hydrophobic low molecular weight proteins (surfactant associated proteins SP-B and SP-C). The phospholipid content of the extract consists primarily of phosphatidylcholine and dipaImitoylphosphatidylcholine. Poractant alfa is a creamy white suspension of this extract in 0.9% sodium chloride solution. It contains no preservatives.</description>
  <cas-number>129069-19-8</cas-number>
  <unii>KE3U2023NP</unii>
  <state>liquid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A7757</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>19956811</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Fujii AM, Carillo M: Animal-derived surfactant treatment of respiratory distress syndrome in premature neonates: a review. Drugs Today (Barc). 2009 Sep;45(9):697-709. doi: 1396674/dot.2009.45.9.1418185.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A7758</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25683992</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Jeon GW, Oh M, Sin JB: Efficacy of surfactant-TA, calfactant and poractant alfa for preterm infants with respiratory distress syndrome: a retrospective study. Yonsei Med J. 2015 Mar;56(2):433-9. doi: 10.3349/ymj.2015.56.2.433.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A7759</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>9727777</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Alberti A, Pettenazzo A, Enzi GB, Palamidese A, Mapp C, Ventura P, Baritussio A: Uptake and degradation of Curosurf after tracheal administration to newborn and adult rabbits. Eur Respir J. 1998 Aug;12(2):294-300.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A7760</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>9150335</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Bourbon JR, Chailley-Heu B, Gautier B: The exogenous surfactant Curosurf enhances phosphatidylcholine content in isolated type II cells. Eur Respir J. 1997 Apr;10(4):914-9.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A7761</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25583659</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Calkovska A, Uhliarova B, Joskova M, Franova S, Kolomaznik M, Calkovsky V, Smolarova S: Pulmonary surfactant in the airway physiology: a direct relaxing effect on the smooth muscle. Respir Physiol Neurobiol. 2015 Apr;209:95-105. doi: 10.1016/j.resp.2015.01.004. Epub 2015 Jan 10.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A7762</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>19822594</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Cogo PE, Facco M, Simonato M, Verlato G, Rondina C, Baritussio A, Toffolo GM, Carnielli VP: Dosing of porcine surfactant: effect on kinetics and gas exchange in respiratory distress syndrome. Pediatrics. 2009 Nov;124(5):e950-7. doi: 10.1542/peds.2009-0126. Epub 2009 Oct 12.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A7763</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>26690260</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Singh N, Halliday HL, Stevens TP, Suresh G, Soll R, Rojas-Reyes MX: Comparison of animal-derived surfactants for the prevention and treatment of respiratory distress syndrome in preterm infants. Cochrane Database Syst Rev. 2015 Dec 21;12:CD010249. doi: 10.1002/14651858.CD010249.pub2.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A7764</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>7527760</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Wiseman LR, Bryson HM: Porcine-derived lung surfactant. A review of the therapeutic efficacy and clinical tolerability of a natural surfactant preparation (Curosurf) in neonatal respiratory distress syndrome. Drugs. 1994 Sep;48(3):386-403.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A7765</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17480144</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Sweet D, Bevilacqua G, Carnielli V, Greisen G, Plavka R, Saugstad OD, Simeoni U, Speer CP, Valls-I-Soler A, Halliday H: European consensus guidelines on the management of neonatal respiratory distress syndrome. J Perinat Med. 2007;35(3):175-86.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A7766</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>8002555</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Schurch S, Schurch D, Curstedt T, Robertson B: Surface activity of lipid extract surfactant in relation to film area compression and collapse. J Appl Physiol (1985). 1994 Aug;77(2):974-86.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A7767</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>16188788</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Malloy CA, Nicoski P, Muraskas JK: A randomized trial comparing beractant and poractant treatment in neonatal respiratory distress syndrome. Acta Paediatr. 2005 Jun;94(6):779-84.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A7768</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>15085492</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Ramanathan R, Rasmussen MR, Gerstmann DR, Finer N, Sekar K: A randomized, multicenter masked comparison trial of poractant alfa (Curosurf) versus beractant (Survanta) in the treatment of respiratory distress syndrome in preterm infants. Am J Perinatol. 2004 Apr;21(3):109-19.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A7769</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>1727997</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Speer CP, Robertson B, Curstedt T, Halliday HL, Compagnone D, Gefeller O, Harms K, Herting E, McClure G, Reid M, et al.: Randomized European multicenter trial of surfactant replacement therapy for severe neonatal respiratory distress syndrome: single versus multiple doses of Curosurf. Pediatrics. 1992 Jan;89(1):13-20.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference>Curosurf: Product Monograph. Parma, Italy: Chiesi Farmaceutici S.p.A.; 2008: 25-27.</synthesis-reference>
  <indication>Poractant alfa is indicated for the treatment of Respiratory Distress Syndrome (RDS) in premature infants.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>Poractant alfa improved lung compliance, pulmonary gas exchange and survival in preterm rabbits.</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>Endogenous pulmonary surfactant reduces surface tension at the air-liquid interface of the alveoli in the lungs, thus stabilizing them against collapse under transpulmonary pressures. A deficiency of pulmonary surfactant in premature infants allows surface tension to increase to the point where sections of lung collapse and respiratory distress syndrome (RDS) develops. Poractant alfa lowers minimum surface tension to less than or equal to 4 mN/m. This compensates for the lack of endogenous surfactant and restores adequate surface activity to the lungs.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity>Studies on the carcinogenicity or reproductive effects of poractant alfa have not been conducted. Mutagenicity assays were negative.&#13;
In the case of an overdose with poractant alfa where there are clear clinical effects on the infant's respiration, ventilation, or oxygenation, it is recommended that as much of the solution be aspirated as possible and the infant be managed with supportive measures. Fluid and electrolyte balances should be monitored closely in this case. </toxicity>
  <metabolism>No studies on the metabolism of poractant alfa have been performed in humans. One small study in rabbits did find that poractant alfa may be degraded by macrophages and that it may, in part, be recycled in the alveoli in a similar manner to endogenous lung surfactant.</metabolism>
  <absorption>Poractant alfa is administered directly to the site of action in the lungs via endotracheal tube. It very rapidly adsorbs to the air-liquid interface to form a stable surfactant monolayer. No studies on absorption of poractant alfa have been performed in humans.</absorption>
  <half-life>The half-life of poractant alfa has only been evaluated in animal studies. When studied in adult and newborn rabbits, the half-life in the lungs was found to be 25 and 67 respectively. </half-life>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination>No studies on elimination of poractant alfa have been performed in humans.</route-of-elimination>
  <volume-of-distribution>No studies on the distribution of poractant alfa have been performed in humans.</volume-of-distribution>
  <clearance>No studies on clearance of poractant alfa have been performed in humans.</clearance>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>Curosurf</name>
      <labeller>Dey</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>49502-180</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2006-04-07</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2006-04-07</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Suspension</dosage-form>
      <strength>80 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Endotracheal</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Curosurf</name>
      <labeller>Chiesi USA, Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>10122-510</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1999-11-18</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Suspension</dosage-form>
      <strength>80 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Endotracheal</route>
      <fda-application-number>NDA020744</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Curosurf</name>
      <labeller>Chiesi Farmaceutici S.P.A.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>02241551</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2016-12-19</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Suspension</dosage-form>
      <strength>80 mg</strength>
      <route>Endotracheal</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>Curosurf</name>
      <ingredients>Poractant alfa</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Curosurf</name>
      <ingredients>Poractant alfa</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Curosurf</name>
      <ingredients>Poractant alfa</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Alveolar Surface Tension Reduction</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Bradycardia-Causing Agents</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Complex Mixtures</category>
      <mesh-id>D045424</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Lipids</category>
      <mesh-id>D008055</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Membrane Lipids</category>
      <mesh-id>D008563</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Pulmonary Surfactants</category>
      <mesh-id>D011663</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Respiratory System Agents</category>
      <mesh-id>D019141</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Surface-Active Agents</category>
      <mesh-id>D013501</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Surfactant Activity</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Suspension</form>
      <route>Endotracheal</route>
      <strength>80 mg/1mL</strength>
    </dosage>
    <dosage>
      <form>Suspension</form>
      <route>Endotracheal</route>
      <strength>80 mg</strength>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes>
    <ahfs-code>48:36.00</ahfs-code>
  </ahfs-codes>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <fda-label>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/fda_labels/DB09113.pdf?1456694339</fda-label>
  <msds>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/msds/DB09113.pdf?1456694546</msds>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09063</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceritinib</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Ceritinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09083</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ivabradine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Ivabradine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08877</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ruxolitinib</name>
      <description>Ruxolitinib may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00104</drugbank-id>
      <name>Octreotide</name>
      <description>Octreotide may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00187</drugbank-id>
      <name>Esmolol</name>
      <description>Esmolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00195</drugbank-id>
      <name>Betaxolol</name>
      <description>Betaxolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00211</drugbank-id>
      <name>Midodrine</name>
      <description>Midodrine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00230</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pregabalin</name>
      <description>Pregabalin may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metoprolol</name>
      <description>Metoprolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00270</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isradipine</name>
      <description>Isradipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00335</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atenolol</name>
      <description>Atenolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00343</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diltiazem</name>
      <description>Diltiazem may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00347</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimethadione</name>
      <description>Trimethadione may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00373</drugbank-id>
      <name>Timolol</name>
      <description>Timolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00381</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amlodipine</name>
      <description>Amlodipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00390</drugbank-id>
      <name>Digoxin</name>
      <description>Digoxin may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00393</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nimodipine</name>
      <description>Nimodipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00401</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nisoldipine</name>
      <description>Nisoldipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00436</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bendroflumethiazide</name>
      <description>Bendroflumethiazide may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00489</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sotalol</name>
      <description>Sotalol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00528</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lercanidipine</name>
      <description>Lercanidipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00555</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lamotrigine</name>
      <description>Lamotrigine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00568</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cinnarizine</name>
      <description>Cinnarizine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00571</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propranolol</name>
      <description>Propranolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00575</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clonidine</name>
      <description>Clonidine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00593</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethosuximide</name>
      <description>Ethosuximide may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00598</drugbank-id>
      <name>Labetalol</name>
      <description>Labetalol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00612</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bisoprolol</name>
      <description>Bisoprolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00622</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nicardipine</name>
      <description>Nicardipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00633</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexmedetomidine</name>
      <description>Dexmedetomidine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00653</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium sulfate</name>
      <description>Magnesium sulfate may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00661</drugbank-id>
      <name>Verapamil</name>
      <description>Verapamil may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00674</drugbank-id>
      <name>Galantamine</name>
      <description>Galantamine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00697</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tizanidine</name>
      <description>Tizanidine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00708</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sufentanil</name>
      <description>Sufentanil may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00802</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alfentanil</name>
      <description>Alfentanil may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00813</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fentanyl</name>
      <description>Fentanyl may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00825</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levomenthol</name>
      <description>Levomenthol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00836</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loperamide</name>
      <description>Loperamide may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00843</drugbank-id>
      <name>Donepezil</name>
      <description>Donepezil may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00866</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alprenolol</name>
      <description>Alprenolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00899</drugbank-id>
      <name>Remifentanil</name>
      <description>Remifentanil may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00909</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zonisamide</name>
      <description>Zonisamide may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00960</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pindolol</name>
      <description>Pindolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00968</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methyldopa</name>
      <description>Methyldopa may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00989</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rivastigmine</name>
      <description>Rivastigmine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01018</drugbank-id>
      <name>Guanfacine</name>
      <description>Guanfacine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01023</drugbank-id>
      <name>Felodipine</name>
      <description>Felodipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01054</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitrendipine</name>
      <description>Nitrendipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01074</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perhexiline</name>
      <description>Perhexiline may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01115</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nifedipine</name>
      <description>Nifedipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01118</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amiodarone</name>
      <description>Amiodarone may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01136</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carvedilol</name>
      <description>Carvedilol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01158</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bretylium</name>
      <description>Bretylium may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01182</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propafenone</name>
      <description>Propafenone may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01193</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acebutolol</name>
      <description>Acebutolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01203</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nadolol</name>
      <description>Nadolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01244</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bepridil</name>
      <description>Bepridil may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01295</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bevantolol</name>
      <description>Bevantolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01297</drugbank-id>
      <name>Practolol</name>
      <description>Practolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01359</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penbutolol</name>
      <description>Penbutolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01388</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mibefradil</name>
      <description>Mibefradil may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01580</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxprenolol</name>
      <description>Oxprenolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04743</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nimesulide</name>
      <description>Nimesulide may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04825</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prenylamine</name>
      <description>Prenylamine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04838</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclandelate</name>
      <description>Cyclandelate may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04841</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flunarizine</name>
      <description>Flunarizine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04842</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluspirilene</name>
      <description>Fluspirilene may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04846</drugbank-id>
      <name>Celiprolol</name>
      <description>Celiprolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04855</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dronedarone</name>
      <description>Dronedarone may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04861</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nebivolol</name>
      <description>Nebivolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04897</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lucinactant</name>
      <description>Lucinactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04920</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clevidipine</name>
      <description>Clevidipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05246</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methsuximide</name>
      <description>Methsuximide may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05885</drugbank-id>
      <name>Seletracetam</name>
      <description>Seletracetam may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06152</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nylidrin</name>
      <description>Nylidrin may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lacosamide</name>
      <description>Lacosamide may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06283</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ziconotide</name>
      <description>Ziconotide may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06415</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calfactant</name>
      <description>Calfactant may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06446</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dotarizine</name>
      <description>Dotarizine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06663</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pasireotide</name>
      <description>Pasireotide may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06712</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nilvadipine</name>
      <description>Nilvadipine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06726</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bufuralol</name>
      <description>Bufuralol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06761</drugbank-id>
      <name>Beractant</name>
      <description>Beractant may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06791</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lanreotide</name>
      <description>Lanreotide may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tranilast</name>
      <description>Tranilast may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08807</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bopindolol</name>
      <description>Bopindolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08808</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bupranolol</name>
      <description>Bupranolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08838</drugbank-id>
      <name>Agmatine</name>
      <description>Agmatine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08865</drugbank-id>
      <name>Crizotinib</name>
      <description>Crizotinib may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08868</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fingolimod</name>
      <description>Fingolimod may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08895</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tofacitinib</name>
      <description>Tofacitinib may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08896</drugbank-id>
      <name>Regorafenib</name>
      <description>Regorafenib may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08952</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indenolol</name>
      <description>Indenolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08980</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fendiline</name>
      <description>Fendiline may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08992</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eperisone</name>
      <description>Eperisone may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09013</drugbank-id>
      <name>Befunolol</name>
      <description>Befunolol may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09089</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimebutine</name>
      <description>Trimebutine may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09090</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pinaverium</name>
      <description>Pinaverium may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09204</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arotinolol</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Arotinolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09216</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolfenamic acid</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Tolfenamic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09227</drugbank-id>
      <name>Barnidipine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Barnidipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09229</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aranidipine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Aranidipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09230</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azelnidipine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Azelnidipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09231</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benidipine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Benidipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09232</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cilnidipine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Cilnidipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09234</drugbank-id>
      <name>Darodipine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Darodipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09235</drugbank-id>
      <name>Efonidipine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Efonidipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09236</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lacidipine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Lacidipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09238</drugbank-id>
      <name>Manidipine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Manidipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09239</drugbank-id>
      <name>Niguldipine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Niguldipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09240</drugbank-id>
      <name>Niludipine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Niludipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09351</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levobetaxolol</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Levobetaxolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11770</drugbank-id>
      <name>Talinolol</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Talinolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11785</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anisodamine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Anisodamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11960</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carboxyamidotriazole</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Carboxyamidotriazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12092</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naftopidil</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Naftopidil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12093</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetrahydropalmatine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Tetrahydropalmatine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12131</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vinpocetine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Vinpocetine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12212</drugbank-id>
      <name>Landiolol</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Landiolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12752</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bucindolol</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Bucindolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12923</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gallopamil</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Gallopamil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13443</drugbank-id>
      <name>Esatenolol</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Esatenolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13488</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bencyclane</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Bencyclane.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13500</drugbank-id>
      <name>Otilonium</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Otilonium.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13508</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cloranolol</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Cloranolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13530</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mepindolol</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Mepindolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13725</drugbank-id>
      <name>Terodiline</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Terodiline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13757</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epanolol</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Epanolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13766</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lidoflazine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Lidoflazine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13775</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tertatolol</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Tertatolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13791</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penfluridol</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Penfluridol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13835</drugbank-id>
      <name>Caroverine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Caroverine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13950</drugbank-id>
      <name>WIN 55212-2</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of WIN 55212-2.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13961</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fish oil</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Fish oil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14063</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexverapamil</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Dexverapamil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14064</drugbank-id>
      <name>Emopamil</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Emopamil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14065</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lomerizine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Lomerizine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14066</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetrandrine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Tetrandrine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14068</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexniguldipine</name>
      <description>Poractant alfa may increase the bradycardic activities of Dexniguldipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11732</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lasmiditan</name>
      <description>Lasmiditan may increase the bradycardic activities of Poractant alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>Water Solubility</kind>
      <value>Insoluble. </value>
      <source>#MSDS</source>
    </property>
  </experimental-properties>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Drugs Product Database (DPD)</resource>
      <identifier>11967</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910412</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>KEGG Drug</resource>
      <identifier>D08402</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Wikipedia</resource>
      <identifier>Poractant_alfa</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEMBL</resource>
      <identifier>CHEMBL1201622</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links>
    <external-link>
      <resource>RxList</resource>
      <url>http://www.rxlist.com/curosurf-drug.htm</url>
    </external-link>
    <external-link>
      <resource>Drugs.com</resource>
      <url>http://www.drugs.com/drp/poractant-alfa.html</url>
    </external-link>
  </external-links>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>