<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2008-03-19" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB06255</drugbank-id>
  <name>Incadronic acid</name>
  <description>Incadronic acid is a third generation bisphosphonate which can suppress bone resorption by osteoclasts. It is used to treat hypercalcemia, and bone disorders associated with malignancy and osteoporosis. In rats with induced hypercalcemia, incadronate has been found to be 46 times more potent than pamidronate and 11 times more potent than aledronate.&#13;
&#13;
Incadronate has also been found to have anti-tumor effects in mice. In rat models of breast cancer, bisphosphonate treatment has been shown to inhibit the progression and development of bone metastases and reduce tumor burden in vivo. It has also been recognized as a potential treatment for adult T-cell leukaemia which is characterized by hypercalcemia and tumor-induced osteolysis. [A14427] Incadronate, as well as other nitrogen containing bisphosphonates, such as aledronate and minodronate, have been found to induce apoptosis of hematopoietic tumor cells. In vitro human myeloma cells have undergone apoptosis when exposed to incadronate. [A14430]  &#13;
&#13;
When combined with Tipifarnib, a potent farnesyl transferase inhibitor which can suppress the growth of myeloma cells, growth suppression of myeloma cells in vitro is intensified. [A14431] Because of these findings Incadronate is being investigated as a treatment for multiple myeloma, a B-cell malignancy associated with bone loss. &#13;
&#13;
Incadronate is available by prescription only, and is not marked is the United States, UK, Canada, or Australia. It is an approved treatment for malignancy-associated hypercalcemia (MAH) in Japan.[A14433]</description>
  <cas-number>124351-85-5</cas-number>
  <unii>G5C4M8847E</unii>
  <average-mass>287.189</average-mass>
  <monoisotopic-mass>287.068761332</monoisotopic-mass>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>experimental</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A14426</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>12742232</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Iguchi T, Miyakawa Y, Yamamoto K, Kizaki M, Ikeda Y: Nitrogen-containing bisphosphonates induce S-phase cell cycle arrest and apoptosis of myeloma cells by activating MAPK pathway and inhibiting mevalonate pathway. Cell Signal. 2003 Jul;15(7):719-27.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A14427</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17233845</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Ishikawa C, Matsuda T, Okudaira T, Tomita M, Kawakami H, Tanaka Y, Masuda M, Ohshiro K, Ohta T, Mori N: Bisphosphonate incadronate inhibits growth of human T-cell leukaemia virus type I-infected T-cell lines and primary adult T-cell leukaemia cells by interfering with the mevalonate pathway. Br J Haematol. 2007 Feb;136(3):424-32.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A14428</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>24683210</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Kim SB, Lee JS, Kim HT, Im YH, Kim TW, Ryoo BY, Park YH, Park JO, Park K, Katoh H, Yamamoto M: Clinical evaluation of incadronate in korean patients with malignancy-associated hypercalcemia: An open-label, multicenter study. Curr Ther Res Clin Exp. 2007 May;68(3):193-204. doi: 10.1016/j.curtheres.2007.06.004.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A14429</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>12784404</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Matsuo A, Shuto T, Hirata G, Satoh H, Matsumoto Y, Zhao H, Iwamoto Y: Antiinflammatory and chondroprotective effects of the aminobisphosphonate incadronate (YM175) in adjuvant induced arthritis. J Rheumatol. 2003 Jun;30(6):1280-90.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A14430</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>12796698</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Oades GM, Senaratne SG, Clarke IA, Kirby RS, Colston KW: Nitrogen containing bisphosphonates induce apoptosis and inhibit the mevalonate pathway, impairing Ras membrane localization in prostate cancer cells. J Urol. 2003 Jul;170(1):246-52.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A14431</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>16236616</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Ochiai N, Yamada N, Uchida R, Fuchida S, Okano A, Okamoto M, Ashihara E, Inaba T, Shimazaki C: Nitrogen-containing bisphosphonate incadronate augments the inhibitory effect of farnesyl transferase inhibitor tipifarnib on the growth of fresh and cloned myeloma cells in vitro. Leuk Lymphoma. 2005 Nov;46(11):1619-25.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A14432</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>9850051</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Shipman CM, Croucher PI, Russell RG, Helfrich MH, Rogers MJ: The bisphosphonate incadronate (YM175) causes apoptosis of human myeloma cells in vitro by inhibiting the mevalonate pathway. Cancer Res. 1998 Dec 1;58(23):5294-7.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A14433</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>9208339</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Usui T, Oiso Y, Tomita A, Ogata E, Uchida T, Ikeda K, Watanabe T, Higuchi S: Pharmacokinetics of incadronate, a new bisphosphonate, in healthy volunteers and patients with malignancy-associated hypercalcemia. Int J Clin Pharmacol Ther. 1997 Jun;35(6):239-44.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>For the treatment of hypercalcemia associated with malignant disease.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>Incadronate suppresses bone resorption by inhibiting osteoclasts. Incadronate was found to induce apoptosis in myeloma cells by S-phase cell cycle arrest via inhibition of the mevalonate (MVA) pathway and activation of the MAPK pathway. [1] Similarly, in studies looking at the potential role of incadronate as a treatment for adult T-cell leukemia, incadronate has been shown to inhibit the growth of T-cell lines infected with the human T-cell leukaemia virus by inducing apoptosis and S-phase cell cycle arrest by inhibiting the mevalonate pathway.  &#13;
&#13;
Nitrogen containing bisphosphonates such as incandronate are known to induce apoptosis of hematopoietic tumor cells by inhibiting the Ras signaling pathway, as well as activating the Bim-mediated mitochondrial intrinsic apoptotic pathway. [5] They also induce apoptosis by inhibiting the prenylation of small G-proteins. [5]</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption>Pharmacokinetic studies in patients with MAH have indicated linear pharmacokinetics with intravenous administration. [8]&#13;
&#13;
In studies comparing absorption of incadronate in healthy volunteers verses volunteers with MAH plasma levels have been similar at 2 h, however at 8 h the plasma levels are three times higher in patients with MAH. This can be explained by the decrease in renal function experienced by patients with MAH. Notably, however, the plasma levels of incadronate are not as high as expected based on the reduction in renal clearance. This indicates that patients with hypercalcemia may experience enhanced bone uptake of the drug. [8]</absorption>
  <half-life>0.26-0.40 h (t1/2 alpha) and 1.58 - 1.98 h (t1/2 beta). [8]</half-life>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination>Renally eliminated. [8]</route-of-elimination>
  <volume-of-distribution>Incadronate rapidly relocalizes to bone due to its high affinity for mineralized bone. [4] Due to its incorporation into bone marrow osteoclasts the concentration of incadronate in the bone marrow is high. [4] </volume-of-distribution>
  <clearance>60% renal clearance. [8]  Changes in renal clearance may affect the pharmacokinetics of incadronate.</clearance>
  <classification>
    <description>This compound belongs to the class of organic compounds known as bisphosphonates. These are organic compounds containing two phosphonate groups linked together through a carbon atoms.</description>
    <direct-parent>Bisphosphonates</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic acids and derivatives</superclass>
    <class>Organic phosphonic acids and derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Bisphosphonates</subclass>
    <alternative-parent>Dialkylamines</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Hydrocarbon derivatives</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Organic oxides</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Organic phosphonic acids</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Organophosphorus compounds</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Organopnictogen compounds</alternative-parent>
    <substituent>Aliphatic homomonocyclic compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Amine</substituent>
    <substituent>Bisphosphonate</substituent>
    <substituent>Hydrocarbon derivative</substituent>
    <substituent>Organic nitrogen compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Organic oxide</substituent>
    <substituent>Organic oxygen compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Organonitrogen compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Organophosphonic acid</substituent>
    <substituent>Organophosphorus compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Organopnictogen compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Secondary aliphatic amine</substituent>
    <substituent>Secondary amine</substituent>
  </classification>
  <salts>
    <salt>
      <drugbank-id primary="true">DBSALT000559</drugbank-id>
      <name>Disodium incadronate</name>
      <unii>7L16W0096A</unii>
      <cas-number>138330-18-4</cas-number>
      <inchikey>RLIRIVMEKVNVQX-UHFFFAOYSA-L</inchikey>
      <average-mass>330.164</average-mass>
      <monoisotopic-mass>330.03740086</monoisotopic-mass>
    </salt>
  </salts>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Cimadronate</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Incadronate</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products/>
  <international-brands>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Bisphonal</name>
      <company>Astellas</company>
    </international-brand>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Yin Fu</name>
      <company>Renfu Pharmaceutical</company>
    </international-brand>
  </international-brands>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Bisphosphonates</category>
      <mesh-id>D004164</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Bone Density Conservation Agents</category>
      <mesh-id>D050071</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Organophosphonates</category>
      <mesh-id>D063065</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Organophosphorus Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D009943</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01609</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deferasirox</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding and gastrointestinal ulceration can be increased when Incadronic acid is combined with Deferasirox.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00112</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bevacizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Bevacizumab is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00480</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lenalidomide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Lenalidomide is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01041</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thalidomide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Thalidomide is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01268</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sunitinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Sunitinib is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01270</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ranibizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Ranibizumab is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02640</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fumagillin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Fumagillin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02709</drugbank-id>
      <name>Resveratrol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Resveratrol is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04866</drugbank-id>
      <name>Halofuginone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Halofuginone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05288</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anecortave acetate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Anecortave acetate is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06423</drugbank-id>
      <name>Endostatin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Endostatin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06436</drugbank-id>
      <name>Semaxanib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Semaxanib is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06461</drugbank-id>
      <name>Squalamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Squalamine is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06589</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pazopanib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Pazopanib is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06647</drugbank-id>
      <name>Volociximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Volociximab is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08633</drugbank-id>
      <name>TNP-470</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when TNP-470 is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08910</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pomalidomide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Pomalidomide is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11366</drugbank-id>
      <name>Roquinimex</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Roquinimex is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11727</drugbank-id>
      <name>Endostar</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Endostar is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12056</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trebananib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Trebananib is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12081</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anecortave</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Anecortave is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12671</drugbank-id>
      <name>Beloranib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Beloranib is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14864</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brolucizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of jaw osteonecrosis and anti-angiogenesis can be increased when Brolucizumab is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pantoprazole</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Incadronic acid can be decreased when used in combination with Pantoprazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00338</drugbank-id>
      <name>Omeprazole</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Incadronic acid can be decreased when used in combination with Omeprazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00448</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lansoprazole</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Incadronic acid can be decreased when used in combination with Lansoprazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00736</drugbank-id>
      <name>Esomeprazole</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Incadronic acid can be decreased when used in combination with Esomeprazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01129</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rabeprazole</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Incadronic acid can be decreased when used in combination with Rabeprazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05351</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexlansoprazole</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Incadronic acid can be decreased when used in combination with Dexlansoprazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13762</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexrabeprazole</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Incadronic acid can be decreased when used in combination with Dexrabeprazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11964</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ilaprazole</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Incadronic acid can be decreased when used in combination with Ilaprazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00159</drugbank-id>
      <name>Icosapent</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Icosapent is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00244</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mesalazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Mesalazine is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00328</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indomethacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Indomethacin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00461</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nabumetone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Nabumetone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00465</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketorolac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Ketorolac is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00469</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenoxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Tenoxicam is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00482</drugbank-id>
      <name>Celecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Celecoxib is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00500</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolmetin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Tolmetin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00533</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rofecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Rofecoxib is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00554</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piroxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Piroxicam is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00573</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Fenoprofen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00580</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valdecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Valdecoxib is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00586</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diclofenac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Diclofenac is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00605</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulindac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Sulindac is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00712</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flurbiprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Flurbiprofen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00749</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etodolac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Etodolac is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00784</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mefenamic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Mefenamic acid is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00788</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naproxen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Naproxen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00795</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfasalazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Sulfasalazine is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00812</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenylbutazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Phenylbutazone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00814</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meloxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Meloxicam is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00821</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Carprofen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00861</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diflunisal</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Diflunisal is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00936</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salicylic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Salicylic acid is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00939</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meclofenamic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Meclofenamic acid is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00945</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetylsalicylic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Acetylsalicylic acid is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00991</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxaprozin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Oxaprozin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01009</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Ketoprofen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01014</drugbank-id>
      <name>Balsalazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Balsalazide is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01050</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibuprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Ibuprofen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01250</drugbank-id>
      <name>Olsalazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Olsalazine is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01283</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lumiracoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Lumiracoxib is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01397</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium salicylate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Magnesium salicylate is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01399</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salsalate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Salsalate is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01401</drugbank-id>
      <name>Choline magnesium trisalicylate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Choline magnesium trisalicylate is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01419</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antrafenine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Antrafenine is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01424</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aminophenazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Aminophenazone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01435</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antipyrine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Antipyrine is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01600</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiaprofenic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Tiaprofenic acid is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01628</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etoricoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Etoricoxib is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02224</drugbank-id>
      <name>Taxifolin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Taxifolin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03585</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxyphenbutazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Oxyphenbutazone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04552</drugbank-id>
      <name>Niflumic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Niflumic acid is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04725</drugbank-id>
      <name>Licofelone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Licofelone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04743</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nimesulide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Nimesulide is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04812</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benoxaprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Benoxaprofen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metamizole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Metamizole is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04828</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zomepirac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Zomepirac is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05095</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cimicoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Cimicoxib is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06725</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lornoxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Lornoxicam is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06736</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aceclofenac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Aceclofenac is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06737</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zaltoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Zaltoprofen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07402</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azapropazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Azapropazone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07477</drugbank-id>
      <name>Felbinac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Felbinac is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08439</drugbank-id>
      <name>Parecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Parecoxib is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08797</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salicylamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Salicylamide is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08940</drugbank-id>
      <name>Kebuzone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Kebuzone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08942</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isoxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Isoxicam is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08951</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Indoprofen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08955</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibuproxam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Ibuproxam is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08976</drugbank-id>
      <name>Floctafenine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Floctafenine is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08981</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenbufen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Fenbufen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08984</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etofenamate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Etofenamate is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08991</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epirizole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Epirizole is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09084</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benzydamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Benzydamine is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09212</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loxoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Loxoprofen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexibuprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Dexibuprofen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09214</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexketoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Dexketoprofen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09215</drugbank-id>
      <name>Droxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Droxicam is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09216</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolfenamic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Tolfenamic acid is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09217</drugbank-id>
      <name>Firocoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Firocoxib is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clonixin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Clonixin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09285</drugbank-id>
      <name>Morniflumate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Morniflumate is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09288</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propacetamol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Propacetamol is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09295</drugbank-id>
      <name>Talniflumate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Talniflumate is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11455</drugbank-id>
      <name>Robenacoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Robenacoxib is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11466</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tepoxalin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Tepoxalin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11518</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flunixin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Flunixin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12399</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polmacoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Polmacoxib is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12445</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitroaspirin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Nitroaspirin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12480</drugbank-id>
      <name>Betulinic Acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Betulinic Acid is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12545</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indobufen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Indobufen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12610</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ebselen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Ebselen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13001</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tinoridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Tinoridine is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13167</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alclofenac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Alclofenac is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13217</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fentiazac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Fentiazac is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13232</drugbank-id>
      <name>Suxibuzone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Suxibuzone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13286</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bumadizone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Bumadizone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13314</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alminoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Alminoprofen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flunoxaprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Flunoxaprofen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13364</drugbank-id>
      <name>Feprazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Feprazone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13371</drugbank-id>
      <name>Difenpiramide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Difenpiramide is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13407</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nifenazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Nifenazone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13432</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lonazolac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Lonazolac is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13481</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenidap</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Tenidap is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13501</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bendazac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Bendazac is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13514</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pranoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Pranoprofen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13524</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propyphenazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Propyphenazone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13527</drugbank-id>
      <name>Proglumetacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Proglumetacin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13538</drugbank-id>
      <name>Guacetisal</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Guacetisal is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13544</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethenzamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Ethenzamide is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13612</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbaspirin calcium</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Carbaspirin calcium is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13629</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mofebutazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Mofebutazone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13649</drugbank-id>
      <name>Proquazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Proquazone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13657</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benorilate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Benorilate is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13722</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pirprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Pirprofen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acemetacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Acemetacin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13860</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imidazole salicylate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Imidazole salicylate is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14059</drugbank-id>
      <name>SC-236</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when SC-236 is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14060</drugbank-id>
      <name>NS-398</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when NS-398 is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14938</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flurbiprofen axetil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of gastrointestinal bleeding can be increased when Flurbiprofen axetil is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00017</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salmon Calcitonin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypocalcemia can be increased when Salmon Calcitonin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06773</drugbank-id>
      <name>Human calcitonin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypocalcemia can be increased when Human calcitonin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13189</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcitonin porcine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypocalcemia can be increased when Calcitonin porcine is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13742</drugbank-id>
      <name>Elcatonin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypocalcemia can be increased when Elcatonin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00314</drugbank-id>
      <name>Capreomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Capreomycin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00452</drugbank-id>
      <name>Framycetin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Framycetin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00479</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amikacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00684</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tobramycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Tobramycin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00798</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gentamicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Gentamicin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00955</drugbank-id>
      <name>Netilmicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Netilmicin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00994</drugbank-id>
      <name>Neomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Neomycin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01082</drugbank-id>
      <name>Streptomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Streptomycin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01172</drugbank-id>
      <name>Kanamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Kanamycin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01421</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paromomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Paromomycin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ribostamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Ribostamycin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04263</drugbank-id>
      <name>Geneticin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Geneticin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04626</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apramycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Apramycin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04729</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gentamicin C1a</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Gentamicin C1a is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04808</drugbank-id>
      <name>Neamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Neamine is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06696</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arbekacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Arbekacin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08437</drugbank-id>
      <name>Puromycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Puromycin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11512</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dihydrostreptomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Dihydrostreptomycin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11520</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hygromycin B</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Hygromycin B is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12604</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sisomicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Sisomicin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Plazomicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Plazomicin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13270</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dibekacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Dibekacin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13274</drugbank-id>
      <name>Micronomicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Micronomicin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13540</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isepamicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Isepamicin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13673</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bekanamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Bekanamycin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01370</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aluminium</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Aluminium.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01377</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium oxide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Magnesium oxide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01390</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium bicarbonate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Sodium bicarbonate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06723</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aluminum hydroxide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Aluminum hydroxide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06724</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium carbonate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium carbonate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08938</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magaldrate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Magaldrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09104</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium hydroxide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Magnesium hydroxide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09281</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium trisilicate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Magnesium trisilicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09481</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium carbonate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Magnesium carbonate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13209</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bismuth subnitrate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Bismuth subnitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13249</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium silicate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Magnesium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13280</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aluminium acetoacetate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Aluminium acetoacetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13322</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrotalcite</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Hydrotalcite.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13486</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium peroxide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Magnesium peroxide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Almasilate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Almasilate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13626</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aluminium glycinate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Aluminium glycinate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13650</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aloglutamol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Aloglutamol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13829</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium silicate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14517</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aluminium phosphate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Aluminium phosphate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00653</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium sulfate</name>
      <description>Magnesium sulfate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09407</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium chloride</name>
      <description>Magnesium chloride can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11110</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium citrate</name>
      <description>Magnesium citrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13359</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium aspartate</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13749</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium gluconate</name>
      <description>Magnesium gluconate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13786</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium orotate</name>
      <description>Magnesium orotate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14513</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium</name>
      <description>Magnesium can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14514</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium levulinate</name>
      <description>Magnesium levulinate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14515</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium lactate</name>
      <description>Magnesium lactate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00258</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium acetate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium acetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00326</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium glucoheptonate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium glucoheptonate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01164</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium chloride</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium Chloride.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01373</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11093</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium Citrate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium Citrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11126</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium gluconate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium gluconate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11348</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium Phosphate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium Phosphate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13142</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium glubionate anhydrous</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium glubionate anhydrous.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13231</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium lactate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium lactate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13365</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium lactate gluconate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium lactate gluconate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13590</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium pangamate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium pangamate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13800</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium levulinate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium levulinate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14577</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium cation</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium cation.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14684</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium polycarbophil</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium polycarbophil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09139</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m oxidronate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypocalcemia can be increased when Incadronic acid is combined with Technetium Tc-99m oxidronate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00214</drugbank-id>
      <name>Torasemide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypocalcemia can be increased when Torasemide is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00695</drugbank-id>
      <name>Furosemide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypocalcemia can be increased when Furosemide is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00887</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bumetanide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypocalcemia can be increased when Bumetanide is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00903</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etacrynic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypocalcemia can be increased when Etacrynic acid is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02925</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piretanide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypocalcemia can be increased when Piretanide is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08961</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azosemide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypocalcemia can be increased when Azosemide is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00091</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclosporine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cyclosporine is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00229</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefotiam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefotiam is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00267</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefmenoxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefmenoxime is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00274</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefmetazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefmetazole is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00282</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pamidronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Pamidronic acid is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00300</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenofovir disoproxil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Tenofovir disoproxil is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00369</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cidofovir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cidofovir is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00384</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triamterene</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Triamterene is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00430</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefpiramide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefpiramide is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00438</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftazidime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Ceftazidime is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00447</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loracarbef</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Loracarbef is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00456</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefalotin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefalotin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00493</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefotaxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefotaxime is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00512</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vancomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Vancomycin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00515</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cisplatin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cisplatin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00529</drugbank-id>
      <name>Foscarnet</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Foscarnet is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00563</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methotrexate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Methotrexate is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00567</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cephalexin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cephalexin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00577</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valaciclovir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Valaciclovir is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00626</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bacitracin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Bacitracin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00681</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amphotericin B</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Amphotericin B is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00689</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cephaloglycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cephaloglycin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00718</drugbank-id>
      <name>Adefovir dipivoxil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Adefovir dipivoxil is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00738</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentamidine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Pentamidine is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00742</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mannitol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Mannitol is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00787</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acyclovir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Acyclovir is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00833</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefaclor</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefaclor is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00864</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tacrolimus</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Tacrolimus is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00923</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceforanide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Ceforanide is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00958</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carboplatin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Carboplatin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00999</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrochlorothiazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Hydrochlorothiazide is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01066</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefditoren</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefditoren is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01072</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atazanavir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Atazanavir is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01111</drugbank-id>
      <name>Colistimethate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Colistimethate is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01112</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefuroxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefuroxime is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01139</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefapirin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefapirin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01140</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefadroxil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefadroxil is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01150</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefprozil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefprozil is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01212</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftriaxone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Ceftriaxone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01326</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefamandole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefamandole is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01327</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefazolin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefazolin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01328</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefonicid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefonicid is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01329</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefoperazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefoperazone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01330</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefotetan</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefotetan is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01331</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefoxitin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefoxitin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01332</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftizoxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Ceftizoxime is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01333</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefradine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefradine is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01356</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium cation</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Lithium cation is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01413</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefepime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefepime is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01414</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefacetrile</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefacetrile is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01415</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftibuten</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Ceftibuten is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01416</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefpodoxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefpodoxime is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01601</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lopinavir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Lopinavir is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02247</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrolyzed Cephalothin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Hydrolyzed Cephalothin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03450</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cephalothin Group</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cephalothin Group is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04570</drugbank-id>
      <name>Latamoxef</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Latamoxef is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04918</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftobiprole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Ceftobiprole is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06590</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftaroline fosamil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Ceftaroline fosamil is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09008</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefaloridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefaloridine is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09062</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefminox</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefminox is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09299</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenofovir alafenamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Tenofovir alafenamide is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11367</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefroxadine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefroxadine is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11935</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flomoxef</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Flomoxef is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12151</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brincidofovir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Brincidofovir is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13266</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefatrizine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefatrizine is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13461</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefcapene</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefcapene is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13470</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefodizime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefodizime is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13499</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefsulodin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefsulodin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13504</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefetamet</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefetamet is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13638</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefbuperazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefbuperazone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13667</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefozopran</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefozopran is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13682</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefpirome</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefpirome is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13778</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefazedone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Cefazedone is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13821</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftezole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Ceftezole is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13868</drugbank-id>
      <name>Adefovir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Adefovir is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14126</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenofovir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Tenofovir is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14713</drugbank-id>
      <name>Inotersen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01438</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenazopyridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Phenazopyridine is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14507</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium citrate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Lithium citrate is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14509</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium carbonate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Lithium carbonate is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15066</drugbank-id>
      <name>Givosiran</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Givosiran is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00399</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zoledronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Zoledronic acid is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00630</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alendronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Alendronic acid is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00710</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibandronate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ibandronate is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00720</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clodronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Clodronic acid is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00884</drugbank-id>
      <name>Risedronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Risedronic acid is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01077</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etidronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Etidronic acid is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01133</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiludronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tiludronic acid is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05829</drugbank-id>
      <name>Parathyroid hormone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Parathyroid hormone can be decreased when used in combination with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00325</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitroprusside</name>
      <description>Nitroprusside can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prussian blue</name>
      <description>Prussian blue can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09146</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iron sucrose</name>
      <description>Iron sucrose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09501</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric ammonium citrate</name>
      <description>Ferric ammonium citrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09507</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferumoxsil</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09508</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferumoxides</name>
      <description>Ferumoxides can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11171</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric sulfate</name>
      <description>Ferric sulfate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11210</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous bisglycinate</name>
      <description>Ferrous bisglycinate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11417</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gleptoferron</name>
      <description>Gleptoferron can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11576</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric oxide</name>
      <description>Ferric oxide can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iron isomaltoside 1000</name>
      <description>Iron isomaltoside 1000 can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12821</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perflubutane</name>
      <description>Perflubutane can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13257</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous sulfate anhydrous</name>
      <description>Ferrous sulfate anhydrous can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13381</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium feredetate</name>
      <description>Sodium feredetate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13423</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric hydroxide</name>
      <description>Ferric hydroxide can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13569</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous chloride</name>
      <description>Ferrous chloride can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13949</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric cation</name>
      <description>Ferric cation can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14488</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous gluconate</name>
      <description>Ferrous gluconate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14489</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous succinate</name>
      <description>Ferrous succinate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14491</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous fumarate</name>
      <description>Ferrous fumarate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14520</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetraferric tricitrate decahydrate</name>
      <description>Tetraferric tricitrate decahydrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14695</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric oxyhydroxide</name>
      <description>Ferric oxyhydroxide can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <calculated-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>-0.06</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logS</kind>
      <value>-1.4</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Water Solubility</kind>
      <value>1.25e+01 g/l</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>-1.4</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>[(cycloheptylamino)(phosphono)methyl]phosphonic acid</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Traditional IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>incadronic acid</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Weight</kind>
      <value>287.189</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Monoisotopic Weight</kind>
      <value>287.068761332</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>SMILES</kind>
      <value>OP(O)(=O)C(NC1CCCCCC1)P(O)(O)=O</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Formula</kind>
      <value>C8H19NO6P2</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChI</kind>
      <value>InChI=1S/C8H19NO6P2/c10-16(11,12)8(17(13,14)15)9-7-5-3-1-2-4-6-7/h7-9H,1-6H2,(H2,10,11,12)(H2,13,14,15)</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChIKey</kind>
      <value>LWRDQHOZTAOILO-UHFFFAOYSA-N</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polar Surface Area (PSA)</kind>
      <value>127.09</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Refractivity</kind>
      <value>61.77</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polarizability</kind>
      <value>25.08</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rotatable Bond Count</kind>
      <value>4</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Acceptor Count</kind>
      <value>7</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Donor Count</kind>
      <value>5</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest acidic)</kind>
      <value>-1.1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest basic)</kind>
      <value>5.57</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Physiological Charge</kind>
      <value>-2</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Number of Rings</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Bioavailability</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rule of Five</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Ghose Filter</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>MDDR-Like Rule</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
  </calculated-properties>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEBI</resource>
      <identifier>135189</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Compound</resource>
      <identifier>3699</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>175427066</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChemSpider</resource>
      <identifier>3571</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Wikipedia</resource>
      <identifier>Incadronic_acid</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEMBL</resource>
      <identifier>CHEMBL53950</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>