<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-11-18" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05894</drugbank-id>
  <name>GT 389-255</name>
  <description>Peptimmune’s lead product GT 389-255, is a novel lipase inhibitor and fat binding hydrogel polymer conjugate for the treatment of obesity which has completed single and multiple ascending dose (SAD and MAD) Phase I trials. It is expected to block fat absorption with fewer side effects than currently marketed lipase inhibitors.&#13;
</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in obesity.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>GT 389-255 is a novel conjugate of a proprietary pancreatic lipase inhibitor and a fatbinding hydrogel polymer for the treatment of obesity. GT 389-255 is a novel conjugate of a proprietary pancreatic lipase inhibitor and a fat binding hydrogel polymer for the treatment of obesity. It acts within the gastro-intestinal tract to prevent fat digestion and is expected to inhibit &gt; 30% of fat absorption. The novel conjugate is expected to have fewer side-effects than currently marketed therapies. The currently marketed pancreatic lipase inhibitor Orlistat, is associated with oily incontinence, caused by mal-absorbed triglycerides. GT 389-255 is expected to have minimal systemic exposure. Less than 1% of the lipase inhibitor is absorbed and the fat binding polymer is not absorbed.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910299</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>