<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2007-10-21" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05236</drugbank-id>
  <name>ReN001</name>
  <description>ReN001 is a clonal human neural stem cell line developed for clinical use in the treatment of stable disability after stroke. ReN001 a strong candidate for one of the first cell-based IND applications to be submitted to the Food and Drug Administration in the United States for consideration for the treatment of stroke in humans.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>liquid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3297</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17981710</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Stroemer P, Hope A, Patel S, Pollock K, Sinden J: Development of a human neural stem cell line for use in recovery from disability after stroke. Front Biosci. 2008 Jan 1;13:2290-2.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>For the treatment of stroke.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>ReN001 is a clonal human neural stem cell line which has been conditionally immortalized using the fusion transgene c-mycERTAM to allow controlled expansion when cultured in the presence of 4-hydroxytamoxifen. The cell line has been banked and fully characterized to assure there is genetic stability and no phenotypic drift with extended passages. In vivo studies determined the ability of the cell line to survive after implantation into damaged brain and its efficacy in the reduction of chronic behavioural dysfunction after implantation into a rodent model of stroke damage. A further study was conducted in this model and a dose-dependent effect was observed on behavioural recovery. No safety or toxicology issues were identified in in vivo studies with this cell line.</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action/>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910042</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>