<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2007-10-21" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB04976</drugbank-id>
  <name>M40403</name>
  <description>M40403 is a low molecular weight, synthetic manganese containing superoxide dismutase mimetic (SODm) that selectively removes superoxide anion.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3117</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>11181422</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Salvemini D, Mazzon E, Dugo L, Riley DP, Serraino I, Caputi AP, Cuzzocrea S: Pharmacological manipulation of the inflammatory cascade by the superoxide dismutase mimetic, M40403. Br J Pharmacol. 2001 Feb;132(4):815-27.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3118</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>11734191</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Cuzzocrea S, Mazzon E, Dugo L, Caputi AP, Riley DP, Salvemini D: Protective effects of M40403, a superoxide dismutase mimetic, in a rodent model of colitis. Eur J Pharmacol. 2001 Nov 30;432(1):79-89.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3119</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>12110615</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Masini E, Cuzzocrea S, Mazzon E, Marzocca C, Mannaioni PF, Salvemini D: Protective effects of M40403, a selective superoxide dismutase mimetic, in myocardial ischaemia and reperfusion injury in vivo. Br J Pharmacol. 2002 Jul;136(6):905-17.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3120</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>12490600</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Wang C, McInnis J, West JB, Bao J, Anastasio N, Guidry JA, Ye Y, Salvemini D, Johnson KM: Blockade of phencyclidine-induced cortical apoptosis and deficits in prepulse inhibition by M40403, a superoxide dismutase mimetic. J Pharmacol Exp Ther. 2003 Jan;304(1):266-71.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3121</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>12583992</pubmed-id>
        <citation>McFadden SL, Ding D, Salvemini D, Salvi RJ: M40403, a superoxide dismutase mimetic, protects cochlear hair cells from gentamicin, but not cisplatin toxicity. Toxicol Appl Pharmacol. 2003 Jan 1;186(1):46-54.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3122</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>12730689</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Samlowski WE, Petersen R, Cuzzocrea S, Macarthur H, Burton D, McGregor JR, Salvemini D: A nonpeptidyl mimic of superoxide dismutase, M40403, inhibits dose-limiting hypotension associated with interleukin-2 and increases its antitumor effects. Nat Med. 2003 Jun;9(6):750-5. Epub 2003 May 5.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3123</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>12755394</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Marzocca C, Vannacci A, Cuzzocrea S, Salvemini D, Mannaioni PF, Masini E: Effects of the SOD mimetic, M40403, on prostaglandin production in an in vivo model of ischemia and reperfusion in rat heart. Inflamm Res. 2003 Apr;52 Suppl 1:S23-4.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3124</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>12871831</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Jiang F, Guo Y, Salvemini D, Dusting GJ: Superoxide dismutase mimetic M40403 improves endothelial function in apolipoprotein(E)-deficient mice. Br J Pharmacol. 2003 Jul;139(6):1127-34.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3125</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>15321736</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Di Filippo C, Cuzzocrea S, Marfella R, Fabbroni V, Scollo G, Berrino L, Giugliano D, Rossi F, D'Amico M: M40403 prevents myocardial injury induced by acute hyperglycaemia in perfused rat heart. Eur J Pharmacol. 2004 Aug 16;497(1):65-74.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Intended for the treatment of pain and possibly various forms of cancer.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>M40403 treatment exerts a protective effect against ischaemia-reperfusion-induced myocardial injury, supporting a key role for superoxide anion in reperfusion injuries.</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>M40403 is the lead candidate in a unique class of compounds known as&#13;
superoxide dismutase (SOD) mimetics. These stable, low molecular weight&#13;
compounds mimic the effect of superoxide dismutase, a naturally occurring&#13;
enzyme designed to destroy superoxide free radicals present in various&#13;
diseases associated with pain and inflammation.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Elements</category>
      <mesh-id>D004602</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Metals</category>
      <mesh-id>D008670</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Metals, Heavy</category>
      <mesh-id>D019216</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Transition Elements</category>
      <mesh-id>D028561</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences>
    <sequence format="FASTA">&gt;P04179|SODM_HUMAN Superoxide dismutase [Mn], mitochondrial precursor - Homo sapiens
MLSRAVCGTSRQLAPALGYLGSRQKHSLPDLPYDYGALEPHINAQIMQLHHSKHHAAYVN
NLNVTEEKYQEALAKGDVTAQIALQPALKFNGGGHINHSIFWTNLSPNGGGEPKGELLEA
IKRDFGSFDKFKEKLTAASVGVQGSGWGWLGFNKERGHLQIAACPNQDPLQGTTGLIPLL
GIDVWEHAYYLQYKNVRPDYLKAIWNVINWENVTERYMACKK</sequence>
  </sequences>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347909869</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>UniProtKB</resource>
      <identifier>P04179</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>