<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-11-18" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05722</drugbank-id>
  <name>CGC-11047</name>
  <description>CGC-11047 is a polyamine analog designed to halt cell growth and induce apoptosis.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii>HU43305R7O</unii>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3755</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17410332</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Mitchell JL, Thane TK, Sequeira JM, Marton LJ, Thokala R: Antizyme and antizyme inhibitor activities influence cellular responses to polyamine analogs. Amino Acids. 2007 Aug;33(2):291-7. Epub 2007 Apr 6.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3756</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>16950258</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Lima e Silva R, Kachi S, Akiyama H, Shen J, Hatara MC, Aslam S, Gong YY, Khu NH, Lauer TW, Hackett SF, Marton LJ, Campochiaro PA: Trans-scleral delivery of polyamine analogs for ocular neovascularization. Exp Eye Res. 2006 Nov;83(5):1260-7. Epub 2006 Sep 6.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3757</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>15872118</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Loussouarn G, Marton LJ, Nichols CG: Molecular basis of inward rectification: structural features of the blocker defined by extended polyamine analogs. Mol Pharmacol. 2005 Aug;68(2):298-304. Epub 2005 May 4.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in lymphoma (unspecified), macular degeneration, prostate cancer, and solid tumors.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>CGC-11047 is a polyamine analog with anti-proliferative properties. Polyamines are cell components considered essential for cell proliferation and differentiation. They are believed to work by displacing polyamines from their natural binding sites and preventing cell replication. CGC-11047 has been very well-tolerated in Phase I clinical trials and has demonstrated promising activity in patients with advanced disease.</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>The mechanism of action of CGC-11047 is unknown but it is believed to block the growth of cancer cells by blocking the production of new DNA in the cancer cells.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Amines</category>
      <mesh-id>D000588</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910197</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>