<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2017-06-23" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB13359</drugbank-id>
  <name>Magnesium aspartate</name>
  <description>Magnesium aspartate is a magnesium salt of aspartic acid that is commonly used as a mineral supplement. It displays high oral bioavailability and water solubiltiy compared to other magnesium salts such as magnesium citrate, magnesium carbonate and magnesium oxide.</description>
  <cas-number>7018-07-7</cas-number>
  <unii>R17X820ROL</unii>
  <groups>
    <group>experimental</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication/>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action/>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>Dermamed Nutrition for troubled skin</name>
      <labeller>DermaMed</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>69711-687</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2019-09-18</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Capsule, gelatin coated</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Oral</route>
      <fda-application-number>part347</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>true</over-the-counter>
      <approved>false</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>Dermamed Nutrition for troubled skin</name>
      <ingredients>Ascorbic acid + Copper Cu-64 + Magnesium aspartate + Thiamine + Vitamin A + Vitamin D + Zinc gluconate</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Agents that produce neuromuscular block (indirect)</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Alimentary Tract and Metabolism</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Magnesium Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D017616</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Metal cations</category>
      <mesh-id>D002412</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Metal divalent cations</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Mineral Supplements</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Capsule, gelatin coated</form>
      <route>Oral</route>
      <strength/>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes>
    <atc-code code="A12CC05">
      <level code="A12CC">Magnesium</level>
      <level code="A12C">OTHER MINERAL SUPPLEMENTS</level>
      <level code="A12">MINERAL SUPPLEMENTS</level>
      <level code="A">ALIMENTARY TRACT AND METABOLISM</level>
    </atc-code>
  </atc-codes>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00202</drugbank-id>
      <name>Succinylcholine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Succinylcholine can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00416</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metocurine iodide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Metocurine iodide can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00483</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gallamine triethiodide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Gallamine triethiodide can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00565</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cisatracurium</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Cisatracurium can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00728</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rocuronium</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Rocuronium can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00732</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atracurium besylate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Atracurium besylate can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01135</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxacurium</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Doxacurium can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01226</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mivacurium</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Mivacurium can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01245</drugbank-id>
      <name>Decamethonium</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Decamethonium can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01336</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metocurine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Metocurine can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01337</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pancuronium</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Pancuronium can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01338</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pipecuronium</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Pipecuronium can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01339</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vecuronium</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Vecuronium can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04834</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rapacuronium</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Rapacuronium can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11156</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pyrantel</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Pyrantel can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12989</drugbank-id>
      <name>Neosaxitoxin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Neosaxitoxin can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13295</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atracurium</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Atracurium can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13584</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gallamine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Gallamine can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13648</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alcuronium</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Alcuronium can be increased when used in combination with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01586</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ursodeoxycholic acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ursodeoxycholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02123</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glycochenodeoxycholic Acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Glycochenodeoxycholic Acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02659</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cholic Acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Cholic Acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02691</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glycocholic acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Glycocholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03619</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deoxycholic acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Deoxycholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04348</drugbank-id>
      <name>Taurocholic acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Taurocholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05990</drugbank-id>
      <name>Obeticholic acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Obeticholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06777</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chenodeoxycholic acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Chenodeoxycholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08833</drugbank-id>
      <name>Taurochenodeoxycholic acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Taurochenodeoxycholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08834</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tauroursodeoxycholic acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Tauroursodeoxycholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08857</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bamet-UD2</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Bamet-UD2 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11622</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dehydrocholic acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dehydrocholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11789</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hyodeoxycholic Acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Hyodeoxycholic Acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00136</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcitriol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Magnesium aspartate can be increased when it is combined with Calcitriol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00146</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcifediol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Magnesium aspartate can be increased when it is combined with Calcifediol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00153</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ergocalciferol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Magnesium aspartate can be increased when it is combined with Ergocalciferol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00169</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cholecalciferol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Magnesium aspartate can be increased when it is combined with Cholecalciferol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00910</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paricalcitol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Magnesium aspartate can be increased when it is combined with Paricalcitol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01070</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dihydrotachysterol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Magnesium aspartate can be increased when it is combined with Dihydrotachysterol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01436</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alfacalcidol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Magnesium aspartate can be increased when it is combined with Alfacalcidol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04258</drugbank-id>
      <name>Seocalcitol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Magnesium aspartate can be increased when it is combined with Seocalcitol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04796</drugbank-id>
      <name>Inecalcitol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Magnesium aspartate can be increased when it is combined with Inecalcitol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04891</drugbank-id>
      <name>Becocalcidiol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Magnesium aspartate can be increased when it is combined with Becocalcidiol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05295</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eldecalcitol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Magnesium aspartate can be increased when it is combined with Eldecalcitol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06117</drugbank-id>
      <name>1alpha,24S-Dihydroxyvitamin D2</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Magnesium aspartate can be increased when it is combined with 1alpha,24S-Dihydroxyvitamin D2.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06194</drugbank-id>
      <name>Elocalcitol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Magnesium aspartate can be increased when it is combined with Elocalcitol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06272</drugbank-id>
      <name>Maxacalcitol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Magnesium aspartate can be increased when it is combined with Maxacalcitol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06410</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxercalciferol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Magnesium aspartate can be increased when it is combined with Doxercalciferol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13097</drugbank-id>
      <name>1alpha-Hydroxyvitamin D5</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Magnesium aspartate can be increased when it is combined with 1alpha-Hydroxyvitamin D5.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13689</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tacalcitol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Magnesium aspartate can be increased when it is combined with Tacalcitol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08826</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deferiprone</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Deferiprone resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06210</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eltrombopag</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Eltrombopag resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Raltegravir</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Raltegravir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Halofantrine</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Halofantrine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00929</drugbank-id>
      <name>Misoprostol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium aspartate is combined with Misoprostol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moxifloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Moxifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00365</drugbank-id>
      <name>Grepafloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Grepafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00467</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enoxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Enoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00487</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pefloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pefloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00537</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ciprofloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ciprofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00685</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trovafloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Trovafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00779</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nalidixic acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Nalidixic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rosoxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rosoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00827</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cinoxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Cinoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00978</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lomefloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Lomefloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01044</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gatifloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Gatifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01059</drugbank-id>
      <name>Norfloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Norfloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01137</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levofloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Levofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01165</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ofloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sparfloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sparfloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01405</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temafloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Temafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04576</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fleroxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Fleroxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05488</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m ciprofloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Technetium Tc-99m ciprofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06160</drugbank-id>
      <name>Garenoxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Garenoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06600</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nemonoxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Nemonoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08972</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flumequine</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Flumequine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11404</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enrofloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Enrofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11443</drugbank-id>
      <name>Orbifloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Orbifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11491</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sarafloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sarafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11511</drugbank-id>
      <name>Difloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Difloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11774</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pazufloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pazufloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11892</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prulifloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Prulifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11943</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delafloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Delafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13261</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sitafloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sitafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13627</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxolinic acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Oxolinic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13772</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rufloxacin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rufloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13823</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pipemidic acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pipemidic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00256</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lymecycline</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Lymecycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00453</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clomocycline</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Clomocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxytetracycline</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Oxytetracycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00618</drugbank-id>
      <name>Demeclocycline</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Demeclocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00759</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetracycline</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Tetracycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00931</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metacycline</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Metacycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01017</drugbank-id>
      <name>Minocycline</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Minocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12035</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sarecycline</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sarecycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12455</drugbank-id>
      <name>Omadacycline</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Omadacycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13092</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meclocycline</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Meclocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penimepicycline</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Penimepicycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00270</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isradipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Isradipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00343</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diltiazem</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Diltiazem is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00347</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimethadione</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Trimethadione is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00381</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amlodipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Amlodipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00393</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nimodipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Nimodipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00401</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nisoldipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Nisoldipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00528</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lercanidipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Lercanidipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00555</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lamotrigine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Lamotrigine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00568</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cinnarizine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Cinnarizine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00593</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethosuximide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Ethosuximide is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00622</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nicardipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Nicardipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00653</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium sulfate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Magnesium sulfate is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00661</drugbank-id>
      <name>Verapamil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Verapamil is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00836</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loperamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Loperamide is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00909</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zonisamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Zonisamide is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01023</drugbank-id>
      <name>Felodipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Felodipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01054</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitrendipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Nitrendipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01074</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perhexiline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Perhexiline is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01115</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nifedipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Nifedipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01118</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amiodarone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Amiodarone is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01136</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carvedilol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Carvedilol is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01244</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bepridil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Bepridil is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01388</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mibefradil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Mibefradil is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04743</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nimesulide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Nimesulide is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04825</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prenylamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Prenylamine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04838</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclandelate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Cyclandelate is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04841</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flunarizine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Flunarizine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04842</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluspirilene</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Fluspirilene is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04920</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clevidipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Clevidipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05246</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methsuximide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Methsuximide is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05885</drugbank-id>
      <name>Seletracetam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Seletracetam is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06152</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nylidrin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Nylidrin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06283</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ziconotide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Ziconotide is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06446</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dotarizine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Dotarizine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06712</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nilvadipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Nilvadipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tranilast</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Tranilast is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08162</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fasudil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Fasudil is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08838</drugbank-id>
      <name>Agmatine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Agmatine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08980</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fendiline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Fendiline is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08992</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eperisone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Eperisone is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09089</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimebutine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Trimebutine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09090</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pinaverium</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Pinaverium is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09216</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolfenamic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Tolfenamic acid is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09227</drugbank-id>
      <name>Barnidipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Barnidipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09229</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aranidipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Aranidipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09230</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azelnidipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Azelnidipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09231</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benidipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Benidipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09232</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cilnidipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Cilnidipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09234</drugbank-id>
      <name>Darodipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Darodipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09235</drugbank-id>
      <name>Efonidipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Efonidipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09236</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lacidipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Lacidipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09238</drugbank-id>
      <name>Manidipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Manidipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09239</drugbank-id>
      <name>Niguldipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Niguldipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09240</drugbank-id>
      <name>Niludipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Niludipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11960</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carboxyamidotriazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Carboxyamidotriazole is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12092</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naftopidil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Naftopidil is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12093</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetrahydropalmatine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Tetrahydropalmatine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12131</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vinpocetine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Vinpocetine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12923</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gallopamil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Gallopamil is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13488</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bencyclane</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Bencyclane is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13500</drugbank-id>
      <name>Otilonium</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Otilonium is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13725</drugbank-id>
      <name>Terodiline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Terodiline is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13766</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lidoflazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Lidoflazine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13791</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penfluridol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Penfluridol is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13835</drugbank-id>
      <name>Caroverine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Caroverine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13950</drugbank-id>
      <name>WIN 55212-2</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when WIN 55212-2 is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13961</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fish oil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Fish oil is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14063</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexverapamil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Dexverapamil is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14064</drugbank-id>
      <name>Emopamil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Emopamil is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14065</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lomerizine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Lomerizine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14066</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetrandrine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Tetrandrine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14068</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexniguldipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of hypotension can be increased when Dexniguldipine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00630</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alendronic acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Alendronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00710</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibandronate</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ibandronate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00720</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clodronic acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Clodronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00884</drugbank-id>
      <name>Risedronic acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Risedronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01077</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etidronic acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Etidronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01133</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiludronic acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Tiludronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06255</drugbank-id>
      <name>Incadronic acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Incadronic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02369</drugbank-id>
      <name>3-Aza-2,3-Dihydrogeranyl Diphosphate</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of 3-Aza-2,3-Dihydrogeranyl Diphosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02423</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiopyrophosphate</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Thiopyrophosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02552</drugbank-id>
      <name>Geranyl Diphosphate</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Geranyl Diphosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04160</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pyrophosphoric acid</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pyrophosphoric acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05143</drugbank-id>
      <name>OXI-4503</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07841</drugbank-id>
      <name>Geranylgeranyl diphosphate</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Geranylgeranyl diphosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09147</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric pyrophosphate</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferric pyrophosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09413</drugbank-id>
      <name>Monopotassium phosphate</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Monopotassium phosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09414</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dipotassium phosphate</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dipotassium phosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09449</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium phosphate, monobasic</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sodium phosphate, monobasic resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11348</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium Phosphate</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Calcium Phosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11493</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium tripolyphosphate</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sodium tripolyphosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14481</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium phosphate dihydrate</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Calcium phosphate dihydrate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14523</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phosphate ion</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Phosphate ion resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00091</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclosporine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Cyclosporine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00314</drugbank-id>
      <name>Capreomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Capreomycin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00319</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piperacillin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Piperacillin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00452</drugbank-id>
      <name>Framycetin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Framycetin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00468</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Quinine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00512</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vancomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Vancomycin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00560</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tigecycline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Tigecycline is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00608</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chloroquine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Chloroquine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00684</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tobramycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Tobramycin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00798</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gentamicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Gentamicin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00903</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etacrynic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Etacrynic acid is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00908</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinidine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Quinidine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00955</drugbank-id>
      <name>Netilmicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Netilmicin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00994</drugbank-id>
      <name>Neomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Neomycin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01035</drugbank-id>
      <name>Procainamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Procainamide is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01082</drugbank-id>
      <name>Streptomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Streptomycin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01111</drugbank-id>
      <name>Colistimethate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Colistimethate is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01172</drugbank-id>
      <name>Kanamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Kanamycin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01190</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clindamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Clindamycin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01219</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dantrolene</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Dantrolene is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01301</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rolitetracycline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Rolitetracycline is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01377</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium oxide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Magnesium oxide is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01378</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium cation</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Magnesium cation is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01421</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paromomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Paromomycin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01627</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lincomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Lincomycin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ribostamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Ribostamycin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04263</drugbank-id>
      <name>Geneticin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Geneticin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04626</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apramycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Apramycin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04729</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gentamicin C1a</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Gentamicin C1a is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04808</drugbank-id>
      <name>Neamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Neamine is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06696</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arbekacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Arbekacin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06827</drugbank-id>
      <name>Viomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Viomycin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08437</drugbank-id>
      <name>Puromycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Puromycin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09104</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium hydroxide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Magnesium hydroxide is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09281</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium trisilicate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Magnesium trisilicate is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09407</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium chloride</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Magnesium chloride is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09409</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium acetate tetrahydrate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Magnesium acetate tetrahydrate is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09481</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium carbonate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Magnesium carbonate is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11110</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium citrate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Magnesium citrate is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11189</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium glycinate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Magnesium glycinate is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11230</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium Aluminum Silicate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Magnesium Aluminum Silicate is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11512</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dihydrostreptomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Dihydrostreptomycin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11520</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hygromycin B</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Hygromycin B is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12604</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sisomicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Sisomicin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Plazomicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Plazomicin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13249</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium silicate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Magnesium silicate is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13270</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dibekacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Dibekacin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13274</drugbank-id>
      <name>Micronomicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Micronomicin is combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13540</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isepamicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Magnesium aspartate is combined with Isepamicin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13673</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bekanamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Magnesium aspartate is combined with Bekanamycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13749</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium gluconate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Magnesium aspartate is combined with Magnesium gluconate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13786</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium orotate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Magnesium aspartate is combined with Magnesium orotate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13862</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium phosphate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Magnesium aspartate is combined with Magnesium phosphate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13996</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium acetate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of neuromuscular blockade can be increased when Magnesium aspartate is combined with Magnesium acetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00042</drugbank-id>
      <name>Botulinum Toxin Type B</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium aspartate is combined with Botulinum Toxin Type B.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00083</drugbank-id>
      <name>Botulinum toxin type A</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium aspartate is combined with Botulinum toxin type A.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00184</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nicotine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium aspartate is combined with Nicotine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00657</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mecamylamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium aspartate is combined with Mecamylamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01090</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentolinium</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium aspartate is combined with Pentolinium.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01116</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimethaphan</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium aspartate is combined with Trimethaphan.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01199</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tubocurarine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium aspartate is combined with Tubocurarine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08837</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetraethylammonium</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium aspartate is combined with Tetraethylammonium.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08960</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hexamethonium</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium aspartate is combined with Hexamethonium.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08999</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclopentamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium aspartate is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00254</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxycycline</name>
      <description>The absorption of Doxycycline can be decreased when combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01155</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemifloxacin</name>
      <description>The absorption of Gemifloxacin can be decreased when combined with Magnesium aspartate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00252</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenytoin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Phenytoin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00532</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mephenytoin</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Mephenytoin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00564</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbamazepine</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Carbamazepine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00849</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylphenobarbital</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Methylphenobarbital resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01174</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenobarbital</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Phenobarbital resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01609</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deferasirox</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Deferasirox resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01071</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mequitazine</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Mequitazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347911448</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Wikipedia</resource>
      <identifier>Magnesium_aspartate</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>