<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2007-11-18" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05718</drugbank-id>
  <name>Maxy-G34</name>
  <description>MAXY-G34 is a pegylated variant of human granulocyte-colony stimulating factor (G-CSF). This variant contains multiple non-naturally occurring lysines that have been introduced into alpha helixes of wild type human G-CSF as PEGylation sites, and from which multiple undesired, naturally occurring lysines have been removed as compared to wild type human G-CSF to avoid PEGylation of such sites. Specifically, the amino acid sequence of MAXY-G34 differs from that of human wild type G-CSF at residues 16, 34, 40, 105 and 159. This was accomplished by removing the three lysine residues at positions 16, 34 and 40, and replacing them with arginine, and substituting two new lysine residues at positions 105 and 159. MAXY-G34 is pegylated with 5 kd mPEG SPA (succinimidyl propionate) groups at 3 amino acid residues, including PEG groups attached at the amino terminal end of the protein and at two internal lysine residues, while Neulasta has a single 20 Kd PEG group attached at the N terminal end of the wild type G-CSF protein. It is being developed by Maxygen, Inc. for the treatment of chemotherapy-induced neutropenia.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>liquid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in adverse effects (chemotherapy) and neutropenics.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>Maxy-G34 is a PEGylated proprietary G-CSF variant designed to be administered as a single subcutaneous injection once per chemotherapy cycle. Maxygen has made changes in the G-CSF gene sequence that code for novel PEGylation sites in the resulting protein. In contrast to the currently marketed PEGylated G-CSF, Maxy-G34 has multiple PEG groups attached at specifically selected sites on the molecule. In several in vivo models, Maxy- G34 has demonstratedimproved pharmacokinetics and pharmacodynamics compared to the currently marketed PEGylated G-CSF.</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>Neutropenia is a severe decrease in neutrophil cell counts in the blood. Neutropenia is a common side effect of chemotherapeutic treatments for many forms of cancer, including breast cancer, lung cancer, lymphomas and leukemias. Neutropenic patients contract bacterial infections more easily and often, some of which can be life threatening. Further, and most importantly, neutropenic patients may receive reduced or delayed chemotherapy treatment, which can result in cancer progression. Maxy-G34, like natural G-CSF is a protein that stimulates the body's bone marrow to produce neutrophils, a specific type of white blood cell that plays an important role in the defense against bacterial infections.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Alcohols</category>
      <mesh-id>D000438</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Proteins</category>
      <mesh-id>D000602</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Biological Factors</category>
      <mesh-id>D001685</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Carbohydrates</category>
      <mesh-id>D002241</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Colony-Stimulating Factors</category>
      <mesh-id>D003115</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Compounds used in a research, industrial, or household setting</category>
      <mesh-id>D020313</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Cytokines</category>
      <mesh-id>D016207</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Ethylene Glycols</category>
      <mesh-id>D005026</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Glycoconjugates</category>
      <mesh-id>D006001</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Glycols</category>
      <mesh-id>D006018</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Glycoproteins</category>
      <mesh-id>D006023</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Hematopoietic Cell Growth Factors</category>
      <mesh-id>D016298</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Intercellular Signaling Peptides and Proteins</category>
      <mesh-id>D036341</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Macromolecular Substances</category>
      <mesh-id>D046911</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Peptides</category>
      <mesh-id>D010455</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Polymers</category>
      <mesh-id>D011108</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Proteins</category>
      <mesh-id>D011506</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Recombinant Proteins</category>
      <mesh-id>D011994</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00531</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclophosphamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of pulmonary toxicity can be increased when Maxy-G34 is combined with Cyclophosphamide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00309</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vindesine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of peripheral neuropathy can be increased when Maxy-G34 is combined with Vindesine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00361</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vinorelbine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of peripheral neuropathy can be increased when Maxy-G34 is combined with Vinorelbine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00541</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vincristine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of peripheral neuropathy can be increased when Maxy-G34 is combined with Vincristine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00570</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vinblastine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of peripheral neuropathy can be increased when Maxy-G34 is combined with Vinblastine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05168</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vintafolide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of peripheral neuropathy can be increased when Maxy-G34 is combined with Vintafolide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11641</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vinflunine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of peripheral neuropathy can be increased when Maxy-G34 is combined with Vinflunine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13374</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vincamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of peripheral neuropathy can be increased when Maxy-G34 is combined with Vincamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910196</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>