<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2007-11-18" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05368</drugbank-id>
  <name>Ragweed pollen extract</name>
  <description>Ragweed pollen extract has been developed by Curalogic. The company has initiated a phase III trial with its product for oral immunotherapy of ragweed allergy. While traditional disease-modifying immunotherapeutics are administered by subcutaneous injection, Curalogic has developed a more convenient orally administered drug.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3407</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>8760779</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Litwin A, Flanagan M, Entis G, Gottschlich G, Esch R, Gartside P, Michael JG: Immunologic effects of encapsulated short ragweed extract: a potent new agent for oral immunotherapy. Ann Allergy Asthma Immunol. 1996 Aug;77(2):132-8.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3408</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>12811019</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Andre C, Perrin-Fayolle M, Grosclaude M, Couturier P, Basset D, Cornillon J, Piperno D, Girodet B, Sanchez R, Vallon C, Bellier P, Nasr M: A double-blind placebo-controlled evaluation of sublingual immunotherapy with a standardized ragweed extract in patients with seasonal rhinitis. Evidence for a dose-response relationship. Int Arch Allergy Immunol. 2003 Jun;131(2):111-8.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in allergic reaction.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>Ragweed pollen extract is the oral immunotherapy delivered via microencapsulated beads put into a capsule, which "enables the antigen to be delivered more efficiently to the Peyer's patches in the jejunum and duodenum, where the antigen can be presented and processed and not destroyed by stomach acid.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Ragwitek</name>
      <company>Merck Sharp &amp; Dohme</company>
    </international-brand>
  </international-brands>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910104</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>