<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2015-11-30" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB09397</drugbank-id>
  <name>Technetium Tc-99m sulfur colloid</name>
  <description>Technetium 99m sulfur colloid is a radiopharmaceutical diagnostic agent used in the evaluation of various conditions including lymph node metastases in breast cancer, detection of shunt patency, imaging of reticuloendothelial cells for assessment of liver function, and studies of esophageal transit and gastroesophageal reflux.  Following injection or oral administration, single photon emission computer tomography (SPECT) imaging is performed using a gamma camera to detect technetium-99m decay. This is possible as Technetium-99m decays by isomeric transition to technetium-99 through the release of a gamma ray. Depending on site of administration and intended usage, Technetium 99m sulfur colloid enters the capillaries and is transported to the lymph nodes (subcutaneous injection), mixes with peritoneal fluid (intraperitoneal injection), is taken up by reticulocytes (intravenous injection), or enters the gastroesphageal tract (oral administration).</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii>556Q0P6PB1</unii>
  <average-mass>355.39</average-mass>
  <monoisotopic-mass>354.682823946</monoisotopic-mass>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A18573</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>26822231</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Giovinazzo H, Kumar P, Sheikh A, Brooks KM, Ivanovic M, Walsh M, Caron WP, Kowalsky RJ, Song G, Whitlow A, Clarke-Pearson DL, Brewster WR, Van Le L, Zamboni BA, Bae-Jump V, Gehrig PA, Zamboni WC: Technetium Tc 99m sulfur colloid phenotypic probe for the pharmacokinetics and pharmacodynamics of PEGylated liposomal doxorubicin in women with ovarian cancer. Cancer Chemother Pharmacol. 2016 Mar;77(3):565-73. doi: 10.1007/s00280-015-2945-y. Epub 2016 Jan 28.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A18574</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>2947769</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Shih WJ, Domstad PA, Friedman B, DeLand FH: Intrathoracic abnormalities demonstrated by technetium-99m sulfur colloid imaging. Clin Nucl Med. 1986 Nov;11(11):792-6.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A18575</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>27349530</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Bowen SR, Chapman TR, Borgman J, Miyaoka RS, Kinahan PE, Liou IW, Sandison GA, Vesselle HJ, Nyflot MJ, Apisarnthanarax S: Measuring total liver function on sulfur colloid SPECT/CT for improved risk stratification and outcome prediction of hepatocellular carcinoma patients. EJNMMI Res. 2016 Dec;6(1):57. doi: 10.1186/s13550-016-0212-9. Epub 2016 Jun 27.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A18576</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>12927917</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Zuckerman E, Slobodin G, Sabo E, Yeshurun D, Naschitz JE, Groshar D: Quantitative liver-spleen scan using single photon emission computerized tomography (SPECT) for assessment of hepatic function in cirrhotic patients. J Hepatol. 2003 Sep;39(3):326-32.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Technetium 99m sulfur colloid is indicated as a diagnostic agent in adults for the following tests: localization of lymph nodes draining a primary tumor in patients with breast cancer or malignant melanoma; and evaluation of peritoneo-venous (LeVeen) shunt patency. It is indicated in both adult and pediatric patients for: imaging areas of functioning reticuloendothelial cells in the liver, spleen and bone marrow; and studies of esophageal transit and gastroesophageal reflux, and detection of pulmonary aspiration of gastric contents.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>Following injection or oral administration, single photon emission computer tomography (SPECT) imaging is performed using a gamma camera to detect technetium-99m decay. This is possible as Technetium-99m decays by isomeric transition to technetium-99 through the release of a gamma ray. </mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity>The most frequently reported adverse reactions, across all categories of use and routes of administration, include rash, allergic reaction, urticaria, anaphylaxis/anaphylactic shock, and hypotension. Less frequently reported adverse reactions are fatal cardiopulmonary arrest, seizures, dyspnea, bronchospasm, abdominal pain, flushing, nausea, vomiting, itching, fever, chills, perspiration, numbness, and dizziness. Local injection site reactions, including burning, blanching, erythema, sclerosis, swelling, eschar, and scarring, have also been reported. Anaphylactic reactions including rare fatalities have occurred following intravenously administered Technetium Tc 99m Sulfur Colloid. &#13;
Radiation-emitting products, including Technetium Tc 99m Sulfur Colloid Injection, may increase the risk for cancer, especially in pediatric patients. Use the smallest dose necessary for imaging and ensure safe handling to protect the patient and health care worker.</toxicity>
  <metabolism>In the average patient 80 to 90% of the injected collodial particles are phagocytized by the Kupffer cells of the liver, 5 to 10% by the spleen and the balance by the bone marrow.</metabolism>
  <absorption>When administered subcutaneously, Technetium Tc 99m Sulfur Colloid enters the lymphatic capillaries and is transported with lymph to lymph nodes where it can be used to detect drainage of primary tumours. &#13;
When administered by intraperitoneal injection, Technetium Tc 99m Sulfur Colloid mixes with the peritoneal fluid where the rate of clearance from the cavity allows assessment of shunt patency.&#13;
When administered by intravenous injection, Technetium Tc 99m Sulfur Colloid is taken up by the reticuloendothelial system (RES), allowing RES rich structures to be imaged. Uptake of the radioactive colloid by organs of the RES is dependent upon both their relative blood flow rates and the functional capacity of the phagocytic cells.&#13;
When administered orally, Technetium Tc 99m sulfur colloid can be used in esophageal transit studies, gastroesophageal reflux scintigraphy, and for the detection of pulmonary aspiration of gastric contents. This is possible as the active substance is not absorbed from the GI tract. </absorption>
  <half-life>Technetium Tc 99m decays by isomeric transition with a physical half-life of 6.02 hours. Following intravenous administration, Technetium Tc 99m Sulfur Colloid Injection is rapidly cleared from the blood by the reticuloendothelial system with a nominal half-life of approximately 2 1/2 minutes.</half-life>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination>Following oral ingestion, elimination is primarily through the feces. </route-of-elimination>
  <volume-of-distribution>Following oral ingestion, Technetium Tc 99m Sulfur Colloid is distributed primarily through the gastrointestinal tract.</volume-of-distribution>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description>This compound belongs to the class of organic compounds known as organic transition metal salts. These are organic salt compounds containing a transition metal atom in its ionic form.</description>
    <direct-parent>Organic transition metal salts</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic salts</superclass>
    <class>Organic metal salts</class>
    <subclass>Organic transition metal salts</subclass>
    <substituent>Organic transition metal salt</substituent>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Technetium (99mTc) sulfur colloid</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Technetium 99m sulfur colloid</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Technetium Tc 99m sulfur colloid</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Technetium Tc-99m Sulfur Colloid</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>Kit for the Prepartion of Technetium Tc99m Sulfur Colloid</name>
      <labeller>Pharmalucence Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>45567-0030</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1978-04-19</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Kit</dosage-form>
      <strength>18.1 mg/10mL</strength>
      <route>Intravenous; Oral; Subcutaneous</route>
      <fda-application-number>NDA017858</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>Kit for the Prepartion of Technetium Tc99m Sulfur Colloid</name>
      <ingredients>Technetium Tc-99m sulfur colloid</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Compounds used in a research, industrial, or household setting</category>
      <mesh-id>D020313</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Diagnostic Radiopharmaceuticals</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Diagnostic Uses of Chemicals</category>
      <mesh-id>D064907</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Hepatic and Reticulo Endothelial System</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Indicators and Reagents</category>
      <mesh-id>D007202</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Laboratory Chemicals</category>
      <mesh-id>D019995</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Radioactive Diagnostic Agent</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Radiopharmaceutical Activity</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Radiopharmaceuticals</category>
      <mesh-id>D019275</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Sulfur Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D013457</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Technetium (99Mtc), Particles and Colloids</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Technetium Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D017556</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Kit</form>
      <route>Intravenous; Oral; Subcutaneous</route>
      <strength>18.1 mg/10mL</strength>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes>
    <atc-code code="V09DB05">
      <level code="V09DB">Technetium (99mTc), particles and colloids</level>
      <level code="V09D">HEPATIC AND RETICULO ENDOTHELIAL SYSTEM</level>
      <level code="V09">DIAGNOSTIC RADIOPHARMACEUTICALS</level>
      <level code="V">VARIOUS</level>
    </atc-code>
  </atc-codes>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <fda-label>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/fda_labels/DB09397.pdf?1473782147</fda-label>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <calculated-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>0.82</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logS</kind>
      <value>-2.6</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Water Solubility</kind>
      <value>6.08e-01 g/l</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>4.76</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>octathiocane (99Tc)technetium</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Traditional IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>cyclooctasulfur (99Tc)technetium</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Weight</kind>
      <value>355.39</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Monoisotopic Weight</kind>
      <value>354.682823946</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>SMILES</kind>
      <value>[99Tc].S1SSSSSSS1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Formula</kind>
      <value>S8Tc</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChI</kind>
      <value>InChI=1S/S8.Tc/c1-2-4-6-8-7-5-3-1;/i;1+2</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChIKey</kind>
      <value>FJTPHHNWVXNMEK-NLQOEHMXSA-N</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polar Surface Area (PSA)</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Refractivity</kind>
      <value>46.05</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polarizability</kind>
      <value>20.4</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rotatable Bond Count</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Acceptor Count</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Donor Count</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Physiological Charge</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Number of Rings</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Bioavailability</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rule of Five</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Ghose Filter</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>MDDR-Like Rule</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
  </calculated-properties>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Compound</resource>
      <identifier>76957057</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347827842</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>KEGG Drug</resource>
      <identifier>D06048</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEMBL</resource>
      <identifier>CHEMBL1201529</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>