<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2017-09-08" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB13905</drugbank-id>
  <name>Scorpion (centruroides) immune Fab2 antivenin (equine)</name>
  <description>Centruroides (scorpion) Immune F(ab')2 (equine) is a purified preparation of immune globulin F(ab’)2 fragments that are derived from plasma of the horses immunized with venom of *C. noxius*, *C. l. limpidus*, *C. l. tecomanus*, and *C. s. suffusus*. It is intravenously administered patients with clinical signs of scorpion envenomation so that the Fab fragments bind to the toxins and limit systemic toxicity. It was approved by FDA in 2011 and is marketed under the name Anascorp [L2196].&#13;
&#13;
Anascorp is produced from equine IgG antibodies. Because initial development and use of this product in Mexico, venoms from several Centruroides species endemic to Mexico are pooled and diluted [L2207].&#13;
&#13;
This drug is a polyvalent antivenin proven to be useful against scorpion stings.&#13;
It is the first specific treatment to neutralize toxin from Centruroides scorpion stings, particularly those of the _Centruroides sculpturatus_ in the United States [L2206].&#13;
&#13;
Envenomation by a scorpion sting can result in serious cardiovascular effects [A32483].&#13;
Severe scorpion stings may cause loss of muscle control and respiratory failure, warranting heavy sedation and hospitalization in an intensive care unit. Most commonly, children experience severe reactions, however, adults can be affected, too [L2195], [L2196], [L2198].</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii>DDA050FCEA</unii>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A32482</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25506567</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Sanaei-Zadeh H: Hypersensitivity reaction to scorpion antivenom. Indian Dermatol Online J. 2014 Nov;5(Suppl 1):S51-2. doi: 10.4103/2229-5178.144536.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A32483</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>21209062</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Bawaskar HS, Bawaskar PH: Efficacy and safety of scorpion antivenom plus prazosin compared with prazosin alone for venomous scorpion (Mesobuthus tamulus) sting: randomised open label clinical trial. BMJ. 2011 Jan 5;342:c7136.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L2195</ref-id>
        <title>Antidote Relieves Scorpion Stings</title>
        <url>https://www.fda.gov/ForConsumers/ConsumerUpdates/ucm266515.htm</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L2196</ref-id>
        <title>Anascorp</title>
        <url>https://www.drugs.com/history/anascorp.html</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L2197</ref-id>
        <title>Scorpion antivenin approved</title>
        <url>http://www.ajhp.org/content/68/18/1668.1?sso-checked=true</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L2198</ref-id>
        <title>FDA Approves First-Ever Antivenom for Scorpion Stings</title>
        <url>https://www.medscape.com/viewarticle/747536</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L2199</ref-id>
        <title>Efficacy and safety of scorpion antivenom plus prazosin compared with prazosin alone for venomous scorpion (Mesobuthus tamulus) sting: randomised open label clinical trial</title>
        <url>https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3016167/</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L2200</ref-id>
        <title>Management of scorpion envenoming: a systematic review and meta-analysis of controlled clinical trials</title>
        <url>https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC5385045/</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L2201</ref-id>
        <title>Emerging options for the management of scorpion stings</title>
        <url>https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3401053/</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L2203</ref-id>
        <title>Hypersensitivity reaction to scorpion antivenom</title>
        <url>https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4252954/</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L2204</ref-id>
        <title>Adverse reactions to snake antivenom, and their prevention and treatment</title>
        <url>https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4767202/</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L2205</ref-id>
        <title>Centruroides (Scorpion) Immune F(ab′)2 (Equine)</title>
        <url>https://www.drugs.com/monograph/centruroides-scorpion-immune-f-ab-8242-2-equine.html</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L2206</ref-id>
        <title>PDR drug reference</title>
        <url>http://www.pdr.net/drug-summary/Anascorp-centruroides--scorpion--immune-F-ab--39--2--equine--1483</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L2207</ref-id>
        <title>Utah poison control</title>
        <url>https://poisoncontrol.utah.edu/newsletters/pdfs/toxicology-today-archive/Vol14_Iss3.pdf</url>
      </link>
    </links>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Indicated for treatment of clinical signs of scorpion envenomation [L2195], [L2196].</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>In 2008, 15 522 scorpion envenomations were reported to the National Poison Data System in the USA, with one fatality ocurring in a toddler. In the United States, Centruroides _sculpturatus_, commonly known as the Arizona bark scorpion, is the only scorpion species whose venom is toxic to humans.  Though most _Centruroides_ scorpion stings in adults are well-tolerated with minimal effects, pediatric patients are quite susceptible to signicant morbidity from the venom [L2207].&#13;
&#13;
In a pharmacokinetic study of 1534 patients, 95-100% of the study group were relieved of systemic signs associated with scorpion envenomation in less than four hours after initiating Anascorp treatment. In the historical control database, only 3.1% of patients experienced relief of symptoms within 4 hours of hospital admission [FDA label].  Clinical manifestations of scorpion sting and envenomation include sweating, salivation, cool extremities, priapism, hypertension or hypotension, and tachycardia [L2201].&#13;
&#13;
In 1396/1534 patients, the average time from the start of Anascorp infusion to the resolution of clinical signs and symptoms of envenomation was 1.42 hours (0.2 to 20.5 hours). Pediatric patients were found to experience a slightly faster time to resolution (1.28 ± 0.8 hours) compared to that of adult patients (1.91 ±1.4 hours). The time to resolution of symptoms was not affected by use of sedatives (474 patients who received sedatives resolved in 1.49 ± 1.1 hours and 922 patients who did not receive sedatives resolved in 1.38 ± 0.9 hours) [FDA label].</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>Anascorp, the trade name of this drug, is composed of venom-specific F(ab’)2 fragments of immunoglobulin G (IgG) that bind to and neutralize venom toxins, promoting redistribution away from target tissues and subsequent elimination from the body [FDA label].</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity>The most common adverse reactions observed in ≥ 2% of patients in the clinical studies for Anascorp were: vomiting, pyrexia, rash, nausea, and pruritus [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
Severe hypersensitivity reactions, including anaphylaxis, may occur with Anascorp [L2203], [FDA label]. Diligent patient monitoring for hypersensitivity reactions and preparation for intravenous therapy using epinephrine, corticosteroids, and diphenhydramine hydrochloride is recommended during the infusion. If an anaphylactic reaction occurs during the Anascorp infusion, case administration immediately, and administer warranted emergency medical care [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
Patients with existing allergies to horse protein are at a higher risk for developing anaphylactic reactions. Patients who have had previous therapy with Anascorp or another equine antivenom/antitoxin may have become sensitized to equine proteins and be at an elevated risk for a severe hypersensitivity reaction [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
Trace amounts of cresol from the manufacturing process are contained in Anascorp. Localized reactions and generalized myalgias have been observed with the use of cresol as an injectable excipient [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
Monitor patients with follow-up visit(s) for signs and symptoms of delayed allergic reactions or serum sickness (symptoms include rash, fever, myalgia, arthralgia), and treat appropriately if necessary. Eight out of 1,534 (0.5%) patients in the clinical trials exhibited symptoms suggestive of serum sickness [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
Anascorp is created from equine (horse) plasma, it may carry a risk of transmitting infectious agents, e.g., viruses [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
The following adverse reactions have been identified during post-approval use of Anascorp: chest tightness, palpitations, rash, and pruritus.  Because these reactions are reported voluntarily from a population of uncertain size, it is not always possible to reliably estimate their frequency or establish a causal relationship to drug exposure [FDA label].</toxicity>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life>&#13;
&#13;
159 ± 57 h [FDA label].</half-life>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution>Steady state: 13.6 ± 5.4 L [FDA label].</volume-of-distribution>
  <clearance>83.5 ± 38.4 ml/Hr [FDA label]</clearance>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Antivenin, scorpion</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Antivenin,centruroides immune Fab2</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Centruroides (scorpion) Immune F(ab')2 (equine)</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Centruroides (scorpion) immune F(ab')2 (equine) injection</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Centruroides (scorpion) immune F(ab)2 intravenous (equine)</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Centruroides (scorpion) immune Fab2 (equine)</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Centruroides antivenin</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Centruroides antivenin (equine)</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Centruroides Fab2 antivenin (equine)</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Centruroides suffusus suffusus) (equine)</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Mexican scorpion (centruroides) Fab2 antivenin (equine)</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Polyvalent mexican scorpion antivenin (horse)</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Scorpion (centruroides) Fab2 immunoglobulin (equine)</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>Anascorp</name>
      <labeller>Rare Disease Therapeutics, Inc</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>66621-0150</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2011-08-03</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Injection, powder, lyophilized, for solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>3.8 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>BLA125335</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>Anascorp</name>
      <ingredients>Scorpion (centruroides) immune Fab2 antivenin (equine)</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Antivenin</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Passively Acquired Immunity</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Venom Neutralization</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Injection, powder, lyophilized, for solution</form>
      <route>Intravenous</route>
      <strength>3.8 mg/1mL</strength>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <fda-label>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/fda_labels/DB13905.pdf?1505420688</fda-label>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347911474</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>