<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2017-06-23" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB13829</drugbank-id>
  <name>Calcium silicate</name>
  <description/>
  <cas-number>1344-95-2</cas-number>
  <unii>S4255P4G5M</unii>
  <average-mass>230.288</average-mass>
  <monoisotopic-mass>229.9227111</monoisotopic-mass>
  <groups>
    <group>experimental</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication/>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action/>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description>This compound belongs to the class of inorganic compounds known as alkaline earth metal silicates. These are inorganic compounds in which the largest oxoanion is silicate, and in which the heaviest atom not in an oxoanion is an alkaline earth metal.</description>
    <direct-parent>Alkaline earth metal silicates</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Inorganic compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Mixed metal/non-metal compounds</superclass>
    <class>Alkaline earth metal oxoanionic compounds</class>
    <subclass>Alkaline earth metal silicates</subclass>
    <alternative-parent>Inorganic calcium salts</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Inorganic oxides</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Metalloid salts</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Miscellaneous silicates</alternative-parent>
    <substituent>Alkaline earth metal silicate</substituent>
    <substituent>Inorganic calcium salt</substituent>
    <substituent>Inorganic metalloid salt</substituent>
    <substituent>Inorganic oxide</substituent>
    <substituent>Inorganic salt</substituent>
    <substituent>Silicate</substituent>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Acids</category>
      <mesh-id>D000143</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Acids, Noncarboxylic</category>
      <mesh-id>D000148</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Alimentary Tract and Metabolism</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Anions</category>
      <mesh-id>D000838</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Antacids</category>
      <mesh-id>D000863</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Bone Substitutes</category>
      <mesh-id>D018786</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Calcium Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D017610</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Drugs for Acid Related Disorders</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Electrolytes</category>
      <mesh-id>D004573</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Gastric Acid Lowering Agents</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Ions</category>
      <mesh-id>D007477</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Minerals</category>
      <mesh-id>D008903</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Oxides</category>
      <mesh-id>D010087</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Oxygen Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D017601</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Silicon Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D017655</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes>
    <atc-code code="A02AC02">
      <level code="A02AC">Calcium compounds</level>
      <level code="A02A">ANTACIDS</level>
      <level code="A02">DRUGS FOR ACID RELATED DISORDERS</level>
      <level code="A">ALIMENTARY TRACT AND METABOLISM</level>
    </atc-code>
  </atc-codes>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06616</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bosutinib</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Bosutinib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01066</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefditoren</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Cefditoren can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06695</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dabigatran etexilate</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dabigatran etexilate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08912</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dabrafenib</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dabrafenib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01254</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dasatinib</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dasatinib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00530</drugbank-id>
      <name>Erlotinib</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Erlotinib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01167</drugbank-id>
      <name>Itraconazole</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Itraconazole resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09027</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ledipasvir</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ledipasvir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00422</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylphenidate</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause an increase in the absorption of Methylphenidate resulting in an increased serum concentration and potentially a worsening of adverse effects.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04868</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nilotinib</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Nilotinib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06589</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pazopanib</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pazopanib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08931</drugbank-id>
      <name>Riociguat</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Riociguat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08930</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dolutegravir</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dolutegravir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00451</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levothyroxine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Levothyroxine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01344</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolevamer</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tolevamer is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09020</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bisacodyl</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Bisacodyl can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00178</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ramipril</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ramipril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00492</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosinopril</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Fosinopril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00519</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trandolapril</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Trandolapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00542</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benazepril</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Benazepril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00584</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enalapril</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Enalapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00691</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moexipril</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Moexipril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00722</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lisinopril</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Lisinopril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00790</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perindopril</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Perindopril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00881</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinapril</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Quinapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00886</drugbank-id>
      <name>Omapatrilat</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Omapatrilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01180</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rescinnamine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rescinnamine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01197</drugbank-id>
      <name>Captopril</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Captopril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01340</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cilazapril</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Cilazapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01348</drugbank-id>
      <name>Spirapril</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Spirapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08836</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temocapril</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Temocapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imidapril</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Imidapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13166</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zofenopril</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Zofenopril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13312</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delapril</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Delapril resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14125</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benazeprilat</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Benazeprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14207</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosinoprilat</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Fosinoprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ramiprilat</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ramiprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14209</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trandolaprilat</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Trandolaprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14210</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moexiprilat</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Moexiprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perindoprilat</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Perindoprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14217</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinaprilat</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Quinaprilat resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14231</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinoline Yellow WS</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Quinoline Yellow WS resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01416</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefpodoxime</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Cefpodoxime can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00908</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinidine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate may decrease the excretion rate of Quinidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00437</drugbank-id>
      <name>Allopurinol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Allopurinol can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Raltegravir</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Raltegravir can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00688</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mycophenolate mofetil</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Mycophenolate mofetil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01024</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mycophenolic acid</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Mycophenolic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00847</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cysteamine</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Cysteamine can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01026</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketoconazole</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ketoconazole resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00372</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiethylperazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Thiethylperazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00420</drugbank-id>
      <name>Promazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Promazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00433</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prochlorperazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Prochlorperazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00477</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorpromazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Chlorpromazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00508</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triflupromazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Triflupromazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00623</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluphenazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Fluphenazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00679</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thioridazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Thioridazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00680</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moricizine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Moricizine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00831</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trifluoperazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Trifluoperazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00850</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perphenazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Perphenazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00933</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mesoridazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Mesoridazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01063</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetophenazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Acetophenazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01069</drugbank-id>
      <name>Promethazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Promethazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01246</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alimemazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Alimemazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01403</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methotrimeprazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Methotrimeprazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01608</drugbank-id>
      <name>Periciazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Periciazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01614</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acepromazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Acepromazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aceprometazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Aceprometazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01621</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pipotiazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pipotiazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01622</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thioproperazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Thioproperazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05687</drugbank-id>
      <name>BL-1020</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of BL-1020 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09000</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyamemazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Cyamemazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09241</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylene blue</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Methylene blue resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11540</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propiopromazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Propiopromazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12710</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Perazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Butaperazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Butaperazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13382</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorproethazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Chlorproethazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13420</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiazinam</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Thiazinam resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13784</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dixyrazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dixyrazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14651</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perphenazine enanthate</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Perphenazine enanthate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06799</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methenamine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Methenamine can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00254</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxycycline</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Doxycycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00256</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lymecycline</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Lymecycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00453</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clomocycline</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Clomocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxytetracycline</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Oxytetracycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00618</drugbank-id>
      <name>Demeclocycline</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Demeclocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00759</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetracycline</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Tetracycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00931</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metacycline</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Metacycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01017</drugbank-id>
      <name>Minocycline</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Minocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12035</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sarecycline</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sarecycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12455</drugbank-id>
      <name>Omadacycline</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Omadacycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13092</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meclocycline</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Meclocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penimepicycline</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Penimepicycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06824</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triethylenetetramine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Triethylenetetramine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01098</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rosuvastatin</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rosuvastatin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00282</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pamidronic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Pamidronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00399</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zoledronic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Zoledronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00630</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alendronic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Alendronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00710</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibandronate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ibandronate can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00720</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clodronic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Clodronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00884</drugbank-id>
      <name>Risedronic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Risedronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01077</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etidronic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Etidronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01133</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiludronic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tiludronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06255</drugbank-id>
      <name>Incadronic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Incadronic acid can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00443</drugbank-id>
      <name>Betamethasone</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Betamethasone can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00588</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluticasone propionate</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Fluticasone propionate can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00620</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triamcinolone</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Triamcinolone can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00635</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisone</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Prednisone can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00687</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fludrocortisone</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Fludrocortisone can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00741</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrocortisone</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Hydrocortisone can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00860</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisolone</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Prednisolone can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00959</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylprednisolone</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Methylprednisolone can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01108</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trilostane</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Trilostane can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01222</drugbank-id>
      <name>Budesonide</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Budesonide can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01234</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexamethasone</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Dexamethasone can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01380</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cortisone acetate</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Cortisone acetate can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01384</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paramethasone</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Paramethasone can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04630</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aldosterone</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Aldosterone can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08970</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluprednidene</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Fluprednidene can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08971</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluocortolone</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Fluocortolone can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09378</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluprednisolone</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Fluprednisolone can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09383</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meprednisone</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Meprednisone can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11487</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexamethasone isonicotinate</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Dexamethasone isonicotinate can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11529</drugbank-id>
      <name>Melengestrol</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Melengestrol can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11750</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clobetasol</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Clobetasol can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11921</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deflazacort</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Deflazacort can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13003</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cortivazol</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Cortivazol can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednylidene</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Prednylidene can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13223</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluocortin</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Fluocortin can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13491</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluperolone</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Fluperolone can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13664</drugbank-id>
      <name>Formocortal</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Formocortal can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13728</drugbank-id>
      <name>Halometasone</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Halometasone can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13843</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cloprednol</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Cloprednol can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13856</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluclorolone</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Fluclorolone can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13867</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluticasone</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Fluticasone can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14538</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrocortisone aceponate</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Hydrocortisone aceponate can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14541</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrocortisone cypionate</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Hydrocortisone cypionate can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00873</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loteprednol</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Loteprednol can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14631</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisolone phosphate</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Prednisolone phosphate can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14633</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisolone hemisuccinate</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Prednisolone hemisuccinate can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14634</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluprednidene acetate</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Fluprednidene acetate can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14643</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylprednisolone aceponate</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Methylprednisolone aceponate can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14646</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisone acetate</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Prednisone acetate can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14652</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clocortolone acetate</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Clocortolone acetate can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14659</drugbank-id>
      <name>Melengestrol acetate</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Melengestrol acetate can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14669</drugbank-id>
      <name>Betamethasone phosphate</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Betamethasone phosphate can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14681</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cortisone</name>
      <description>The bioavailability of Cortisone can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00182</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amphetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amphetamine can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00191</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phentermine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Phentermine can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00852</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pseudoephedrine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Pseudoephedrine can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00865</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benzphetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Benzphetamine can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00937</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diethylpropion</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Diethylpropion can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01255</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lisdexamfetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Lisdexamfetamine can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01365</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mephentermine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Mephentermine can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01442</drugbank-id>
      <name>MMDA</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of MMDA can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01454</drugbank-id>
      <name>Midomafetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Midomafetamine can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01467</drugbank-id>
      <name>2,5-Dimethoxy-4-ethylamphetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of 2,5-Dimethoxy-4-ethylamphetamine can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01484</drugbank-id>
      <name>4-Bromo-2,5-dimethoxyamphetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of 4-Bromo-2,5-dimethoxyamphetamine can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01509</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenamfetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tenamfetamine can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01556</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorphentermine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Chlorphentermine can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01566</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylenedioxyethamphetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Methylenedioxyethamphetamine can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01576</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dextroamphetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Dextroamphetamine can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01577</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metamfetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Metamfetamine can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09480</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iofetamine I-123</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Iofetamine I-123 can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12080</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ritobegron</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ritobegron can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13108</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mephedrone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Mephedrone can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13624</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methoxyphenamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Methoxyphenamine can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13703</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gepefrine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Gepefrine can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13940</drugbank-id>
      <name>2,5-Dimethoxy-4-ethylthioamphetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of 2,5-Dimethoxy-4-ethylthioamphetamine can be increased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00316</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetaminophen</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Acetaminophen resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09288</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propacetamol</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Propacetamol resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00653</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium sulfate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium sulfate can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01377</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium oxide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium oxide can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01378</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium cation</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium cation can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01638</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sorbitol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sorbitol can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09104</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium hydroxide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium hydroxide can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09281</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium trisilicate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium trisilicate can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09287</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polyethylene glycol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Polyethylene glycol can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09413</drugbank-id>
      <name>Monopotassium phosphate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Monopotassium phosphate can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09414</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dipotassium phosphate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Dipotassium phosphate can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09449</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium phosphate, monobasic</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sodium phosphate, monobasic can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09462</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glycerin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Glycerin can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09472</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium sulfate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sodium sulfate can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09481</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium carbonate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium carbonate can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09484</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium fluorophosphate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sodium fluorophosphate can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11110</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium citrate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium citrate can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11189</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium glycinate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium glycinate can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12942</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lactitol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Lactitol can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13486</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium peroxide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium peroxide can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13526</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentaerithrityl</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Pentaerithrityl can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13707</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium tartrate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sodium tartrate can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14482</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium ascorbate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sodium ascorbate can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14499</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium sulfate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Potassium sulfate can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14502</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium phosphate, dibasic</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sodium phosphate, dibasic can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14503</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium phosphate, monobasic, unspecified form</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sodium phosphate, monobasic, unspecified form can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14504</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium phosphate, dibasic, unspecified form</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sodium phosphate, dibasic, unspecified form can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14513</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00582</drugbank-id>
      <name>Voriconazole</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Voriconazole resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01110</drugbank-id>
      <name>Miconazole</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Miconazole resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01263</drugbank-id>
      <name>Posaconazole</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Posaconazole resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04794</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bifonazole</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Bifonazole resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06395</drugbank-id>
      <name>Abafungin</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Abafungin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06440</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ravuconazole</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ravuconazole resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06636</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isavuconazonium</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Isavuconazonium resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08943</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isoconazole</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Isoconazole resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11633</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isavuconazole</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Isavuconazole resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12073</drugbank-id>
      <name>Albaconazole</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Albaconazole resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13425</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flutrimazole</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Flutrimazole resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13434</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenticonazole</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Fenticonazole resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13684</drugbank-id>
      <name>Omoconazole</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Omoconazole resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00537</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ciprofloxacin</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ciprofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00220</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nelfinavir</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Nelfinavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00224</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indinavir</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Indinavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00503</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ritonavir</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ritonavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00701</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amprenavir</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Amprenavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00932</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tipranavir</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Tipranavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01232</drugbank-id>
      <name>Saquinavir</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Saquinavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Darunavir</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Darunavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01319</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosamprenavir</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Fosamprenavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01601</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lopinavir</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Lopinavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11586</drugbank-id>
      <name>Asunaprevir</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Asunaprevir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08864</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rilpivirine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rilpivirine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00581</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lactulose</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Lactulose can be decreased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09073</drugbank-id>
      <name>Palbociclib</name>
      <description>The absorption of Palbociclib can be decreased when combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06701</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexmethylphenidate</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dexmethylphenidate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12147</drugbank-id>
      <name>Erdafitinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Calcium silicate is combined with Erdafitinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00788</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naproxen</name>
      <description>Naproxen can cause a decrease in the absorption of Calcium silicate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01611</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydroxychloroquine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Hydroxychloroquine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01112</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefuroxime</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Cefuroxime can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00608</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chloroquine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Chloroquine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09101</drugbank-id>
      <name>Elvitegravir</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Elvitegravir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00996</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gabapentin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Gabapentin can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08872</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gabapentin enacarbil</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Gabapentin enacarbil can be decreased when it is combined with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00424</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hyoscyamine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Hyoscyamine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01045</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rifampicin</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rifampicin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00657</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mecamylamine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate may decrease the excretion rate of Mecamylamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01043</drugbank-id>
      <name>Memantine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate may decrease the excretion rate of Memantine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00859</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penicillamine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Penicillamine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00391</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulpiride</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sulpiride can be increased when used in combination with Calcium silicate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00244</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mesalazine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Mesalazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prussian blue</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Prussian blue resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09146</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iron sucrose</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Iron sucrose resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09501</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric ammonium citrate</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferric ammonium citrate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09507</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferumoxsil</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxsil resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09508</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferumoxides</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferumoxides resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11171</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric sulfate</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferric sulfate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11210</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous bisglycinate</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferrous bisglycinate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11417</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gleptoferron</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Gleptoferron resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iron isomaltoside 1000</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Iron isomaltoside 1000 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12821</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perflubutane</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Perflubutane resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13257</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous sulfate anhydrous</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferrous sulfate anhydrous resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13381</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium feredetate</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sodium feredetate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13423</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric hydroxide</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferric hydroxide resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13569</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous chloride</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferrous chloride resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13949</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric cation</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferric cation resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14488</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous gluconate</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferrous gluconate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14489</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous succinate</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferrous succinate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14491</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous fumarate</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferrous fumarate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14520</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetraferric tricitrate decahydrate</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Tetraferric tricitrate decahydrate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14695</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric oxyhydroxide</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferric oxyhydroxide resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00893</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iron Dextran</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Iron Dextran resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01592</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iron</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Iron resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09147</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric pyrophosphate</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferric pyrophosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00390</drugbank-id>
      <name>Digoxin</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate may increase the arrhythmogenic activities of Digoxin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13401</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metildigoxin</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate may increase the arrhythmogenic activities of Metildigoxin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13691</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetyldigoxin</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate may increase the arrhythmogenic activities of Acetyldigoxin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00705</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delavirdine</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Delavirdine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gefitinib</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Gefitinib resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01072</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atazanavir</name>
      <description>Calcium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of Atazanavir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <calculated-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>-0.77</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logS</kind>
      <value>-2.5</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Water Solubility</kind>
      <value>7.84e-01 g/l</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>-2.6</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>calcium ditrihydrogen silicate</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Traditional IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>calcium ditrihydrogen silicate</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Weight</kind>
      <value>230.288</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Monoisotopic Weight</kind>
      <value>229.9227111</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>SMILES</kind>
      <value>[Ca++].O[Si](O)(O)[O-].O[Si](O)(O)[O-]</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Formula</kind>
      <value>CaH6O8Si2</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChI</kind>
      <value>InChI=1S/Ca.2H3O4Si/c;2*1-5(2,3)4/h;2*1-3H/q+2;2*-1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChIKey</kind>
      <value>LECAAGVQUHQAJK-UHFFFAOYSA-N</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polar Surface Area (PSA)</kind>
      <value>83.75</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Refractivity</kind>
      <value>9.14</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polarizability</kind>
      <value>6.06</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rotatable Bond Count</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Acceptor Count</kind>
      <value>4</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Donor Count</kind>
      <value>3</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest acidic)</kind>
      <value>9.82</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest basic)</kind>
      <value>-4.8</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Physiological Charge</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Number of Rings</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Bioavailability</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rule of Five</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Ghose Filter</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>MDDR-Like Rule</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
  </calculated-properties>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChemSpider</resource>
      <identifier>32700984</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Wikipedia</resource>
      <identifier>Calcium_silicate</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>