<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2015-12-01" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB11051</drugbank-id>
  <drugbank-id>DB05348</drugbank-id>
  <name>Azficel-T</name>
  <description>Azficel-T is an autologous cellular product composed of fibroblasts indicated for improvement of the appearance of moderate to severe nasolabial fold wrinkles in adults. Dermal fibroblasts are collected from the post-auricular biopsy tissue and aseptically expanded using standard tissue-culture procedures until sufficient cells for three doses are obtained [FDA Label]. Expanded cells are then suspended in a cell medium. As a replacement for lost dermal constituents in the aging or skin deformation process, treatment with autologous fibroblasts has shown to improve wrinkle and acne scar appearance than with placebo treatment [A31920, A31926]. Intradermal administration of autologous dermal fibroblasts into irradiated skin following surgical procedures was associated with an improved healing process of subsequent surgical wounds [A31927]. Azficel-T is marketed in the US as Laviv for intradermal injection.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii>022461SR75</unii>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A31919</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>22409385</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Smith SR, Munavalli G, Weiss R, Maslowski JM, Hennegan KP, Novak JM: A multicenter, double-blind, placebo-controlled trial of autologous fibroblast therapy for the treatment of nasolabial fold wrinkles. Dermatol Surg. 2012 Jul;38(7 Pt 2):1234-43. doi: 10.1111/j.1524-4725.2012.02349.x. Epub 2012 Mar 12.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A31920</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>23566237</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Munavalli GS, Smith S, Maslowski JM, Weiss RA: Successful treatment of depressed, distensible acne scars using autologous fibroblasts: a multi-site, prospective, double blind, placebo-controlled clinical trial. Dermatol Surg. 2013 Aug;39(8):1226-36. doi: 10.1111/dsu.12204. Epub 2013 Apr 8.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A31921</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>18490597</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Fisher GJ, Varani J, Voorhees JJ: Looking older: fibroblast collapse and therapeutic implications. Arch Dermatol. 2008 May;144(5):666-72. doi: 10.1001/archderm.144.5.666.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A31926</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>22092878</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Eca LP, Pinto DG, de Pinho AM, Mazzetti MP, Odo ME: Autologous fibroblast culture in the repair of aging skin. Dermatol Surg. 2012 Feb;38(2):180-4. doi: 10.1111/j.1524-4725.2011.02192.x. Epub  2011 Oct 10.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A31927</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>10423337</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Ferguson PC, Boynton EL, Wunder JS, Hill RP, O'Sullivan B, Sandhu JS, Bell RS: Intradermal injection of autologous dermal fibroblasts improves wound healing in irradiated skin. J Surg Res. 1999 Aug;85(2):331-8. doi: 10.1006/jsre.1999.5664.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A31943</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>21526076</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Nilforoushzadeh MA, Siadat AH, Arianrad M, Moulavi F, Baradaran EH, Esfahani MH: Soft tissue augmentation by autologous cultured fibroblasts transplantation for treatment of wrinkles and scars: a case series of 20 patients. J Res Med Sci. 2010 May;15(3):167-71.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Indicated for improvement of the appearance of moderate to severe nasolabial fold wrinkles in adults [FDA Label].</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>In clinical studies involving patients with moderate to severe bilateral nasolabial fold wrinkles, there was a substantial improvement in the wrinkle appearance [FDA Label]. In a randomized multicenter, double-blind, placebo-controlled trial in subjects with bilateral moderate to severe acne scarring, treatment of autologous fibroblast treatment was associated with a significant improvement in the appearance of acne scars without permanent adverse reactions [A31920].</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>The mechanism of action of azficel-T, or autologous human fibroblasts, is not fully elucidated. Autologous fibroblasts correct dermal defects such as acne or other dermal conditions associated with aging, such as reduced elasticity. The importance of collagen matrix production by fibroblasts in maintaining skin integrity and reducing the appearance of scars has been highlighted. The appearance of acne scars is also associated with the loss of collagen at the site of inflammation following resolution of localized intense inflammation and wound healing associated with inflammatory acne [A31920]. Fragmentation of the dermal collagen matrix occurs in the natural aging process; due to UV-induced photodamage and the actions of collagen-degrading enzymes (matrix metalloproteinases, MMPs) overtime, the structural integrity of the dermis and function of fibroblasts may be impaired [A31921]. While fibroblasts are responsible in the synthesis, organization, regulation and the maintenance of collagen network, the function of fibroblasts are strongly dependent on the physical properties of collagen fibres, and vice versa [A31921]. The aging process is associated with a reduced rate of collagen turnover and formation of modified crosslinks that normally give structural support for collagen fibres. These crosslinks prevent the removal of degraded collagen, leading to accumulation of collagen fragments within the extracellular matrix, and compromised structural and mechanical integrity of the dermis [A31921]. Integrins that are expressed by the fibroblasts allow the cell to bind to collagen matrix and allow mechanical tension within fibroblasts and the collagenous matrix. In the presence of fragmented collagen, the fibroblasts lose attachment to the collagen matrix and collapse within the dermis and subsequently leads to reduced collagen production and increased production of MMPs [A31921]. Autologous human fibroblasts have the ability to increase the formation of human collagen _in vivo_ and promote remodelling of pre-existing extracellular matrix in the scarred tissue [A31920, A31943]. They may also decrease the degradation of collagen [A31943].</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity>The adverse reactions from azficel-T treatment tend to be limited to injection site reactions [FDA Label].</toxicity>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Autologous cultured fibroblasts</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>Laviv</name>
      <labeller>Fibrocell Technologies, Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>75935-001</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2011-07-15</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Injection, suspension</dosage-form>
      <strength>15000000 1/1mL</strength>
      <route>Intradermal</route>
      <fda-application-number>BLA125348</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>Laviv</name>
      <ingredients>Azficel-T</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Autologous Cultured Cell</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Injection, suspension</form>
      <route>Intradermal</route>
      <strength>15000000 1/1mL</strength>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <fda-label>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/fda_labels/DB11051.pdf?1519159947</fda-label>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00159</drugbank-id>
      <name>Icosapent</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Icosapent is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00244</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mesalazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Mesalazine is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00328</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indomethacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Indomethacin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00461</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nabumetone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Nabumetone is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00465</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketorolac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ketorolac is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00469</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenoxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tenoxicam is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00482</drugbank-id>
      <name>Celecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Celecoxib is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00500</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolmetin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tolmetin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00533</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rofecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Rofecoxib is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00554</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piroxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Piroxicam is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00573</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Fenoprofen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00580</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valdecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Valdecoxib is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00586</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diclofenac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Diclofenac is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00605</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulindac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulindac is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00712</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flurbiprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Flurbiprofen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00749</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etodolac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Etodolac is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00784</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mefenamic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Mefenamic acid is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00788</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naproxen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Naproxen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00795</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfasalazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfasalazine is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00812</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenylbutazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Phenylbutazone is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00814</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meloxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Meloxicam is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00821</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Carprofen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00861</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diflunisal</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Diflunisal is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00936</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salicylic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Salicylic acid is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00939</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meclofenamic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Meclofenamic acid is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00945</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetylsalicylic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Acetylsalicylic acid is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00991</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxaprozin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Oxaprozin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01009</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ketoprofen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01014</drugbank-id>
      <name>Balsalazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Balsalazide is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01050</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibuprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ibuprofen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01250</drugbank-id>
      <name>Olsalazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Olsalazine is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01283</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lumiracoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Lumiracoxib is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01397</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium salicylate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium salicylate is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01399</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salsalate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Salsalate is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01401</drugbank-id>
      <name>Choline magnesium trisalicylate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Choline magnesium trisalicylate is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01419</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antrafenine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Antrafenine is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01424</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aminophenazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Aminophenazone is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01435</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antipyrine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Antipyrine is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01600</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiaprofenic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tiaprofenic acid is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01628</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etoricoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Etoricoxib is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02224</drugbank-id>
      <name>Taxifolin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Taxifolin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03585</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxyphenbutazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Oxyphenbutazone is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04552</drugbank-id>
      <name>Niflumic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Niflumic acid is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04725</drugbank-id>
      <name>Licofelone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Licofelone is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04743</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nimesulide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Nimesulide is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04812</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benoxaprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Benoxaprofen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metamizole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Metamizole is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04828</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zomepirac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Zomepirac is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05095</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cimicoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Cimicoxib is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06725</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lornoxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Lornoxicam is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06736</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aceclofenac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Aceclofenac is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06737</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zaltoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Zaltoprofen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07402</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azapropazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Azapropazone is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07477</drugbank-id>
      <name>Felbinac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Felbinac is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08439</drugbank-id>
      <name>Parecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Parecoxib is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08797</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salicylamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Salicylamide is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08940</drugbank-id>
      <name>Kebuzone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Kebuzone is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08942</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isoxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Isoxicam is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08951</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Indoprofen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08955</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibuproxam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ibuproxam is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08976</drugbank-id>
      <name>Floctafenine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Floctafenine is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08981</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenbufen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Fenbufen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08984</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etofenamate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Etofenamate is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08991</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epirizole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Epirizole is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09084</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benzydamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Benzydamine is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09212</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loxoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Loxoprofen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexibuprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Dexibuprofen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09214</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexketoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Dexketoprofen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09215</drugbank-id>
      <name>Droxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Droxicam is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09216</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolfenamic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tolfenamic acid is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09217</drugbank-id>
      <name>Firocoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Firocoxib is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clonixin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Clonixin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09285</drugbank-id>
      <name>Morniflumate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Morniflumate is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09288</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propacetamol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Propacetamol is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09295</drugbank-id>
      <name>Talniflumate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Talniflumate is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11455</drugbank-id>
      <name>Robenacoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Robenacoxib is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11466</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tepoxalin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tepoxalin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11518</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flunixin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Flunixin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12399</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polmacoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Polmacoxib is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12445</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitroaspirin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Nitroaspirin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12480</drugbank-id>
      <name>Betulinic Acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Betulinic Acid is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12545</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indobufen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Indobufen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12610</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ebselen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ebselen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13001</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tinoridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tinoridine is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13167</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alclofenac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Alclofenac is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13217</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fentiazac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Fentiazac is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13232</drugbank-id>
      <name>Suxibuzone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Suxibuzone is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13286</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bumadizone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Bumadizone is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13314</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alminoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Alminoprofen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flunoxaprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Flunoxaprofen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13364</drugbank-id>
      <name>Feprazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Feprazone is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13371</drugbank-id>
      <name>Difenpiramide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Difenpiramide is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13407</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nifenazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Nifenazone is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13432</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lonazolac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Lonazolac is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13481</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenidap</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tenidap is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13501</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bendazac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Bendazac is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13514</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pranoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Pranoprofen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13524</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propyphenazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Propyphenazone is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13527</drugbank-id>
      <name>Proglumetacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Proglumetacin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13538</drugbank-id>
      <name>Guacetisal</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Guacetisal is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13544</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethenzamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ethenzamide is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13612</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbaspirin calcium</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Carbaspirin calcium is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13629</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mofebutazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Mofebutazone is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13649</drugbank-id>
      <name>Proquazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Proquazone is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13657</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benorilate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Benorilate is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13722</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pirprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Pirprofen is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acemetacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Acemetacin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13860</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imidazole salicylate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Imidazole salicylate is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14059</drugbank-id>
      <name>SC-236</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when SC-236 is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14060</drugbank-id>
      <name>NS-398</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when NS-398 is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14938</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flurbiprofen axetil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Flurbiprofen axetil is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00001</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lepirudin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Lepirudin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00006</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bivalirudin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Bivalirudin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00009</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alteplase</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Alteplase is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00013</drugbank-id>
      <name>Urokinase</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Urokinase is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00015</drugbank-id>
      <name>Reteplase</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Reteplase is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00029</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anistreplase</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Anistreplase is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00031</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenecteplase</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tenecteplase is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00054</drugbank-id>
      <name>Abciximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Abciximab is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00055</drugbank-id>
      <name>Drotrecogin alfa</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Drotrecogin alfa is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00086</drugbank-id>
      <name>Streptokinase</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Streptokinase is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00261</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anagrelide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Anagrelide is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00266</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dicoumarol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Dicoumarol is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00278</drugbank-id>
      <name>Argatroban</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Argatroban is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00407</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ardeparin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ardeparin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00498</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenindione</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Phenindione is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00569</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fondaparinux</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Fondaparinux is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00682</drugbank-id>
      <name>Warfarin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Warfarin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00686</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentosan polysulfate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Pentosan polysulfate is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00946</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenprocoumon</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Phenprocoumon is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00975</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dipyridamole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Dipyridamole is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01088</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iloprost</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Iloprost is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01109</drugbank-id>
      <name>Heparin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Heparin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01225</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enoxaparin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Enoxaparin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01240</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epoprostenol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Epoprostenol is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01418</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acenocoumarol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Acenocoumarol is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03410</drugbank-id>
      <name>4-hydroxycoumarin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when 4-hydroxycoumarin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04665</drugbank-id>
      <name>Coumarin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Coumarin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04898</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ximelagatran</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ximelagatran is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04925</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desmoteplase</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Desmoteplase is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04932</drugbank-id>
      <name>Defibrotide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Defibrotide is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05099</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ancrod</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ancrod is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05229</drugbank-id>
      <name>Beraprost</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Beraprost is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05254</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fibrinolysin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Fibrinolysin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06209</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prasugrel</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Prasugrel is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06228</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rivaroxaban</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Rivaroxaban is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06271</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulodexide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulodexide is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06294</drugbank-id>
      <name>Semuloparin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Semuloparin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06406</drugbank-id>
      <name>Idraparinux</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Idraparinux is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06441</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cangrelor</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Cangrelor is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06543</drugbank-id>
      <name>Astaxanthin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Astaxanthin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06605</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apixaban</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Apixaban is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06635</drugbank-id>
      <name>Otamixaban</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Otamixaban is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06679</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amediplase</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Amediplase is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06695</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dabigatran etexilate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Dabigatran etexilate is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06754</drugbank-id>
      <name>Danaparoid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Danaparoid is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06779</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dalteparin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Dalteparin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06822</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tinzaparin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tinzaparin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07767</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferulic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ferulic acid is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08496</drugbank-id>
      <name>(R)-warfarin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when (R)-warfarin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08794</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethyl biscoumacetate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ethyl biscoumacetate is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08813</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nadroparin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Nadroparin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08814</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triflusal</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Triflusal is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08816</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ticagrelor</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ticagrelor is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08994</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ditazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ditazole is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09030</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vorapaxar</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Vorapaxar is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09075</drugbank-id>
      <name>Edoxaban</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Edoxaban is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09125</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium citrate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Potassium citrate is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09154</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium citrate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sodium citrate is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09255</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dextran</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Dextran is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09258</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bemiparin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Bemiparin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09259</drugbank-id>
      <name>Reviparin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Reviparin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09260</drugbank-id>
      <name>Parnaparin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Parnaparin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09261</drugbank-id>
      <name>Certoparin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Certoparin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11095</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desirudin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Desirudin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11154</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zinc citrate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Zinc citrate is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11166</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antithrombin Alfa</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Antithrombin Alfa is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11312</drugbank-id>
      <name>Protein C</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Protein C is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11598</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antithrombin III human</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Antithrombin III human is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11984</drugbank-id>
      <name>Letaxaban</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Letaxaban is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12289</drugbank-id>
      <name>Darexaban</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Darexaban is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12364</drugbank-id>
      <name>Betrixaban</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Betrixaban is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12598</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nafamostat</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Nafamostat is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12726</drugbank-id>
      <name>Monteplase</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Monteplase is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12831</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gabexate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Gabexate is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13136</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluindione</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Fluindione is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13149</drugbank-id>
      <name>Protein S human</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Protein S human is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13199</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brinase</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Brinase is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13275</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clorindione</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Clorindione is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13347</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diphenadione</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Diphenadione is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13451</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tioclomarol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tioclomarol is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13616</drugbank-id>
      <name>Melagatran</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Melagatran is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13646</drugbank-id>
      <name>Saruplase</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Saruplase is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14055</drugbank-id>
      <name>(S)-Warfarin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when (S)-Warfarin is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14094</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tocopherylquinone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tocopherylquinone is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14598</drugbank-id>
      <name>Edetate calcium disodium anhydrous</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Edetate calcium disodium anhydrous is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14600</drugbank-id>
      <name>Edetate disodium anhydrous</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Edetate disodium anhydrous is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14726</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dabigatran</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Dabigatran is combined with Azficel-T.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347911094</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>