<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-10-21" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05113</drugbank-id>
  <name>105AD7</name>
  <description>105AD7 is a human monoclonal antibody that mimics the complement regulatory protein, CD55, overexpressed by many solid tumours including osteosarcoma. 105AD7 induced antitumour inflammatory responses in metastatic colorectal cancer patients. 105AD7 may be a suitable vaccine for treatment of this disease.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3235</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17121873</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Ullenhag GJ, Spendlove I, Watson NF, Indar AA, Dube M, Robins RA, Maxwell-Armstrong C, Scholefield JH, Durrant LG: A neoadjuvant/adjuvant randomized trial of colorectal cancer patients vaccinated with an anti-idiotypic antibody, 105AD7, mimicking CD55. Clin Cancer Res. 2006 Dec 15;12(24):7389-96. Epub 2006 Nov 22.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3236</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>15798769</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Pritchard-Jones K, Spendlove I, Wilton C, Whelan J, Weeden S, Lewis I, Hale J, Douglas C, Pagonis C, Campbell B, Alvarez P, Halbert G, Durrant LG: Immune responses to the 105AD7 human anti-idiotypic vaccine after intensive chemotherapy, for osteosarcoma. Br J Cancer. 2005 Apr 25;92(8):1358-65.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3237</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>12398121</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Maxwell-Armstrong C: Studies using the anti-idiotypic monoclonal antibody 105AD7 in patients with primary and advanced colorectal cancer. Ann R Coll Surg Engl. 2002 Sep;84(5):314-8.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3238</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>11384090</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Maxwell-Armstrong CA, Durrant LG, Buckley TJ, Scholefield JH, Robins RA, Fielding K, Monson JR, Guillou P, Calvert H, Carmichael J, Hardcastle JD: Randomized double-blind phase II survival study comparing immunization with the anti-idiotypic monoclonal antibody 105AD7 against placebo in advanced colorectal cancer. Br J Cancer. 2001 Jun 1;84(11):1443-6.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in colorectal cancer.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>105AD7 vaccine is a human anti-idiotype which mimics the antigen 791Tgp72. The mechanism of action of the vaccine has recently been clarified. The anti-idiotype is rapidly internalized on antigen presenting cells by Fc mediated endocytosis as both Fab and Ab complexed to alum are processed 1,000 fold less efficiently than whole Ab. Sequencing of the Ab have revealed that the CDR-H3 is hypermutated and contains HLA A1, A3 and A24, and HLA-DR1, 3 and 7 MHC binding motifs.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
105AD7 is an antibody-based vaccine that mimics a target (CD55) which is over-expressed in numerous cancers including those of the prostate, colon and pancreas.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Onyvax 105</name>
      <company/>
    </international-brand>
  </international-brands>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347909953</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>