<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-11-18" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05808</drugbank-id>
  <name>PI-88</name>
  <description>PI-88 is a mixture of highly sulfated, monophosphorylated mannose oligosaccharides, derived from the extracellular phosphomannan of the yeast Pichia (Hansenula) holstii, with potential antiangiogenic activity.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3804</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17967543</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Fairweather JK, Hammond E, Johnstone KD, Ferro V: Synthesis and heparanase inhibitory activity of sulfated mannooligosaccharides related to the antiangiogenic agent PI-88. Bioorg Med Chem. 2008 Jan 15;16(2):699-709. Epub 2007 Oct 18.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3805</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17000682</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Basche M, Gustafson DL, Holden SN, O'Bryant CL, Gore L, Witta S, Schultz MK, Morrow M, Levin A, Creese BR, Kangas M, Roberts K, Nguyen T, Davis K, Addison RS, Moore JC, Eckhardt SG: A phase I biological and pharmacologic study of the heparanase inhibitor PI-88 in patients with advanced solid tumors. Clin Cancer Res. 2006 Sep 15;12(18):5471-80.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in hepatocellular carcinoma, liver cancer, melanoma, and multiple myeloma.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>PI-88 retards the growth of primary tumours by inhibiting new blood vessel growth (angiogenesis) in two ways: Heparan sulfate mimicry causes inhibition of heparanase, which prevents the release of angiogenic growth factors from the extracellular matrix (ECM). Interaction with angiogenic growth factors VEGF (Vascular Endothelial Growth Factor), FGF-1 (Fibroblast Growth Factor -1) and FGF-2, reduces their functional activity. PI-88 binds with high (nanomolar) affinity to these growth factors. </mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Carbohydrates</category>
      <mesh-id>D002241</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Polysaccharides</category>
      <mesh-id>D011134</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910242</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>