<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2015-11-30" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB09493</drugbank-id>
  <name>Technetium Tc-99m red blood cells</name>
  <description>Technetium Tc-99m red blood cells is a radiopharmaceutical diagnostic agent that is intravenously administered to be used in blood pool imaging, including cardiac first pass and gated equilibrium imaging and for detection of sites of gastrointestinal bleeding. It is clinically useful in early detection and localization of bleeding sites, and preoperative diagnosis of hemangioma [A32178, A32179]. Autologous red blood cells are radiolabeled with sodium pertechnetate Tc 99m in the reaction vial. Radiolabeled red blood cells are re-injected intravenously into the patient for gamma scintigraphic imaging [FDA Label]. It is suggested that _in vitro_ labelling improves the heart-to-background ratio during imaging [A32181].</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii>D8L75GM22O</unii>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A32179</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>8674366</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Emslie JT, Zarnegar K, Siegel ME, Beart RW Jr: Technetium-99m-labeled red blood cell scans in the investigation of gastrointestinal bleeding. Dis Colon Rectum. 1996 Jul;39(7):750-4.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A32181</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>1992026</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Patrick ST, Glowniak JV, Turner FE, Robbins MS, Wolfangel RG: Comparison of in vitro RBC labeling with the UltraTag RBC kit versus in vivo labeling. J Nucl Med. 1991 Feb;32(2):242-4.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A32186</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>6089353</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Front D, Israel O, Groshar D, Weininger J: Technetium-99m-labeled red blood cell imaging. Semin Nucl Med. 1984 Jul;14(3):226-50.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Indicated for blood pool imaging, including cardiac first pass and gated equilibrium imaging and for detection of sites of gastrointestinal bleeding [FDA Label]. </indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>Technetium Tc-99m red blood cells are diagnostic agents that are distributed within the circulation to assess the vascular nature of hemangiomas and diagnosis of venous occlusion [A32186]. Blood abnormalities can be detected during gamma scintigraphic imaging.</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>Autologous red blood cells (RBC) are collected from the patient and put into the reaction vial for radiolabeling, followed by anticoagulation with heparin or Anticoagulant Citrate Dextrose Solution (ACD). In the reaction vial, stannous ion diffuses across the RBC membrane and accumulates intracellularly. Sodium hypochlorite, which does not cross the RBC membrane, is then added to the reaction vial to oxidize the extracellular stannous ion. Finally, sodium pertechnetate Tc 99m is added to the oxidized reaction vial to diffuse across the red blood cell membrane and be reduced by the intracellular stannous ion. Upon reduction, Tc 99m cannot diffuse out of the RBC. Technetium Tc 99m-labeled red blood cells are injected again into the patient for gamma scintigraphic imaging [FDA Label]. </mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity>No long term animal studies have been performed to evaluate carcinogenic or mutagenic potential or to determine the effects on male or female fertility [FDA Label]. </toxicity>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life>Technetium Tc 99m decays by isomeric transition with a physical half-life of 6.02 hours. The technetium Tc 99m is well retained in the blood pool with an estimated biological half-life of approximately 29 hours [FDA Label].</half-life>
  <protein-binding>Of the total technetium Tc 99m retained in the whole blood pool 24 hours after administration, 95% remains bound to the red blood cells [FDA Label].</protein-binding>
  <route-of-elimination>Approximately 25% of the injected dose is excreted in the urine in the first 24 hours [FDA Label]. </route-of-elimination>
  <volume-of-distribution>Following intravenous injection, the technetium Tc 99m-labeled red blood cells distribute within the blood pool with an estimated volume of distribution of approximately 5.6% of bodyweight [FDA Label].</volume-of-distribution>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Technetium (99mTc) red blood cells</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Technetium Tc 99m red blood cells</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Technetium Tc 99m-labeled red blood cells</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Technetium Tc-99m red blood cell</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Technetium Tc-99m red blood cell human</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>UltraTag RBC</name>
      <labeller>Mallinckrodt</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>0019-9068</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1991-06-10</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2017-07-01</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Kit</dosage-form>
      <strength>0.05 mg/9.5mg</strength>
      <route>Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>NDA019981</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>UltraTag RBC</name>
      <ingredients>Technetium Tc-99m red blood cells</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Radioactive Diagnostic Agent</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Radiopharmaceutical Activity</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Kit</form>
      <route>Intravenous</route>
      <strength>0.05 mg/9.5mg</strength>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <fda-label>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/fda_labels/DB09493.pdf?1521668464</fda-label>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910455</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>