<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-10-21" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05185</drugbank-id>
  <name>TRO19622</name>
  <description>TRO19622 is a cholesterol-like small molecule that has demonstrated a remarkable neuroprotective profile in a battery of both in vitro and in vivo preclinical models. For example, it has demonstrated the ability to prevent neurodegeneration, enhance nerve function and accelerate neuroregeneration following nerve trauma. </description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3282</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17496168</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Bordet T, Buisson B, Michaud M, Drouot C, Galea P, Delaage P, Akentieva NP, Evers AS, Covey DF, Ostuni MA, Lacapere JJ, Massaad C, Schumacher M, Steidl EM, Maux D, Delaage M, Henderson CE, Pruss RM: Identification and characterization of cholest-4-en-3-one, oxime (TRO19622), a novel drug candidate for amyotrophic lateral sclerosis. J Pharmacol Exp Ther. 2007 Aug;322(2):709-20. Epub 2007 May 11.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in neurologic disorders.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>TRO19622 interacts with a physiologically relevant target: the mitochondrial permeability transition pore (mPTP).&#13;
Mitochondria are central mediators of cell death and are implicated in most if not all neurodegenerative diseases regardless of the initiating factor: genetic mutations,&#13;
excitotoxicity, reactive oxygen species, ischemia, chemical toxicity, etc. Mitochondria play diverse roles in all cells.&#13;
In neurons, especially near synaptic sites, mitochondria are essential calcium-buffering organelles in areas where membrane excitability leads to large influx of calcium through calcium channels. Mitochondria also produce the ATP necessary for microtubule-based axoplasmic transport and maintaining the activity of ion and nutrient transporters. If a neuron fails to establish or maintain its functional role, mitochondria are responsible for eliminating it&#13;
by releasing apoptotic factors. TRO19622, by interacting with protein components of the mPTP, prevents the release of&#13;
these apoptotic factors and therefore protects the neuron. This mechanism of action may lead to a general neuroprotective activity with utility in other therapeutic indications.&#13;
</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Cholestanes</category>
      <mesh-id>D002776</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Cholestenes</category>
      <mesh-id>D002782</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Fused-Ring Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D000072473</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Steroids</category>
      <mesh-id>D013256</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910009</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>