<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-11-18" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05430</drugbank-id>
  <name>VLTS-589</name>
  <description>VLTS-589 consists of plasmid encoding the angiomatrix protein Del-1 in conjunction with poloxamer 188 for the treatment of peripheral vascular disease.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3475</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17452167</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Grossman PM, Mendelsohn F, Henry TD, Hermiller JB, Litt M, Saucedo JF, Weiss RJ, Kandzari DE, Kleiman N, Anderson RD, Gottlieb D, Karlsberg R, Snell J, Rocha-Singh K: Results from a phase II multicenter, double-blind placebo-controlled study of Del-1 (VLTS-589) for intermittent claudication in subjects with peripheral arterial disease. Am Heart J. 2007 May;153(5):874-80.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3476</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>15212720</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Rajagopalan S, Olin JW, Young S, Erikson M, Grossman PM, Mendelsohn FO, Regensteiner JG, Hiatt WR, Annex BH: Design of the Del-1 for therapeutic angiogenesis trial (DELTA-1), a phase II multicenter, double-blind, placebo-controlled trial of VLTS-589 in subjects with intermittent claudication secondary to peripheral arterial disease. Hum Gene Ther. 2004 Jun;15(6):619-24.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in peripheral vascular disease.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>VLTS-589 is an investigational nonviral therapeutic comprising a plasmid-expressing Del-1 formulated with poloxamer 188 (facilitating agent). Del-1 plasmid-polaxamer enhances gene transfer at doses that are an order of magnitude different than other comparable trials in a unique bilateral intramuscular dosing pattern to maximize transfection/clinical efficacy and general applicability to patients with peripheral arterial disease (PAD).</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910133</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>