<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2015-12-03" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB11265</drugbank-id>
  <name>Curcuma xanthorrhiza oil</name>
  <description>_Curcuma xanthorrhiza_ oil is extracted from _Curcuma xanthorrhiza_ Roxb., a member of the ginger family (_Zingiberaceae_) that is widely distributed in the region of Southeastern Asia [A33162].  _Curcuma xanthorrhiza_ is also known as Javanese Turmeric or Temoe Lawak [F114]. For centuries, _Curcuma xanthorrhiza_ oil has been used as a traditional medicine due to its antibacterial, antispasmodic, antioxidative, antitumor, anti-inflammatory and protective effects [A33160]. It has been used in the treatment of stomach diseases, liver disorders, constipation, bloody diarrhoea, dysentery, children’s fevers, hypotriglyceridaemic, haemorrhoids and skin eruptions [A33162]. _Curcuma xanthorrhiza_ oil is comprised of 1-2% of curcumin and 3-12% volatile oil, which mainly contains sesquiterpenes, 44.5% of xanthorrhizol, and a small amount of [DB01744] [F114]. However the principal active components of Curcuma xanthorrhiza are [DB11672] and xanthorrhizol that display a wide range of pharmacological activities and synergistic effects [F114]. Curcumin is a mixture of dicinnamoylmethane derivatives and other phenolic and non-phenolic diarylheptanoids [F114]. _Curcuma xanthorrhiza_ oil is found as an active ingredient in cosmetic and hygienic products, and marketing of products containing _Curcuma xanthorrhiza_ oil is authorized in some European countries including Germany and the Netherlands [F114].</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii>F8VF0V2G7H</unii>
  <groups>
    <group>nutraceutical</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A33160</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25133223</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Devaraj S, Ismail S, Ramanathan S, Yam MF: Investigation of antioxidant and hepatoprotective activity of standardized Curcuma xanthorrhiza rhizome in carbon tetrachloride-induced hepatic damaged rats. ScientificWorldJournal. 2014;2014:353128. doi: 10.1155/2014/353128. Epub 2014 Jul 14.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A33161</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>26500452</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Oon SF, Nallappan M, Tee TT, Shohaimi S, Kassim NK, Sa'ariwijaya MS, Cheah YH: Xanthorrhizol: a review of its pharmacological activities and anticancer properties. Cancer Cell Int. 2015 Oct 21;15:100. doi: 10.1186/s12935-015-0255-4. eCollection 2015.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A33162</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25190883</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Salea R, Widjojokusumo E, Veriansyah B, Tjandrawinata RR: Optimizing oil and xanthorrhizol extraction from Curcuma xanthorrhiza Roxb. rhizome by supercritical carbon dioxide. J Food Sci Technol. 2014 Sep;51(9):2197-203. doi: 10.1007/s13197-014-1272-3. Epub 2014 Feb 9.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments>
      <attachment>
        <ref-id>F114</ref-id>
        <title>European Medicines Agency (EMA): Assessment report on Curcuma xanthorrhiza Roxb. (C. xanthorrhiza D. Dietrich)., rhizoma</title>
        <url>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/cite_this/attachments/files/000/000/114/original/WC500144564.pdf?1527261710</url>
      </attachment>
    </attachments>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Indicated for the symptomatic relief of digestive disturbances, such as feelings of fullness, slow digestion and flatulence [F114]. </indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>_Curcuma xanthorrhiza_ oil is reported to exert diuretic, anticancer, anti-inflammatory, antioxidant, antihypertensive, antirheumatic, antihepatotoxic, antidysmenorrheal, antispasmodic, antileucorrhoeal, antibacterial, and antifungal actions experimentally and in literature [A33160]. _In vivo_, oral administration of _Curcuma xanthorrhiza_ oil in rats caused a persistent but transient (5h) increase of bile secretion due to the increase in the total bile acids in the excretive bile [F114]. This cholagogic effect is attributable for a major part to d-camphor contained  in the oil [F114]. In a study of rats with cisplastin-induced hepatotoxicity, administration of _Curcuma xanthorrhiza_ extract resulted in serum enzyme levels such as alanine aminotransferases (ALT), aspartate aminotransferases (AST), and y-glutamate transferases [A33160]. In addition, it was shown to mediate hepatoprotective actions against β-D-galactosamine-induced liver damage and alcohol [A33160]. In male ICR mice treated with cisplatin known to induce toxicity of kidneys and liver, xanthorrhizol demonstrated nephroprotective and hepatoprotective actions to attenuate the elevated levels of blood urea nitrogen and serum creatinine, as well as blood glutamate-pyruvate transaminase (GPT) and glutamate–oxaloacetate transaminase (GOT) levels [A33161].&#13;
&#13;
**Anti-inflammatory actions:** Curcuminoid derivatives and xanthorrhizol elicit anti-inflammatory effects by inhibiting oedema formation [F114]. &#13;
&#13;
**Antibacterial effects:** Xanthorrhizol displays a broad-spectrum antibacterial activity. In a study, it showed the highest antibacterial activity against dental caries causing bacteria (_Streptococcus_ species) to disrupt their biofilm formation _in vitro_, followed by periodontitis causing bacteria (_Actinomyces viscosus_ and _Porphyromona gingialis_) [A33161]. It also strongly inhibited Gram-positive bacteria _Staphylococcus aureus_, methicillin-resistant _Staphylococcus aureus_ (MRSA), Gram-negative bacteria _Escherichia coli_, and acne-causing bacteria _Propionibacterium acnes_ [A33161]. Xanthorrhizol additionally exhibits anticandidal and antifungal properties [A33161]. &#13;
&#13;
**Antiplatelet effects:** _In vitro_, both curcumin and xanthorrhizol showed a strong inhibition towards platelet aggregation stimulated by arachidonic acid, collagen, and ADP in human whole blood [A33161].&#13;
&#13;
**Anticancer effects:** Co-administration of curcumin and xanthorrhizol in MDA-MB-231 cells resulted in synergistic growth inhibition of breast cancer cells [A33161]. Topical application of 2 and 6 μmol xanthorrhizol in rats inhibited TPA-induced tumour formation [F114]. </pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>The prinicipal components, [DB11672] and xanthorrhizol, mediate the main pharmacological actions of _Curcuma xanthorrhiza_ oil. &#13;
&#13;
**Anti-inflammatory and antioxidant actions:** Curcumin and xanthorrhizol are natural antioxidant to exert an anti-inflammatory effect by scavenging the reactive oxygen species, such as hydroxyl radical, superoxide anion, and singlet oxygen, or by chemically reducing oxidized compounds [A33160]. Curcumin inhibits liposomal peroxidation and peroxide-induced DNA damage, and the mechanism of action is thought to involve modulation of cell adhesion molecules (CAMs) and stimulation of ICAM- 1 [F114]. Based on the findings _in vitro_, xanthorrhizol may be a potent inhibitor of cyclooxygenase-2 (COX-2) and inducible nitric oxide synthase (iNOS) to decrease their expression via NF-kB pathway and subsequently inhibit the production of pro-inflammatory prostaglandin E2 (PGE2) and nitric oxide (NO) [A33161]. In activated primary cultured microglial cells, xanthorrhizol was found to inhibit COX-2, iNOS, proinflammatory cytokine interleukin-6 (IL-6) and tumor necrosis factor-α (TNF-α) [A33161]. &#13;
&#13;
**Hepatoprotective actions:** The hepatoprotective effect of _Curcuma xanthorrhiza_ oil is considered mainly a result of its antioxidant properties, as well as its ability to decrease the levels of pro-inflammatory cytokines [F114]. Xanthorrhizol may also attenuate phosphorylation of c-Jun N-terminal kinases (JNKs) [A33161, F114]. &#13;
&#13;
**Antibacterial actions:** While the mode of antibacterial action of xanthorrhizol is not fully understood, it is thought to involve suppression of nuclear factor kappaB (NF-kB) and mitogen-activated protein kinase (MAPK) induced by microbial infection [A33161]. &#13;
&#13;
**Anticancer actions:** The cytotoxic actions of xanthorrhizol against tumour cells is thought to be contributed by its phenol group and may involve its antioxidative and anti-inflammatory activities, induction of apoptosis and cell cycle arrest by reducing cyclin D1 proto-oncogene expression or triggering cyclin-dependent kinase inhibitors (CDKIs) [A33161]. In various cancer cell models, xanthorrhizol was shown to induce apoptosis via activation of p53-dependent mitochondrial pathway. In HeLa cervical cancer cells, xanthorrhizol upregulated p53 and Bax without any effects on Bax/Bcl-2 expression [A33161]. There is also evidence that xanthorrhizol-induced cell death is mediated by the activation of caspase. Xanthorrhizol increased the expression and promoter activity pro-apoptotic non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drug-activated gene-1 (NAG-1), which is notably inhibited during the development of human colorectal cancer and neoplastic tumors [A33161]. Other mode of action involves the regulation of MAPK pathway and inhibition of Akt/NF-kB pathway [A33161].&#13;
&#13;
**Estrogenic and anti-estrogenic actions:** _In vitro_, xanthorrhizol upregulated pS2 and promoted  the interaction of ER-estrogen response elements in MCF-7 cells. It acted as a partial estrogen antagonist of hERα in T47D cells [A33161]. Curcumin also activates gene expression in the breast cancer cell line MCF7, indicating that it may have low estrogenic activity [F114]. </mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity>An aqueous extract of _Curcuma xanthorrhiza_ did not produce any signs of toxicity in mice or rats up to an oral dose of 2 g/kg bw [F114]. In a single toxicity study, no mortality was observed after a single oral administration of xanthorrhizol to mice at 500 mg/kg [F114]. The oral median lethal dose (LD50) of curcumin in mice was &gt;2g/kg bw and single oral doses of curcumin at 1-5 g/kg bw induced no toxic effects in rats [F114]. No case of overdose has been reported. </toxicity>
  <metabolism>There are no pharmacokinetic data for xanthorrhizol. Refer to [DB11672] for its pharmacokinetic information.</metabolism>
  <absorption>There are no pharmacokinetic data for xanthorrhizol. Refer to [DB11672] for its pharmacokinetic information.</absorption>
  <half-life>There are no pharmacokinetic data for xanthorrhizol. Refer to [DB11672] for its pharmacokinetic information.</half-life>
  <protein-binding>There are no pharmacokinetic data for xanthorrhizol. Refer to [DB11672] for its pharmacokinetic information.</protein-binding>
  <route-of-elimination>There are no pharmacokinetic data for xanthorrhizol. Refer to [DB11672] for its pharmacokinetic information.</route-of-elimination>
  <volume-of-distribution>There are no pharmacokinetic data for xanthorrhizol. Refer to [DB11672] for its pharmacokinetic information.</volume-of-distribution>
  <clearance>There are no pharmacokinetic data for xanthorrhizol. Refer to [DB11672] for its pharmacokinetic information.</clearance>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Curcuma xanthorrhiza root oil</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Curcuma xanthorrhiza volatile oil</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Curcuma zanthorrhiza oil</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Curcuma zanthorrhiza root oil</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Temu lawak oil</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>BAMBOO SALT Eunganggo Jook Yeom</name>
      <labeller>Lg Household &amp; Health Care Ltd.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>53208-505</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2011-03-15</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Paste</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Dental</route>
      <fda-application-number>part355</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>true</over-the-counter>
      <approved>false</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>BAMBOO SALT Eunganggo Jook Yeom Toothpaste</name>
      <labeller>Lg Household &amp; Health Care Ltd.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>53208-459</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2010-05-25</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Paste</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Dental</route>
      <fda-application-number>part355</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>true</over-the-counter>
      <approved>false</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>BAMBOO SALT Eunganggo Jook Yeom Toothpaste</name>
      <ingredients>Aminocaproic acid + Curcuma xanthorrhiza oil + Glycyrrhizic acid + Sea salt + Silicon dioxide + Sodium fluoride + Ursodeoxycholic acid</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>BAMBOO SALT Eunganggo Jook Yeom</name>
      <ingredients>Aminocaproic acid + Curcuma xanthorrhiza oil + Glycyrrhizic acid + Sea salt + Silicon dioxide + Sodium fluoride + Ursodeoxycholic acid</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Paste</form>
      <route>Dental</route>
      <strength/>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers/>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>