<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-11-18" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05768</drugbank-id>
  <name>Alkaline Phosphatase</name>
  <description>Alkaline Phosphatase (AP) is an oral treatment and has a very&#13;
favorable side-effect profile. AP only acts locally in the colon to reduce the continuous inflammation of the colon by endotoxin from Gram-negative bacteria and extracellular ATP in UC patients.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in ulcerative colitis.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>Patients with UC have reduced AP levels and activity in the inflamed tissue in the intestines. A short treatment with AP helps to restore the intestinal mucosal barrier in UC patients, which can be classified as a disease modifying antiinflammatory effect.</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>Two substrates that can disturb the homeostasis in&#13;
human organs are endotoxin from Gram-negative bacteria (LPS) and adenosine triphosphate (ATP). Dephosphorylation of LPS and extracellular ATP by AP has been shown to result in restoration of homeostasis in the target organs such as GI tract and kidney, through reduction of inflammationinduced&#13;
damage. In the gastrointestinal tract, the prime source of LPS is derived from the residing Gram-negative microorganisms. In UC patients the mucosal surface of the colon wall is characterized by intermittent lesions and hyperpermeability caused by chronic inflammation. A consequence of the damaged intestinal mucosa is a reduced AP level and an increased influx of LPS responsive cells that&#13;
maintain the inflammatory response. In the gastrointestinal tract, the prime source of LPS is derived from the residing Gram-negative microorganisms. AP reduces LPS-mediated&#13;
inflammation, by preventing activation of the intestinal epithelium and preventing systemic inflammatory responses that result from transmigration of endotoxin though the&#13;
leaky inflamed intestinal mucosa.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Alkaline Phosphatase, antagonists &amp; inhibitors</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Enzymes</category>
      <mesh-id>D004798</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Enzymes and Coenzymes</category>
      <mesh-id>D045762</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Esterases</category>
      <mesh-id>D004950</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Hydrolases</category>
      <mesh-id>D006867</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Phosphoric Monoester Hydrolases</category>
      <mesh-id>D010744</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910221</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Wikipedia</resource>
      <identifier>Alkaline_phosphatase</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>