<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2005-06-13" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB04249</drugbank-id>
  <drugbank-id>EXPT01728</drugbank-id>
  <name>Zinc Substituted Heme C</name>
  <description/>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <average-mass>628.067</average-mass>
  <monoisotopic-mass>626.187152174</monoisotopic-mass>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>experimental</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication/>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action/>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Metal cations</category>
      <mesh-id>D002412</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Metal divalent cations</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Zinc Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D017967</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries>
    <pdb-entry>1m60</pdb-entry>
  </pdb-entries>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01586</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ursodeoxycholic acid</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ursodeoxycholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02123</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glycochenodeoxycholic Acid</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Glycochenodeoxycholic Acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02659</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cholic Acid</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Cholic Acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02691</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glycocholic acid</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Glycocholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03619</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deoxycholic acid</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Deoxycholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04348</drugbank-id>
      <name>Taurocholic acid</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Taurocholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05990</drugbank-id>
      <name>Obeticholic acid</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Obeticholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06777</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chenodeoxycholic acid</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Chenodeoxycholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08833</drugbank-id>
      <name>Taurochenodeoxycholic acid</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Taurochenodeoxycholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08834</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tauroursodeoxycholic acid</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Tauroursodeoxycholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08857</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bamet-UD2</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Bamet-UD2 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11622</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dehydrocholic acid</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dehydrocholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11789</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hyodeoxycholic Acid</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Hyodeoxycholic Acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06210</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eltrombopag</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Eltrombopag resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Raltegravir</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Raltegravir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Halofantrine</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Halofantrine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06824</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triethylenetetramine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Zinc Substituted Heme C can be decreased when it is combined with Triethylenetetramine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moxifloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Moxifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00365</drugbank-id>
      <name>Grepafloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Grepafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00467</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enoxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Enoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00487</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pefloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pefloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00537</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ciprofloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ciprofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00685</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trovafloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Trovafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00779</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nalidixic acid</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Nalidixic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rosoxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rosoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00827</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cinoxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Cinoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00978</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lomefloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Lomefloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01044</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gatifloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Gatifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01059</drugbank-id>
      <name>Norfloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Norfloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01137</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levofloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Levofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01155</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemifloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Gemifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01165</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ofloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sparfloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sparfloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01405</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temafloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Temafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04576</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fleroxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Fleroxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05488</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m ciprofloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Technetium Tc-99m ciprofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06160</drugbank-id>
      <name>Garenoxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Garenoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06600</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nemonoxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Nemonoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08972</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flumequine</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Flumequine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11404</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enrofloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Enrofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11443</drugbank-id>
      <name>Orbifloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Orbifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11491</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sarafloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sarafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11511</drugbank-id>
      <name>Difloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Difloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11774</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pazufloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pazufloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11892</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prulifloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Prulifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11943</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delafloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Delafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13261</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sitafloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sitafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13627</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxolinic acid</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Oxolinic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13772</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rufloxacin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rufloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13823</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pipemidic acid</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pipemidic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00256</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lymecycline</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Lymecycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00453</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clomocycline</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Clomocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00560</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tigecycline</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Tigecycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxytetracycline</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Oxytetracycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00618</drugbank-id>
      <name>Demeclocycline</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Demeclocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00759</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetracycline</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Tetracycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00931</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metacycline</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Metacycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01017</drugbank-id>
      <name>Minocycline</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Minocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01301</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rolitetracycline</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rolitetracycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12035</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sarecycline</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sarecycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12329</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eravacycline</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Eravacycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12455</drugbank-id>
      <name>Omadacycline</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Omadacycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13092</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meclocycline</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Meclocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penimepicycline</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Penimepicycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00252</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenytoin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Phenytoin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00532</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mephenytoin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Mephenytoin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00564</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbamazepine</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Carbamazepine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00849</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylphenobarbital</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Methylphenobarbital resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01174</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenobarbital</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Phenobarbital resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01415</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftibuten</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ceftibuten resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00567</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cephalexin</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Cephalexin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08826</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deferiprone</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Deferiprone resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08930</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dolutegravir</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dolutegravir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01609</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deferasirox</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Deferasirox resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01071</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mequitazine</name>
      <description>Zinc Substituted Heme C can cause a decrease in the absorption of Mequitazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <calculated-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>5.33</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logS</kind>
      <value>-5.2</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Water Solubility</kind>
      <value>4.49e-03 g/l</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>-0.9</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>λ⁴-zinc(4+) ion (19E)-5,9-bis(2-carboxyethyl)-14,19-diethylidene-4,10,15,20-tetramethyl-21,22,23,24-tetraazapentacyclo[16.2.1.1³,⁶.1⁸,¹¹.1¹³,¹⁶]tetracosa-1(20),2,4,6,8,10,12,15,17-nonaene-21,22,23,24-tetraide</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Traditional IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>λ⁴-zinc(4+) ion (19E)-5,9-bis(2-carboxyethyl)-14,19-diethylidene-4,10,15,20-tetramethyl-21,22,23,24-tetraazapentacyclo[16.2.1.1³,⁶.1⁸,¹¹.1¹³,¹⁶]tetracosa-1(20),2,4,6,8,10,12,15,17-nonaene-21,22,23,24-tetraide</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Weight</kind>
      <value>628.067</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Monoisotopic Weight</kind>
      <value>626.187152174</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>SMILES</kind>
      <value>[Zn+4].[H]\C(C)=C1\C(C)=C2[N-]\C\1=C([H])/C1=C(C)C(=C([H])C)\C([N-]1)=C([H])\C1=C(C)C(CCC(O)=O)=C([N-]1)\C([H])=C1/[N-]\C(=C/2\[H])C(C)=C1CCC(O)=O</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Formula</kind>
      <value>C34H34N4O4Zn</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChI</kind>
      <value>InChI=1S/C34H34N4O4.Zn/c1-7-21-17(3)25-13-26-19(5)23(9-11-33(39)40)31(37-26)16-32-24(10-12-34(41)42)20(6)28(38-32)15-30-22(8-2)18(4)27(36-30)14-29(21)35-25;/h7-8,13-16H,9-12H2,1-6H3,(H,39,40)(H,41,42);/q-4;+4/b21-7+,22-8?,26-13-,29-14-,30-15-,31-16-;</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChIKey</kind>
      <value>OSHBEULYPOLYCE-DXQPMOBYSA-N</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polar Surface Area (PSA)</kind>
      <value>115.18</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Refractivity</kind>
      <value>174.7</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polarizability</kind>
      <value>66.32</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rotatable Bond Count</kind>
      <value>6</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Acceptor Count</kind>
      <value>8</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Donor Count</kind>
      <value>2</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest acidic)</kind>
      <value>3.56</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest basic)</kind>
      <value>9.12</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Physiological Charge</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Number of Rings</kind>
      <value>5</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Bioavailability</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rule of Five</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Ghose Filter</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>MDDR-Like Rule</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
  </calculated-properties>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Compound</resource>
      <identifier>131704274</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>46508051</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChemSpider</resource>
      <identifier>64873345</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PDB</resource>
      <identifier>HES</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets>
    <target>
      <id>BE0001009</id>
      <name>Cytochrome c</name>
      <organism>Humans</organism>
      <actions/>
      <references>
        <articles>
          <article>
            <ref-id>A1713</ref-id>
            <pubmed-id>17139284</pubmed-id>
            <citation>Overington JP, Al-Lazikani B, Hopkins AL: How many drug targets are there? Nat Rev Drug Discov. 2006 Dec;5(12):993-6.</citation>
          </article>
          <article>
            <ref-id>A1715</ref-id>
            <pubmed-id>17016423</pubmed-id>
            <citation>Imming P, Sinning C, Meyer A: Drugs, their targets and the nature and number of drug targets. Nat Rev Drug Discov. 2006 Oct;5(10):821-34.</citation>
          </article>
          <article>
            <ref-id>A1991</ref-id>
            <pubmed-id>10592235</pubmed-id>
            <citation>Berman HM, Westbrook J, Feng Z, Gilliland G, Bhat TN, Weissig H, Shindyalov IN, Bourne PE: The Protein Data Bank. Nucleic Acids Res. 2000 Jan 1;28(1):235-42.</citation>
          </article>
        </articles>
        <textbooks/>
        <links/>
        <attachments/>
      </references>
      <known-action>unknown</known-action>
      <polypeptide id="P99999" source="Swiss-Prot">
        <name>Cytochrome c</name>
        <general-function>Metal ion binding</general-function>
        <specific-function>Electron carrier protein. The oxidized form of the cytochrome c heme group can accept an electron from the heme group of the cytochrome c1 subunit of cytochrome reductase. Cytochrome c then transfers this electron to the cytochrome oxidase complex, the final protein carrier in the mitochondrial electron-transport chain.Plays a role in apoptosis. Suppression of the anti-apoptotic members or activation of the pro-apoptotic members of the Bcl-2 family leads to altered mitochondrial membrane permeability resulting in release of cytochrome c into the cytosol. Binding of cytochrome c to Apaf-1 triggers the activation of caspase-9, which then accelerates apoptosis by activating other caspases.</specific-function>
        <gene-name>CYCS</gene-name>
        <locus>7p15.2</locus>
        <cellular-location>Mitochondrion intermembrane space</cellular-location>
        <transmembrane-regions/>
        <signal-regions/>
        <theoretical-pi>10.16</theoretical-pi>
        <molecular-weight>11748.69</molecular-weight>
        <chromosome-location>7</chromosome-location>
        <organism ncbi-taxonomy-id="9606">Humans</organism>
        <external-identifiers>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>HUGO Gene Nomenclature Committee (HGNC)</resource>
            <identifier>HGNC:19986</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>GenAtlas</resource>
            <identifier>CYCS</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>GenBank Gene Database</resource>
            <identifier>M22877</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>GenBank Protein Database</resource>
            <identifier>181242</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>UniProtKB</resource>
            <identifier>P99999</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>UniProt Accession</resource>
            <identifier>CYC_HUMAN</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
        </external-identifiers>
        <synonyms>
          <synonym>CYC</synonym>
        </synonyms>
        <amino-acid-sequence format="FASTA">&gt;lcl|BSEQ0010707|Cytochrome c
MGDVEKGKKIFIMKCSQCHTVEKGGKHKTGPNLHGLFGRKTGQAPGYSYTAANKNKGIIW
GEDTLMEYLENPKKYIPGTKMIFVGIKKKEERADLIAYLKKATNE</amino-acid-sequence>
        <gene-sequence format="FASTA">&gt;lcl|BSEQ0010708|Cytochrome c (CYCS)
ATGGGTGATGTTGAGAAAGGCAAGAAGATTTTTATTATGAAGTGTTCCCAGTGCCACACC
GTTGAAAAGGGAGGCAAGCACAAGACTGGGCCAAATCTCCATGGTCTCTTTGGGCGGAAG
ACAGGTCAGGCCCCTGGATACTCTTACACAGCCGCCAATAAGAACAAAGGCATCATCTGG
GGAGAGGATACACTGATGGAGTATTTGGAGAATCCCAAGAAGTACATCCCTGGAACAAAA
ATGATCTTTGTCGGCATTAAGAAGAAGGAAGAAAGGGCAGACTTAATAGCTTATCTCAAA
AAAGCTACTAATGAGTAA</gene-sequence>
        <pfams>
          <pfam>
            <identifier>PF00034</identifier>
            <name>Cytochrom_C</name>
          </pfam>
        </pfams>
        <go-classifiers>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>component</category>
            <description>cytosol</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>component</category>
            <description>mitochondrial inner membrane</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>component</category>
            <description>mitochondrial intermembrane space</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>component</category>
            <description>mitochondrion</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>component</category>
            <description>nucleus</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>component</category>
            <description>protein phosphatase type 2A complex</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>component</category>
            <description>respiratory chain</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>function</category>
            <description>electron transporter, transferring electrons from CoQH2-cytochrome c reductase complex and cytochrome c oxidase complex activity</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>function</category>
            <description>heme binding</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>function</category>
            <description>metal ion binding</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>activation of cysteine-type endopeptidase activity involved in apoptotic process by cytochrome c</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>apoptotic process</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>ATP synthesis coupled electron transport</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>cellular metabolic process</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>cellular respiration</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>gene expression</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>intrinsic apoptotic signaling pathway</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>mitochondrial electron transport, cytochrome c to oxygen</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>mitochondrial electron transport, ubiquinol to cytochrome c</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>mitochondrion organization</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>organelle organization</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>programmed cell death</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>protein dephosphorylation</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>respiratory electron transport chain</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>response to reactive oxygen species</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>small molecule metabolic process</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>transcription initiation from RNA polymerase II promoter</description>
          </go-classifier>
        </go-classifiers>
      </polypeptide>
    </target>
  </targets>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>