<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2016-02-25" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB11413</drugbank-id>
  <name>Florfenicol</name>
  <description>Florfenicol is a fluorinated synthetic analog of thiamphenicol.</description>
  <cas-number>73231-34-2</cas-number>
  <unii>9J97307Y1H</unii>
  <average-mass>358.21</average-mass>
  <monoisotopic-mass>357.0004627</monoisotopic-mass>
  <groups>
    <group>experimental</group>
    <group>vet_approved</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8378</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>11475424</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Picco EJ, Diaz DC, Valtorta SE, Boggi JC: Chronotoxicology of florfenicol. Chronobiol Int. 2001 May;18(3):567-72.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8379</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17570454</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Park BK, Lim JH, Kim MS, Hwang YH, Yun HI: Pharmacokinetics of florfenicol and its metabolite, florfenicol amine, in dogs. Res Vet Sci. 2008 Feb;84(1):85-9. Epub 2007 Jun 13.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8380</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>15175268</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Blickwede M, Valentin-Weigand P, Schwarz S: Subinhibitory concentrations of florfenicol enhance the adherence of florfenicol-susceptible and florfenicol-resistant Staphylococcus aureus. J Antimicrob Chemother. 2004 Jul;54(1):286-8. Epub 2004 Jun 2.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8381</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>16670108</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Kehrenberg C, Meunier D, Targant H, Cloeckaert A, Schwarz S, Madec JY: Plasmid-mediated florfenicol resistance in Pasteurella trehalosi. J Antimicrob Chemother. 2006 Jul;58(1):13-7. Epub 2006 May 2.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8382</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>12607736</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Hayes JM, Eichman J, Katz T, Gilewicz R: Stability of florfenicol in drinking water. J AOAC Int. 2003 Jan-Feb;86(1):22-9.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8383</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>18307512</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Lane VM, Villarroel A, Wetzlich SE, Clifford A, Taylor I, Craigmill AL: Tissue residues of florfenicol in sheep. J Vet Pharmacol Ther. 2008 Apr;31(2):178-80. doi: 10.1111/j.1365-2885.2007.00918.x.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8384</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>15102069</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Cook AL, St Claire M, Sams R: Use of florfenicol in non-human primates. J Med Primatol. 2004 Jun;33(3):127-33.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8385</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>3806782</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Varma KJ, Adams PE, Powers TE, Powers JD, Lamendola JF: Pharmacokinetics of florfenicol in veal calves. J Vet Pharmacol Ther. 1986 Dec;9(4):412-25.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8386</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>23482237</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Illambas J, Potter T, Sidhu P, Rycroft AN, Cheng Z, Lees P: Pharmacodynamics of florfenicol for calf pneumonia pathogens. Vet Rec. 2013 Mar 30;172(13):340. doi: 10.1136/vr.101155. Epub 2013 Mar 12.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8387</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>15814600</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Kehrenberg C, Schwarz S: Plasmid-borne florfenicol resistance in Pasteurella multocida. J Antimicrob Chemother. 2005 May;55(5):773-5. Epub 2005 Apr 6.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8388</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25287575</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Yu ZG, Geng ZX, Liu TF, Jiang F: In vitro and in vivo evaluation of an in situ forming gel system for sustained delivery of Florfenicol. J Vet Pharmacol Ther. 2015 Jun;38(3):271-7. doi: 10.1111/jvp.12171. Epub 2014 Oct 7.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8389</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25395188</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Xu M, Qian M, Zhang H, Ma J, Wang J, Wu H: Simultaneous determination of florfenicol with its metabolite based on modified quick, easy, cheap, effective, rugged, and safe sample pretreatment and evaluation of their degradation behavior in agricultural soils. J Sep Sci. 2015 Jan;38(2):211-7. doi: 10.1002/jssc.201400919. Epub 2014 Dec 18.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8390</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25567063</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Gao YQ, Gao NY, Deng Y, Yin DQ, Zhang YS: Degradation of florfenicol in water by UV/Na2S 2O 8 process. Environ Sci Pollut Res Int. 2015 Jun;22(11):8693-701. doi: 10.1007/s11356-014-4054-6. Epub 2015 Jan 9.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8391</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25572306</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Woerde DJ, Martin PA, Govendir M: Susceptibility of rapidly growing mycobacteria isolated from Australian cats to ivermectin, moxidectin, ceftiofur and florfenicol. J Feline Med Surg. 2015 Dec;17(12):1065-8. doi: 10.1177/1098612X14565497. Epub 2015 Jan 8.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8392</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25612770</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Fedeniuk RW, McKenzie D, Mizuno M, Neiser C, O'Byrne C, Shurmer B: Development and validation of determinative and confirmatory LC-MS/MS methodologies for total florfenicol and tulathromycin residues in bovine, equine and porcine kidney, liver and muscle tissues. J Chromatogr B Analyt Technol Biomed Life Sci. 2015 Mar 1;983-984:1-9. doi: 10.1016/j.jchromb.2014.12.035. Epub 2015 Jan 12.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8393</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25614968</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Chen H, Son S, Zhang F, Yan J, Li Y, Ding H, Ding L: Rapid preparation of molecularly imprinted polymers by microwave-assisted emulsion polymerization for the extraction of florfenicol in milk. J Chromatogr B Analyt Technol Biomed Life Sci. 2015 Mar 1;983-984:32-8. doi: 10.1016/j.jchromb.2015.01.003. Epub 2015 Jan 13.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8394</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25618189</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Mitchell SM, Ullman JL, Teel AL, Watts RJ: Hydrolysis of amphenicol and macrolide antibiotics: Chloramphenicol, florfenicol, spiramycin, and tylosin. Chemosphere. 2015 Sep;134:504-11. doi: 10.1016/j.chemosphere.2014.08.050. Epub 2015 Jan 21.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8395</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25623169</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Maaland MG, Mo SS, Schwarz S, Guardabassi L: In vitro assessment of chloramphenicol and florfenicol as second-line antimicrobial agents in dogs. J Vet Pharmacol Ther. 2015 Oct;38(5):443-50. doi: 10.1111/jvp.12204. Epub 2015 Jan 27.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8396</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25675893</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Guo L, Song S, Liu L, Peng J, Kuang H, Xu C: Comparsion of an immunochromatographic strip with ELISA for simultaneous detection of thiamphenicol, florfenicol and chloramphenicol in food samples. Biomed Chromatogr. 2015 Sep;29(9):1432-9. doi: 10.1002/bmc.3442. Epub 2015 Feb 10.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8397</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25686865</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Klaudia C, Alina W: The influence of enrofloxacin, florfenicol, ceftiofur and E. coli LPS interaction on T and B cells subset in chicks. Vet Res Commun. 2015 Mar;39(1):53-60. doi: 10.1007/s11259-015-9632-7. Epub 2015 Feb 10.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8398</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25706107</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Gaunt PS, Chatakondi N, Gao D, Endris R: Efficacy of Florfenicol for Control of Mortality Associated with Edwardsiella ictaluri in Three Species of Catfish. J Aquat Anim Health. 2015 Mar;27(1):45-9. doi: 10.1080/08997659.2014.976672.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8399</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25723132</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Peng G, He Q, Al-Hamadani SM, Zhou G, Liu M, Zhu H, Chen J: Dispersive liquid-liquid microextraction method based on solidification of floating organic droplet for the determination of thiamphenicol and florfenicol in environmental water samples. Ecotoxicol Environ Saf. 2015 May;115:229-33. doi: 10.1016/j.ecoenv.2015.02.025. Epub 2015 Feb 24.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8400</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25744433</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Pentecost RL, Niehaus AJ, Werle N, Lakritz J: Absorption and disposition of florfenicol after intravenous, intramuscular and subcutaneous dosing in alpacas. Res Vet Sci. 2015 Apr;99:199-203. doi: 10.1016/j.rvsc.2015.02.006. Epub 2015 Feb  16.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8401</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25771961</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Geng ZX, Li HM, Tian J, Liu TF, Yu ZG: Study of pharmacokinetics of an in situ forming gel system for controlled delivery of florfenicol in pigs. J Vet Pharmacol Ther. 2015 Dec;38(6):596-600. doi: 10.1111/jvp.12218. Epub 2015 Mar 16.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8402</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25827198</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Rottboll LA, Skovgaard K, Barington K, Jensen HE, Friis C: Intrabronchial Microdialysis: Effects of Probe Localization on Tissue Trauma and Drug Penetration into the Pulmonary Epithelial Lining Fluid. Basic Clin Pharmacol Toxicol. 2015 Oct;117(4):242-50. doi: 10.1111/bcpt.12403. Epub 2015 Apr 17.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8403</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25830490</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Pilehvar S, Gielkens K, Trashin SA, Dardenne F, Blust R, Wael K: (Electro)Sensing of Phenicol Antibiotics - A Review. Crit Rev Food Sci Nutr. 2015 Apr 1:0.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8404</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25886128</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Nasim A, Aslam B, Javed I, Ali A, Muhammad F, Raza A, Sindhu ZU: Determination of florfenicol residues in broiler meat and liver samples using RP-HPLC with UV-visible detection. J Sci Food Agric. 2016 Mar;96(4):1284-8. doi: 10.1002/jsfa.7220. Epub 2015 May 12.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8405</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25886555</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Jones ML, Washburn KE, Fajt VR, Rice S, Coetzee JF: Synovial fluid pharmacokinetics of tulathromycin, gamithromycin and florfenicol after a single subcutaneous dose in cattle. BMC Vet Res. 2015 Feb 7;11:26. doi: 10.1186/s12917-015-0346-4.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8406</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25891823</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Zhang Q, Tang SS, Qian MY, Wei L, Zhou D, Zhang ZJ, He JK, Zhang QJ, Zhu P, Xiao XL: Nanoemulsion formulation of florfenicol improves bioavailability in pigs. J Vet Pharmacol Ther. 2016 Feb;39(1):84-9. doi: 10.1111/jvp.12230. Epub 2015 Apr  20.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8407</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25913426</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Fedeniuk RW, Mizuno M, Neiser C, O'Byrne C: Development of LC-MS/MS methodology for the detection/determination and confirmation of chloramphenicol, chloramphenicol 3-O-beta-d-glucuronide, florfenicol, florfenicol amine and thiamphenicol residues in bovine, equine and porcine liver. J Chromatogr B Analyt Technol Biomed Life Sci. 2015 Jun 1;991:68-78. doi: 10.1016/j.jchromb.2015.04.009. Epub 2015 Apr 10.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8408</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25973625</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Zhang A, Yang Y, Wang H, Lei C, Xu C, Guan Z, Liu B, Huang X, Peng L: PREVALENCE OF SULFONAMIDE AND FLORFENICOL RESISTANCE GENES IN ESCHERICHIA COLI ISOLATED FROM YAKS (BOS GRUNNIENS) AND HERDSMEN IN THE TIBETAN PASTURE. J Wildl Dis. 2015 Jul;51(3):626-33. doi: 10.7589/2014-09-234. Epub 2015 May 14.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8409</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>26025252</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Sin DW, Ho C, Wong YT: Phenylboronic Acid Solid Phase Extraction Cleanup and Isotope Dilution Liquid Chromatography-Tandem Mass Spectrometry for the Determination of Florfenicol Amine in Fish Muscles. J AOAC Int. 2015 May-Jun;98(3):566-74. doi: 10.5740/jaoacint.14-267. Epub 2015 May 28.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A8410</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>26049592</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Bosse JT, Li Y, Atherton TG, Walker S, Williamson SM, Rogers J, Chaudhuri RR, Weinert LA, Holden MT, Maskell DJ, Tucker AW, Wren BW, Rycroft AN, Langford PR: Characterisation of a mobilisable plasmid conferring florfenicol and chloramphenicol resistance in Actinobacillus pleuropneumoniae. Vet Microbiol. 2015 Aug 5;178(3-4):279-82. doi: 10.1016/j.vetmic.2015.05.020. Epub 2015 May 28.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication/>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action/>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description>This compound belongs to the class of organic compounds known as benzenesulfonyl compounds. These are aromatic compounds containing a benzenesulfonyl group, which consists of a monocyclic benzene moiety that carries a sulfonyl group.</description>
    <direct-parent>Benzenesulfonyl compounds</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Benzenoids</superclass>
    <class>Benzene and substituted derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Benzenesulfonyl compounds</subclass>
    <alternative-parent>Alkyl chlorides</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Alkyl fluorides</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Aromatic alcohols</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Carboximidic acids</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Hydrocarbon derivatives</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Organic oxides</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Organochlorides</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Organofluorides</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Organonitrogen compounds</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Organopnictogen compounds</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Propargyl-type 1,3-dipolar organic compounds</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Secondary alcohols</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Sulfones</alternative-parent>
    <substituent>Alcohol</substituent>
    <substituent>Alkyl chloride</substituent>
    <substituent>Alkyl fluoride</substituent>
    <substituent>Alkyl halide</substituent>
    <substituent>Aromatic alcohol</substituent>
    <substituent>Aromatic homomonocyclic compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Benzenesulfonyl group</substituent>
    <substituent>Carboximidic acid</substituent>
    <substituent>Carboximidic acid derivative</substituent>
    <substituent>Hydrocarbon derivative</substituent>
    <substituent>Organic 1,3-dipolar compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Organic nitrogen compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Organic oxide</substituent>
    <substituent>Organic oxygen compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Organochloride</substituent>
    <substituent>Organofluoride</substituent>
    <substituent>Organohalogen compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Organonitrogen compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Organooxygen compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Organopnictogen compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Organosulfur compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Propargyl-type 1,3-dipolar organic compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Secondary alcohol</substituent>
    <substituent>Sulfone</substituent>
    <substituent>Sulfonyl</substituent>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">(-)-Florfenicol</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">D-threo-2,2-Dichloro-N-(alpha-(fluoromethyl)-beta-hydroxy-p-(methylsulfonyl)phenethyl)acetamide</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="inn/ban/usan">Florfenicol</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products/>
  <international-brands>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Nuflor</name>
      <company/>
    </international-brand>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Nuflor gold</name>
      <company/>
    </international-brand>
  </international-brands>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Alcohols</category>
      <mesh-id>D000438</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Anti-Bacterial Agents</category>
      <mesh-id>D000900</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Anti-Infective Agents</category>
      <mesh-id>D000890</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Benzene Derivatives</category>
      <mesh-id>D001555</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Glycols</category>
      <mesh-id>D006018</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nitro Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D009574</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nitrobenzenes</category>
      <mesh-id>D009578</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Propylene Glycols</category>
      <mesh-id>D011409</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09268</drugbank-id>
      <name>Picosulfuric acid</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Picosulfuric acid can be decreased when used in combination with Florfenicol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12768</drugbank-id>
      <name>BCG vaccine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of BCG vaccine can be decreased when used in combination with Florfenicol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14022</drugbank-id>
      <name>Typhoid vaccine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Typhoid vaccine can be decreased when used in combination with Florfenicol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00266</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dicoumarol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Florfenicol is combined with Dicoumarol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00498</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenindione</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Florfenicol is combined with Phenindione.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00682</drugbank-id>
      <name>Warfarin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Florfenicol is combined with Warfarin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00946</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenprocoumon</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Florfenicol is combined with Phenprocoumon.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01418</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acenocoumarol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Florfenicol is combined with Acenocoumarol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03410</drugbank-id>
      <name>4-hydroxycoumarin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Florfenicol is combined with 4-hydroxycoumarin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04665</drugbank-id>
      <name>Coumarin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Florfenicol is combined with Coumarin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08496</drugbank-id>
      <name>(R)-warfarin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Florfenicol is combined with (R)-warfarin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08794</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethyl biscoumacetate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Florfenicol is combined with Ethyl biscoumacetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13136</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluindione</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Florfenicol is combined with Fluindione.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13275</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clorindione</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Florfenicol is combined with Clorindione.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13347</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diphenadione</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Florfenicol is combined with Diphenadione.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13451</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tioclomarol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Florfenicol is combined with Tioclomarol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14055</drugbank-id>
      <name>(S)-Warfarin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Florfenicol is combined with (S)-Warfarin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00581</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lactulose</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Lactulose can be decreased when used in combination with Florfenicol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <calculated-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>0.98</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logS</kind>
      <value>-3.2</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Water Solubility</kind>
      <value>2.19e-01 g/l</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>0.67</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>2,2-dichloro-N-[(1R,2S)-3-fluoro-1-hydroxy-1-(4-methanesulfonylphenyl)propan-2-yl]acetamide</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Traditional IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>[(1R,2R,6R,10S,11R,15R,17R)-13-benzyl-6-hydroxy-4,17-dimethyl-5-oxo-15-(prop-1-en-2-yl)-12,14,18-trioxapentacyclo[11.4.1.0^{1,10}.0^{2,6}.0^{11,15}]octadeca-3,8-dien-8-yl]methyl 2-(4-hydroxy-3-methoxyphenyl)acetate</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Weight</kind>
      <value>358.21</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Monoisotopic Weight</kind>
      <value>357.0004627</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>SMILES</kind>
      <value>CS(=O)(=O)C1=CC=C(C=C1)[C@@H](O)[C@@H](CF)NC(=O)C(Cl)Cl</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Formula</kind>
      <value>C12H14Cl2FNO4S</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChI</kind>
      <value>InChI=1S/C12H14Cl2FNO4S/c1-21(19,20)8-4-2-7(3-5-8)10(17)9(6-15)16-12(18)11(13)14/h2-5,9-11,17H,6H2,1H3,(H,16,18)/t9-,10-/m1/s1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChIKey</kind>
      <value>AYIRNRDRBQJXIF-NXEZZACHSA-N</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polar Surface Area (PSA)</kind>
      <value>83.47</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Refractivity</kind>
      <value>78.19</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polarizability</kind>
      <value>31.49</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rotatable Bond Count</kind>
      <value>6</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Acceptor Count</kind>
      <value>4</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Donor Count</kind>
      <value>2</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest acidic)</kind>
      <value>8.49</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest basic)</kind>
      <value>-3.4</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Physiological Charge</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Number of Rings</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Bioavailability</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rule of Five</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Ghose Filter</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>MDDR-Like Rule</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
  </calculated-properties>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Drugs Product Database (DPD)</resource>
      <identifier>63</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEBI</resource>
      <identifier>87185</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>KEGG Drug</resource>
      <identifier>D04194</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChemSpider</resource>
      <identifier>102776</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Wikipedia</resource>
      <identifier>Florfenicol</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEMBL</resource>
      <identifier>CHEMBL1241590</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>