<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2018-10-09" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB14713</drugbank-id>
  <name>Inotersen</name>
  <description>Inotersen is a transthyretin-directed antisense oligonucleotide for the treatment of the polyneuropathy caused by hereditary transthyretin-mediated amyloidosis in adults. It was FDA approved in October 2018 [FDA label]. Inotersen has been shown to improve the course of neurologic disease and quality of life in patients with hereditary transthyretin amyloidosis [A39493].&#13;
&#13;
Hereditary transthyretin amyloidosis is caused by single-nucleotide variants in the gene encoding transthyretin (TTR), which lead to transthyretin misfolding and the deposition of amyloid substance systemically. Progressive amyloid accumulation may lead to multiorgan dysfunction and death [A39493].</description>
  <cas-number>1492984-65-2</cas-number>
  <unii>0IEO0F56LV</unii>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A39493</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>29972757</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Benson MD, Waddington-Cruz M, Berk JL, Polydefkis M, Dyck PJ, Wang AK, Plante-Bordeneuve V, Barroso FA, Merlini G, Obici L, Scheinberg M, Brannagan TH 3rd, Litchy WJ, Whelan C, Drachman BM, Adams D, Heitner SB, Conceicao I, Schmidt HH, Vita G, Campistol JM, Gamez J, Gorevic PD, Gane E, Shah AM, Solomon SD, Monia BP, Hughes SG, Kwoh TJ, McEvoy BW, Jung SW, Baker BF, Ackermann EJ, Gertz MA, Coelho T: Inotersen Treatment for Patients with Hereditary Transthyretin Amyloidosis. N Engl J Med. 2018 Jul 5;379(1):22-31. doi: 10.1056/NEJMoa1716793.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A39494</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>29240946</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Shen X, Corey DR: Chemistry, mechanism and clinical status of antisense oligonucleotides and duplex RNAs. Nucleic Acids Res. 2018 Feb 28;46(4):1584-1600. doi: 10.1093/nar/gkx1239.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A39495</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>29185862</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Crooke ST, Baker BF, Pham NC, Hughes SG, Kwoh TJ, Cai D, Tsimikas S, Geary RS, Bhanot S: The Effects of 2'-O-Methoxyethyl Oligonucleotides on Renal Function in Humans. Nucleic Acid Ther. 2018 Feb;28(1):10-22. doi: 10.1089/nat.2017.0693. Epub 2017 Nov 29.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments>
      <attachment>
        <ref-id>F1938</ref-id>
        <title>Tegsedi EMA label</title>
        <url>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/cite_this/attachments/files/000/001/938/original/tegsedi-epar-product-information_en.pdf?1539980614</url>
      </attachment>
    </attachments>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Inotersen is a transthyretin-directed antisense oligonucleotide indicated for treatment of the polyneuropathy of hereditary transthyretin-mediated amyloidosis in adults [FDA label], [F1938].  </indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>The pharmacodynamic effects of inotersen were studied in hereditary transthyretin-mediated amyloidosis (hATTR) amyloidosis patients treated with 284 mg of inotersen via subcutaneous injection once weekly. With repeated dosing, the mean percentage decreases from baseline in serum TTR (transthyretin) from week 13 to Week 65 of treatment were measured from 68%-74% (median range: 75% to 79%). Similar TTR reductions were seen regardless of TTR mutation, sex, age, or race [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>Inotersen is an antisense oligonucleotide that causes degradation of mutant and wild-type TTR mRNA through binding to the TTR mRNA, which results in a reduction of serum TTR protein and TTR protein deposits in tissues [FDA label], [F1938].</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity>There are a wide variety of warnings on the [FDA label] of this drug. They have been summarized below. See [FDA label] for specific guidelines on prevention/management of these effects:&#13;
&#13;
**Thrombocytopenia**&#13;
&#13;
Inotersen causes reductions in platelet count that can result in sudden and unpredictable thrombocytopenia that can be life-threatening.  Monitor CBC at regular intervals and adjust/pause treatment as necessary. Do not initiate treatment with this drug in patients with a platelet count below 100 x 10^9/L [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
**Glomerulonephritis and Renal Toxicity**&#13;
&#13;
Inotersen can cause glomerulonephritis that may result in dialysis-dependent renal failure [FDA label], [A39495].  It may also exacerbate pre-existing renal dysfunction. Monitor kidney function before and during treatment [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
**Stroke and Cervicocephalic Arterial Dissection**&#13;
&#13;
Inotersen may cause stroke and cervicocephalic arterial dissection [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
**Inflammatory and Immune Effects**&#13;
&#13;
Inflammatory and immune changes are an expected side effect of some antisense oligonucleotide drugs, including inotersen. In clinical studies, serious inflammatory and immune adverse reactions occurred in Inotersen-treated patients, including immune thrombocytopenia and glomerulonephritis, as well as one case of antineutrophil cytoplasmic autoantibody (ANCA)- positive systemic vasculitis [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
**Liver Effects**&#13;
&#13;
The liver is a possible site of accumulation of antisense oligonucleotides. In clinical studies, 8% of inotersen-treated patients had an increased alanine aminotransferase (ALT) at least 3 times the upper limit of normal (ULN), compared to 3% of patients on placebo; 3% of inotersen-treated patients had an ALT at least 8 times the upper limit of normal, compared to no patient on placebo.  Monitor liver function tests as indicated on the FDA label [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
**Hypersensitivity Reactions/Antibody Formation**&#13;
&#13;
Most of these reactions occur within 2 hours of administration of inotersen and included headache, chest pain, hypertension, chills, flushing, dysphagia, palmar erythema, eosinophilia, involuntary choreaform movements, arthralgia, myalgia, and flu-like symptoms [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
**Reduced Serum Vitamin A Levels**&#13;
&#13;
Inotersen treatment leads to a decrease in serum vitamin A levels. Supplementation at the recommended daily allowance of vitamin A is advised for patients taking this drug [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
**Cardiac QT prolongation**&#13;
&#13;
Formal QTc studies have not been conducted with this drug. The risk of QTc prolongation with inotersen was evaluated in a randomized, placebo-controlled trial in healthy volunteers. No major changes in the mean QTc interval (&gt;20 ms) were detected in the trial.&#13;
In the 66-week controlled efficacy trial, 5.4% of the treated patients showed evidence of QRS prolongation on their electrocardiograms (ECGs) to greater than 160 msec and greater than 25% above baseline, compared to and in 1.7% of patients on placebo [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
**Effects on pregnancy**&#13;
&#13;
There are no or limited amount of data from the use of inotersen in pregnant women. Animal studies are insufficient with respect to reproductive toxicity. There are no or limited amount of data from the ingestion of inotersen in pregnant women. Animal studies are not sufficient with respect to reproductive toxicity [F1938].</toxicity>
  <metabolism>Inotersen is metabolized by nucleases to nucleotides of various lengths [FDA label].</metabolism>
  <absorption>Following subcutaneous administration, inotersen is absorbed rapidly into systemic circulation in a dose-dependent fashion, with the median time to maximum plasma concentrations (Cmax) of 2 to 4 hours [FDA label].</absorption>
  <half-life>The terminal elimination half-life is 32.3 (29.4, 35.5) days [FDA label].</half-life>
  <protein-binding>Inotersen is highly bound to human plasma proteins (&gt;94%) and the fraction bound is independent of drug concentration [FDA label], [F1938].</protein-binding>
  <route-of-elimination>Mainly cleared through metabolism [FDA label].</route-of-elimination>
  <volume-of-distribution>Rapidly distributes broadly to tissues, with the highest concentrations observed in the kidney and liver. This drug does not cross the blood-brain barrier [FDA label].</volume-of-distribution>
  <clearance>Inotersen is mainly cleared through metabolism, and the total body clearance (mean and 90% confidence interval) is 3.18 (3.08, 3.29) L/h [FDA label].</clearance>
  <salts>
    <salt>
      <drugbank-id primary="true">DBSALT002811</drugbank-id>
      <name>Inotersen sodium</name>
      <unii>950736UC77</unii>
      <cas-number>1432726-13-0</cas-number>
      <inchikey/>
    </salt>
  </salts>
  <synonyms/>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>Tegsedi</name>
      <labeller>Akcea Therapeutics Inc</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>02481383</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2019-01-07</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>284 mg</strength>
      <route>Subcutaneous</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Tegsedi</name>
      <labeller>Akcea Therapeutics, Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>72126-007</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2018-10-05</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>284 mg/1.5mL</strength>
      <route>Subcutaneous</route>
      <fda-application-number>NDA211172</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>Tegsedi</name>
      <ingredients>Inotersen</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Tegsedi</name>
      <ingredients>Inotersen</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Antisense Elements (Genetics)</category>
      <mesh-id>D016375</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Carbohydrates</category>
      <mesh-id>D002241</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Compounds used in a research, industrial, or household setting</category>
      <mesh-id>D020313</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Decreased RNA Integrity</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Diagnostic Uses of Chemicals</category>
      <mesh-id>D064907</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>DNA</category>
      <mesh-id>D004247</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>DNA, Antisense</category>
      <mesh-id>D016373</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Glycosides</category>
      <mesh-id>D006027</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Increased Protein Breakdown</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Laboratory Chemicals</category>
      <mesh-id>D019995</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Miscellaneous Central Nervous System Agents</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Molecular Probes</category>
      <mesh-id>D015335</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nephrotoxic agents</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nucleic Acid Probes</category>
      <mesh-id>D015341</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nucleic Acids</category>
      <mesh-id>D009696</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nucleic Acids, Nucleotides, and Nucleosides</category>
      <mesh-id>D009706</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nucleotides</category>
      <mesh-id>D009711</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Oligodeoxyribonucleotides, Antisense</category>
      <mesh-id>D020319</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Oligonucleotides</category>
      <mesh-id>D009841</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Oligonucleotides, Antisense</category>
      <mesh-id>D016376</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Polynucleotides</category>
      <mesh-id>D011119</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Potential QTc-Prolonging Agents</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>QTc Prolonging Agents</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Transthyretin-directed RNA Interaction</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Injection, solution</form>
      <route>Subcutaneous</route>
      <strength>284 mg/1.5mL</strength>
    </dosage>
    <dosage>
      <form>Solution</form>
      <route>Subcutaneous</route>
      <strength>284 mg</strength>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes>
    <ahfs-code>28:92.00</ahfs-code>
  </ahfs-codes>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <fda-label>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/fda_labels/DB14713.pdf?1539101110</fda-label>
  <patents>
    <patent>
      <number>7015315</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2006-03-21</approved>
      <expires>2023-03-21</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
    <patent>
      <number>7101993</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2006-09-05</approved>
      <expires>2023-09-05</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
    <patent>
      <number>9399774</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2016-07-26</approved>
      <expires>2031-04-29</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
    <patent>
      <number>9061044</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2015-06-23</approved>
      <expires>2031-04-29</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
    <patent>
      <number>8697860</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2014-04-15</approved>
      <expires>2031-04-29</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
    <patent>
      <number>8101743</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2012-01-24</approved>
      <expires>2025-04-01</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
  </patents>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00529</drugbank-id>
      <name>Foscarnet</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Foscarnet.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00742</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mannitol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Mannitol is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00300</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenofovir disoproxil</name>
      <description>Inotersen may increase the nephrotoxic activities of Tenofovir disoproxil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09299</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenofovir alafenamide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may increase the nephrotoxic activities of Tenofovir alafenamide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14126</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenofovir</name>
      <description>Inotersen may increase the nephrotoxic activities of Tenofovir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00091</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclosporine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cyclosporine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00159</drugbank-id>
      <name>Icosapent</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Icosapent is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00229</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefotiam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefotiam is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00244</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mesalazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Mesalazine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00267</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefmenoxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefmenoxime is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00274</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefmetazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefmetazole is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00328</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indomethacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Indomethacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00384</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triamterene</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Triamterene is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00430</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefpiramide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefpiramide is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00447</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loracarbef</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Loracarbef is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00452</drugbank-id>
      <name>Framycetin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Framycetin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00456</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefalotin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefalotin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00461</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nabumetone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Nabumetone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00465</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketorolac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ketorolac is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00469</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenoxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tenoxicam is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00479</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amikacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00482</drugbank-id>
      <name>Celecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Celecoxib is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00493</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefotaxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefotaxime is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00500</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolmetin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tolmetin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00533</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rofecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Rofecoxib is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00573</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Fenoprofen is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00580</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valdecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Valdecoxib is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00586</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diclofenac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Diclofenac is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00605</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulindac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Sulindac is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00626</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bacitracin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Bacitracin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00681</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amphotericin B</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amphotericin B is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00684</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tobramycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tobramycin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00689</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cephaloglycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cephaloglycin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00718</drugbank-id>
      <name>Adefovir dipivoxil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Adefovir dipivoxil is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00784</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mefenamic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Mefenamic acid is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00788</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naproxen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Naproxen is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00795</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfasalazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Sulfasalazine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00798</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gentamicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Gentamicin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00812</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenylbutazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Phenylbutazone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00814</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meloxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Meloxicam is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00821</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Carprofen is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00864</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tacrolimus</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tacrolimus is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00903</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etacrynic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Etacrynic acid is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00923</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceforanide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ceforanide is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00936</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salicylic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Salicylic acid is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00945</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetylsalicylic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Acetylsalicylic acid is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00955</drugbank-id>
      <name>Netilmicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Netilmicin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00994</drugbank-id>
      <name>Neomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Neomycin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00999</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrochlorothiazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Hydrochlorothiazide is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01014</drugbank-id>
      <name>Balsalazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Balsalazide is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01066</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefditoren</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefditoren is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01072</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atazanavir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Atazanavir is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01082</drugbank-id>
      <name>Streptomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Streptomycin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01111</drugbank-id>
      <name>Colistimethate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Colistimethate is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01112</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefuroxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefuroxime is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01139</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefapirin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefapirin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01150</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefprozil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefprozil is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01172</drugbank-id>
      <name>Kanamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Kanamycin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01250</drugbank-id>
      <name>Olsalazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Olsalazine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01283</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lumiracoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Lumiracoxib is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01326</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefamandole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefamandole is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01327</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefazolin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefazolin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01328</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefonicid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefonicid is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01329</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefoperazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefoperazone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01331</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefoxitin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefoxitin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01332</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftizoxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ceftizoxime is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01397</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium salicylate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Magnesium salicylate is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01399</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salsalate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Salsalate is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01401</drugbank-id>
      <name>Choline magnesium trisalicylate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Choline magnesium trisalicylate is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01413</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefepime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefepime is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01414</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefacetrile</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefacetrile is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01416</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefpodoxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefpodoxime is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01419</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antrafenine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Antrafenine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01421</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paromomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Paromomycin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01424</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aminophenazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Aminophenazone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01435</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antipyrine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Antipyrine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01600</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiaprofenic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tiaprofenic acid is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01628</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etoricoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Etoricoxib is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02247</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrolyzed Cephalothin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Hydrolyzed Cephalothin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03450</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cephalothin Group</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cephalothin Group is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03585</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxyphenbutazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Oxyphenbutazone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ribostamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ribostamycin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04263</drugbank-id>
      <name>Geneticin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Geneticin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04552</drugbank-id>
      <name>Niflumic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Niflumic acid is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04570</drugbank-id>
      <name>Latamoxef</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Latamoxef is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04626</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apramycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Apramycin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04729</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gentamicin C1a</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Gentamicin C1a is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04743</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nimesulide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Nimesulide is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04808</drugbank-id>
      <name>Neamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Neamine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04812</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benoxaprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Benoxaprofen is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metamizole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Metamizole is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04828</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zomepirac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Zomepirac is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04918</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftobiprole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ceftobiprole is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05095</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cimicoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cimicoxib is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06590</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftaroline fosamil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ceftaroline fosamil is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06696</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arbekacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Arbekacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06725</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lornoxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Lornoxicam is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06737</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zaltoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Zaltoprofen is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07402</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azapropazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Azapropazone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07477</drugbank-id>
      <name>Felbinac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Felbinac is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08437</drugbank-id>
      <name>Puromycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Puromycin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08439</drugbank-id>
      <name>Parecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Parecoxib is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08797</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salicylamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Salicylamide is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08940</drugbank-id>
      <name>Kebuzone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Kebuzone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08942</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isoxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Isoxicam is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08951</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Indoprofen is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08955</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibuproxam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ibuproxam is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08976</drugbank-id>
      <name>Floctafenine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Floctafenine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08981</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenbufen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Fenbufen is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08984</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etofenamate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Etofenamate is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08991</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epirizole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Epirizole is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09008</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefaloridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefaloridine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09062</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefminox</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefminox is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09212</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loxoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Loxoprofen is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexibuprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Dexibuprofen is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09215</drugbank-id>
      <name>Droxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Droxicam is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09216</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolfenamic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tolfenamic acid is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09217</drugbank-id>
      <name>Firocoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Firocoxib is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clonixin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Clonixin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09285</drugbank-id>
      <name>Morniflumate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Morniflumate is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09295</drugbank-id>
      <name>Talniflumate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Talniflumate is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11455</drugbank-id>
      <name>Robenacoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Robenacoxib is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11466</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tepoxalin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tepoxalin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11512</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dihydrostreptomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Dihydrostreptomycin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11518</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flunixin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Flunixin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11520</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hygromycin B</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Hygromycin B is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11935</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flomoxef</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Flomoxef is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12445</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitroaspirin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Nitroaspirin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12545</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indobufen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Indobufen is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12604</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sisomicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Sisomicin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13001</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tinoridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tinoridine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13217</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fentiazac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Fentiazac is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13232</drugbank-id>
      <name>Suxibuzone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Suxibuzone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13266</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefatrizine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefatrizine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13270</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dibekacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Dibekacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13274</drugbank-id>
      <name>Micronomicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Micronomicin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13286</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bumadizone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Bumadizone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13314</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alminoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Alminoprofen is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flunoxaprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Flunoxaprofen is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13364</drugbank-id>
      <name>Feprazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Feprazone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13371</drugbank-id>
      <name>Difenpiramide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Difenpiramide is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13407</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nifenazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Nifenazone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13432</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lonazolac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Lonazolac is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13461</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefcapene</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefcapene is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13470</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefodizime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefodizime is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13481</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenidap</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tenidap is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13499</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefsulodin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefsulodin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13501</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bendazac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Bendazac is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13504</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefetamet</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefetamet is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13514</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pranoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Pranoprofen is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13524</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propyphenazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Propyphenazone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13527</drugbank-id>
      <name>Proglumetacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Proglumetacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13538</drugbank-id>
      <name>Guacetisal</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Guacetisal is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13540</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isepamicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Isepamicin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13544</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethenzamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ethenzamide is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13612</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbaspirin calcium</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Carbaspirin calcium is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13629</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mofebutazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Mofebutazone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13638</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefbuperazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefbuperazone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13649</drugbank-id>
      <name>Proquazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Proquazone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13657</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benorilate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Benorilate is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13667</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefozopran</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefozopran is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13673</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bekanamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Bekanamycin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13682</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefpirome</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefpirome is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13722</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pirprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Pirprofen is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13778</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefazedone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefazedone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acemetacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Acemetacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13821</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftezole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ceftezole is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13860</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imidazole salicylate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Imidazole salicylate is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13868</drugbank-id>
      <name>Adefovir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Adefovir is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14059</drugbank-id>
      <name>SC-236</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when SC-236 is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14060</drugbank-id>
      <name>NS-398</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when NS-398 is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01438</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenazopyridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Phenazopyridine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15066</drugbank-id>
      <name>Givosiran</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00007</drugbank-id>
      <name>Leuprolide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Leuprolide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00014</drugbank-id>
      <name>Goserelin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Goserelin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00195</drugbank-id>
      <name>Betaxolol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Betaxolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00199</drugbank-id>
      <name>Erythromycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Erythromycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00207</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azithromycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Azithromycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moxifloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Moxifloxacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00243</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ranolazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Ranolazine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00263</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfisoxazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Sulfisoxazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00333</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methadone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Methadone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00343</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diltiazem</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Diltiazem.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00363</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clozapine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Clozapine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00391</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulpiride</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Sulpiride.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00393</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nimodipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Nimodipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00420</drugbank-id>
      <name>Promazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Promazine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00433</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prochlorperazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Prochlorperazine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00450</drugbank-id>
      <name>Droperidol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Droperidol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00477</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorpromazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Chlorpromazine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00502</drugbank-id>
      <name>Haloperidol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Haloperidol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00526</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxaliplatin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Oxaliplatin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00537</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ciprofloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Ciprofloxacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00544</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluorouracil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Fluorouracil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00556</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perflutren</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Perflutren.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00568</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cinnarizine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Cinnarizine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00571</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propranolol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Propranolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00572</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atropine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Atropine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00608</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chloroquine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Chloroquine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00625</drugbank-id>
      <name>Efavirenz</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Efavirenz.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00640</drugbank-id>
      <name>Adenosine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Adenosine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00738</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentamidine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Pentamidine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00743</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gadobenic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Gadobenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00748</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbinoxamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Carbinoxamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00757</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dolasetron</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Dolasetron.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00778</drugbank-id>
      <name>Roxithromycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Roxithromycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00779</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nalidixic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Nalidixic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00827</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cinoxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Cinoxacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00836</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loperamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Loperamide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00889</drugbank-id>
      <name>Granisetron</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Granisetron.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00904</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ondansetron</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Ondansetron.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00922</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levosimendan</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Levosimendan.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00933</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mesoridazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Mesoridazine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00950</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fexofenadine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Fexofenadine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00967</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desloratadine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Desloratadine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00976</drugbank-id>
      <name>Telithromycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Telithromycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00978</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lomefloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Lomefloxacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00985</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dimenhydrinate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Dimenhydrinate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01087</drugbank-id>
      <name>Primaquine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Primaquine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01113</drugbank-id>
      <name>Papaverine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Papaverine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01114</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorpheniramine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Chlorpheniramine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01115</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nifedipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Nifedipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01137</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levofloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Levofloxacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01155</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemifloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Gemifloxacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01165</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ofloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Ofloxacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01182</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propafenone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Propafenone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01193</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acebutolol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Acebutolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01195</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flecainide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Flecainide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01211</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clarithromycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Clarithromycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01227</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levacetylmethadol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Levacetylmethadol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01232</drugbank-id>
      <name>Saquinavir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Saquinavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01388</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mibefradil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Mibefradil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01580</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxprenolol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Oxprenolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01599</drugbank-id>
      <name>Probucol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Probucol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aceprometazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Aceprometazine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02638</drugbank-id>
      <name>Terlipressin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Terlipressin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04825</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prenylamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Prenylamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04842</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluspirilene</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Fluspirilene.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04957</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azimilide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Azimilide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05223</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pracinostat</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Pracinostat.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05488</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m ciprofloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Technetium Tc-99m ciprofloxacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06160</drugbank-id>
      <name>Garenoxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Garenoxacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06200</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tedisamil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Tedisamil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06334</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tucidinostat</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Tucidinostat.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06402</drugbank-id>
      <name>Telavancin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Telavancin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06589</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pazopanib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Pazopanib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06600</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nemonoxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Nemonoxacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06603</drugbank-id>
      <name>Panobinostat</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Panobinostat.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06712</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nilvadipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Nilvadipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08799</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antazoline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Antazoline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08865</drugbank-id>
      <name>Crizotinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Crizotinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08903</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bedaquiline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Bedaquiline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08952</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indenolol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Indenolol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08980</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fendiline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Fendiline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08992</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eperisone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Eperisone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09016</drugbank-id>
      <name>Butriptyline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Butriptyline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09063</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceritinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Ceritinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09078</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lenvatinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Lenvatinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09224</drugbank-id>
      <name>Melperone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Melperone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09231</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benidipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Benidipine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09555</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexchlorpheniramine maleate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Dexchlorpheniramine maleate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11640</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amifampridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Amifampridine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11830</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mocetinostat</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Mocetinostat.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11841</drugbank-id>
      <name>Entinostat</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Entinostat.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12141</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gilteritinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Gilteritinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12174</drugbank-id>
      <name>CUDC-101</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with CUDC-101.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12286</drugbank-id>
      <name>Simendan</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Simendan.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12376</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ricolinostat</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Ricolinostat.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12523</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mizolastine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Mizolastine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12565</drugbank-id>
      <name>Abexinostat</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Abexinostat.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12877</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxatomide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Oxatomide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13261</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sitafloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Sitafloxacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13273</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sultopride</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Sultopride.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13500</drugbank-id>
      <name>Otilonium</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Otilonium.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13546</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nizofenone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Nizofenone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13652</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bunaftine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Bunaftine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13653</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lorcainide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Lorcainide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13679</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexchlorpheniramine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Dexchlorpheniramine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13791</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penfluridol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Penfluridol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14063</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexverapamil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Dexverapamil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14568</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ivosidenib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Ivosidenib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01224</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quetiapine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Quetiapine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00204</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dofetilide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Dofetilide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00215</drugbank-id>
      <name>Citalopram</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Citalopram.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00246</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ziprasidone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Ziprasidone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00261</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anagrelide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Anagrelide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00280</drugbank-id>
      <name>Disopyramide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Disopyramide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00283</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clemastine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Clemastine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00308</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibutilide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Ibutilide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00313</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valproic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Valproic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00342</drugbank-id>
      <name>Terfenadine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Terfenadine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00365</drugbank-id>
      <name>Grepafloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Grepafloxacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00468</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Quinine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00472</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluoxetine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Fluoxetine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00489</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sotalol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Sotalol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00530</drugbank-id>
      <name>Erlotinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Erlotinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00539</drugbank-id>
      <name>Toremifene</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Toremifene.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00604</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cisapride</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Cisapride.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00619</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imatinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Imatinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00637</drugbank-id>
      <name>Astemizole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Astemizole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00679</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thioridazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Thioridazine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00685</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trovafloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Trovafloxacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00834</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mifepristone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Mifepristone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00875</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flupentixol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Flupentixol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00907</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cocaine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Cocaine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01100</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pimozide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Pimozide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01118</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amiodarone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Amiodarone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01169</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arsenic trioxide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Arsenic trioxide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01175</drugbank-id>
      <name>Escitalopram</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Escitalopram.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01184</drugbank-id>
      <name>Domperidone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Domperidone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sparfloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Sparfloxacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Halofantrine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Halofantrine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01244</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bepridil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Bepridil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01267</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paliperidone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Paliperidone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01405</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temafloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Temafloxacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01601</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lopinavir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Lopinavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01624</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zuclopenthixol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Zuclopenthixol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04844</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetrabenazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Tetrabenazine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04855</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dronedarone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Dronedarone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04868</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nilotinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Nilotinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04946</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iloperidone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Iloperidone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05294</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vandetanib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Vandetanib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06176</drugbank-id>
      <name>Romidepsin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Romidepsin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06216</drugbank-id>
      <name>Asenapine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Asenapine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06697</drugbank-id>
      <name>Artemether</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Artemether.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06708</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lumefantrine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Lumefantrine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08881</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vemurafenib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Vemurafenib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09039</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eliglustat</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Eliglustat.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09083</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ivabradine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Ivabradine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11730</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ribociclib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Ribociclib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11978</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glasdegib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Glasdegib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12161</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deutetrabenazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Deutetrabenazine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13074</drugbank-id>
      <name>Macimorelin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Macimorelin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13725</drugbank-id>
      <name>Terodiline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Terodiline.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11637</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delamanid</name>
      <description>Inotersen may increase the QTc-prolonging activities of Delamanid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00282</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pamidronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Pamidronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00399</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zoledronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Zoledronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00630</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alendronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Alendronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00710</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibandronate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Ibandronate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00720</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clodronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Clodronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00884</drugbank-id>
      <name>Risedronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Risedronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01077</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etidronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Etidronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01133</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiludronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Tiludronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06255</drugbank-id>
      <name>Incadronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00104</drugbank-id>
      <name>Octreotide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Octreotide is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00107</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxytocin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Oxytocin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00187</drugbank-id>
      <name>Esmolol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Esmolol is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00188</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bortezomib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Bortezomib is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00220</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nelfinavir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Nelfinavir is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00334</drugbank-id>
      <name>Olanzapine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Olanzapine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00344</drugbank-id>
      <name>Protriptyline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Protriptyline is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00346</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alfuzosin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Alfuzosin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00347</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimethadione</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Trimethadione is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00354</drugbank-id>
      <name>Buclizine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Buclizine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00358</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mefloquine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Mefloquine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00366</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxylamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Doxylamine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00370</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mirtazapine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Mirtazapine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00374</drugbank-id>
      <name>Treprostinil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Treprostinil is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00381</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amlodipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Amlodipine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00405</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexbrompheniramine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Dexbrompheniramine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00424</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hyoscyamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Hyoscyamine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00427</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triprolidine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Triprolidine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00434</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyproheptadine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Cyproheptadine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00467</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enoxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Enoxacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00487</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pefloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Pefloxacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00503</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ritonavir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Ritonavir is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00540</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nortriptyline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Nortriptyline is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00543</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amoxapine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Amoxapine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00557</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydroxyzine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Hydroxyzine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00582</drugbank-id>
      <name>Voriconazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Voriconazole is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00593</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethosuximide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Ethosuximide is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00613</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amodiaquine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Amodiaquine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00622</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nicardipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Nicardipine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00675</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tamoxifen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Tamoxifen is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00678</drugbank-id>
      <name>Losartan</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Losartan is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00680</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moricizine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Moricizine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00691</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moexipril</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Moexipril is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00697</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tizanidine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Tizanidine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00714</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apomorphine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Apomorphine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00719</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azatadine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Azatadine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00726</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimipramine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Trimipramine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00734</drugbank-id>
      <name>Risperidone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Risperidone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00753</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isoflurane</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Isoflurane is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rosoxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Rosoxacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00818</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propofol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Propofol is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00822</drugbank-id>
      <name>Disulfiram</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Disulfiram is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00825</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levomenthol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Levomenthol is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00835</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brompheniramine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Brompheniramine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00862</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vardenafil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Vardenafil is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00916</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metronidazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Metronidazole is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00920</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketotifen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Ketotifen is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00927</drugbank-id>
      <name>Famotidine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Famotidine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00938</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salmeterol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Salmeterol is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00949</drugbank-id>
      <name>Felbamate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Felbamate is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00983</drugbank-id>
      <name>Formoterol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Formoterol is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01023</drugbank-id>
      <name>Felodipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Felodipine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01026</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketoconazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Ketoconazole is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01044</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gatifloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Gatifloxacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01054</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitrendipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Nitrendipine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01059</drugbank-id>
      <name>Norfloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Norfloxacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01071</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mequitazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Mequitazine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01074</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perhexiline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Perhexiline is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01075</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diphenhydramine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Diphenhydramine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01106</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levocabastine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Levocabastine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01158</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bretylium</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Bretylium is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01167</drugbank-id>
      <name>Itraconazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Itraconazole is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01173</drugbank-id>
      <name>Orphenadrine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Orphenadrine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01176</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclizine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Cyclizine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01189</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desflurane</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Desflurane is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01228</drugbank-id>
      <name>Encainide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Encainide is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01236</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sevoflurane</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Sevoflurane is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01238</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aripiprazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Aripiprazole is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01239</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorprothixene</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Chlorprothixene is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01246</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alimemazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Alimemazine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01254</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dasatinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Dasatinib is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01259</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lapatinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Lapatinib is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01263</drugbank-id>
      <name>Posaconazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Posaconazole is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01268</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sunitinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Sunitinib is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01396</drugbank-id>
      <name>Digitoxin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Digitoxin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01403</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methotrimeprazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Methotrimeprazine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01426</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ajmaline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Ajmaline is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01591</drugbank-id>
      <name>Solifenacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Solifenacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01611</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydroxychloroquine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Hydroxychloroquine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01620</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pheniramine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Pheniramine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01623</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiothixene</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Thiothixene is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02546</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vorinostat</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Vorinostat is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04576</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fleroxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Fleroxacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04695</drugbank-id>
      <name>Farnesyl thiopyrophosphate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Farnesyl thiopyrophosphate is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04846</drugbank-id>
      <name>Celiprolol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Celiprolol is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05039</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indacaterol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Indacaterol is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05246</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methsuximide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Methsuximide is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05465</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tandutinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Tandutinib is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06217</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vernakalant</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Vernakalant is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06283</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ziconotide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Ziconotide is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06288</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amisulpride</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Amisulpride is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06468</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cariporide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Cariporide is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06663</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pasireotide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Pasireotide is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06691</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mepyramine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Mepyramine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06699</drugbank-id>
      <name>Degarelix</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Degarelix is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06719</drugbank-id>
      <name>Buserelin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Buserelin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06788</drugbank-id>
      <name>Histrelin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Histrelin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06825</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triptorelin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Triptorelin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07780</drugbank-id>
      <name>Farnesyl diphosphate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Farnesyl diphosphate is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07841</drugbank-id>
      <name>Geranylgeranyl diphosphate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Geranylgeranyl diphosphate is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08808</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bupranolol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Bupranolol is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08815</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lurasidone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Lurasidone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08864</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rilpivirine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Rilpivirine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08868</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fingolimod</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Fingolimod is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08871</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eribulin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Eribulin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08912</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dabrafenib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Dabrafenib is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08936</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorcyclizine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Chlorcyclizine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08972</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flumequine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Flumequine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09080</drugbank-id>
      <name>Olodaterol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Olodaterol is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09090</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pinaverium</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Pinaverium is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09167</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dosulepin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Dosulepin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09229</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aranidipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Aranidipine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09235</drugbank-id>
      <name>Efonidipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Efonidipine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09236</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lacidipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Lacidipine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09239</drugbank-id>
      <name>Niguldipine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Niguldipine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11390</drugbank-id>
      <name>Coumaphos</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Coumaphos is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11397</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dichlorvos</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Dichlorvos is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11408</drugbank-id>
      <name>Famphur</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Famphur is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11412</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenthion</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Fenthion is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11443</drugbank-id>
      <name>Orbifloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Orbifloxacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11448</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phosmet</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Phosmet is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11491</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sarafloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Sarafloxacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11511</drugbank-id>
      <name>Difloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Difloxacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11591</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bilastine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Bilastine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11614</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rupatadine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Rupatadine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11742</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ebastine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Ebastine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11770</drugbank-id>
      <name>Talinolol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Talinolol is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11774</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pazufloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Pazufloxacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11785</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anisodamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Anisodamine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11891</drugbank-id>
      <name>CUDC-907</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when CUDC-907 is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11892</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prulifloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Prulifloxacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12093</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetrahydropalmatine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Tetrahydropalmatine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12231</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temefos</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Temefos is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12245</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triclabendazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Triclabendazole is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12645</drugbank-id>
      <name>Givinostat</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Givinostat is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12712</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pilsicainide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Pilsicainide is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12766</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cicletanine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Cicletanine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12923</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gallopamil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Gallopamil is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13358</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cibenzoline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Cibenzoline is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13488</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bencyclane</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Bencyclane is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13555</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prajmaline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Prajmaline is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13627</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxolinic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Oxolinic acid is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13651</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lorajmine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Lorajmine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13691</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetyldigoxin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Acetyldigoxin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13744</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piromidic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Piromidic acid is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13766</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lidoflazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Lidoflazine is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13772</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rufloxacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Rufloxacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13823</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pipemidic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Pipemidic acid is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14185</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aripiprazole lauroxil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Aripiprazole lauroxil is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00017</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salmon Calcitonin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Salmon Calcitonin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00035</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desmopressin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Desmopressin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00041</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aldesleukin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Aldesleukin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00080</drugbank-id>
      <name>Daptomycin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Daptomycin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00081</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tositumomab</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tositumomab which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00115</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyanocobalamin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Cyanocobalamin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00158</drugbank-id>
      <name>Folic acid</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Folic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00165</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pyridoxine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pyridoxine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00176</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluvoxamine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Fluvoxamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00182</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amphetamine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Amphetamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00185</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cevimeline</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Cevimeline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00186</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lorazepam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Lorazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00190</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbidopa</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Carbidopa which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00193</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tramadol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tramadol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00196</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluconazole</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Fluconazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00198</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oseltamivir</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Oseltamivir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00200</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydroxocobalamin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Hydroxocobalamin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00206</drugbank-id>
      <name>Reserpine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Reserpine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ticlopidine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ticlopidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pantoprazole</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pantoprazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00225</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gadodiamide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Gadodiamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00230</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pregabalin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pregabalin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00231</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temazepam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Temazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00235</drugbank-id>
      <name>Milrinone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Milrinone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00237</drugbank-id>
      <name>Butabarbital</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Butabarbital which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00245</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benzatropine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Benzatropine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00254</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxycycline</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Doxycycline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00262</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carmustine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Carmustine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metoprolol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Metoprolol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00270</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isradipine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Isradipine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00271</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diatrizoate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Diatrizoate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00273</drugbank-id>
      <name>Topiramate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Topiramate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00279</drugbank-id>
      <name>Liothyronine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Liothyronine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00284</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acarbose</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Acarbose which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00285</drugbank-id>
      <name>Venlafaxine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Venlafaxine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00286</drugbank-id>
      <name>Conjugated estrogens</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Conjugated estrogens which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00289</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atomoxetine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Atomoxetine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00290</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bleomycin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Bleomycin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00292</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etomidate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Etomidate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00294</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etonogestrel</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Etonogestrel which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00296</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ropivacaine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ropivacaine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00303</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ertapenem</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ertapenem which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00312</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentobarbital</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pentobarbital which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00316</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetaminophen</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Acetaminophen which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00319</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piperacillin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Piperacillin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00322</drugbank-id>
      <name>Floxuridine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Floxuridine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00323</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolcapone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tolcapone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00325</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitroprusside</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Nitroprusside which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00327</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydromorphone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Hydromorphone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00330</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethambutol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ethambutol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00331</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metformin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Metformin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00339</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pyrazinamide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pyrazinamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00341</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cetirizine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Cetirizine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00349</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clobazam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Clobazam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00351</drugbank-id>
      <name>Megestrol acetate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Megestrol acetate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00355</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aztreonam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Aztreonam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00356</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorzoxazone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Chlorzoxazone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00359</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfadiazine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Sulfadiazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00364</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sucralfate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Sucralfate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00369</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cidofovir</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Cidofovir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00372</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiethylperazine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Thiethylperazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00373</drugbank-id>
      <name>Timolol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Timolol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00377</drugbank-id>
      <name>Palonosetron</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Palonosetron which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00380</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexrazoxane</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Dexrazoxane which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00398</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sorafenib</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Sorafenib which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00401</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nisoldipine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Nisoldipine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00402</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eszopiclone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Eszopiclone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00404</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alprazolam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Alprazolam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00412</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rosiglitazone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Rosiglitazone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00413</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pramipexole</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pramipexole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00415</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ampicillin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ampicillin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00418</drugbank-id>
      <name>Secobarbital</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Secobarbital which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00422</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylphenidate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Methylphenidate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00432</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trifluridine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Trifluridine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00435</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitric Oxide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Nitric Oxide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00437</drugbank-id>
      <name>Allopurinol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Allopurinol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00438</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftazidime</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ceftazidime which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00440</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimethoprim</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Trimethoprim which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00441</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemcitabine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Gemcitabine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00476</drugbank-id>
      <name>Duloxetine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Duloxetine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00480</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lenalidomide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Lenalidomide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00490</drugbank-id>
      <name>Buspirone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Buspirone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00492</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosinopril</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Fosinopril which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00499</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flutamide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Flutamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00501</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cimetidine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Cimetidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00524</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metolazone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Metolazone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00535</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefdinir</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Cefdinir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00548</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azelaic acid</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Azelaic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00552</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentostatin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pentostatin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00553</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methoxsalen</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Methoxsalen which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00554</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piroxicam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Piroxicam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00555</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lamotrigine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Lamotrigine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00558</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zanamivir</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Zanamivir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00563</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methotrexate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Methotrexate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00567</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cephalexin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Cephalexin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00569</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fondaparinux</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Fondaparinux which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00577</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valaciclovir</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Valaciclovir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00583</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levocarnitine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Levocarnitine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00591</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluocinolone acetonide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Fluocinolone acetonide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00597</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gadoteridol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Gadoteridol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00598</drugbank-id>
      <name>Labetalol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Labetalol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00603</drugbank-id>
      <name>Medroxyprogesterone acetate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Medroxyprogesterone acetate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00612</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bisoprolol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Bisoprolol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00624</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Testosterone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00628</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clorazepic acid</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Clorazepic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00631</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clofarabine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Clofarabine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00633</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexmedetomidine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Dexmedetomidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00635</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Prednisone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00651</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dyphylline</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Dyphylline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00657</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mecamylamine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Mecamylamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00660</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metaxalone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Metaxalone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00661</drugbank-id>
      <name>Verapamil</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Verapamil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00665</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nilutamide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Nilutamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00669</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sumatriptan</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Sumatriptan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00672</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorpropamide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Chlorpropamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00674</drugbank-id>
      <name>Galantamine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Galantamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00683</drugbank-id>
      <name>Midazolam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Midazolam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00688</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mycophenolate mofetil</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Mycophenolate mofetil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00690</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flurazepam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Flurazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00692</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phentolamine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Phentolamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00695</drugbank-id>
      <name>Furosemide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Furosemide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00698</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitrofurantoin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Nitrofurantoin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00706</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tamsulosin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tamsulosin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00709</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lamivudine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Lamivudine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00712</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flurbiprofen</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Flurbiprofen which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00713</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxacillin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Oxacillin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00716</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nedocromil</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Nedocromil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00722</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lisinopril</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Lisinopril which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00730</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiabendazole</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Thiabendazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00731</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nateglinide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Nateglinide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00733</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pralidoxime</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pralidoxime which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00749</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etodolac</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Etodolac which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00759</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetracycline</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tetracycline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00760</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meropenem</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Meropenem which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00761</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium chloride</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Potassium chloride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00763</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methimazole</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Methimazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00775</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tirofiban</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tirofiban which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00780</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenelzine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Phenelzine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00782</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propantheline</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Propantheline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Estradiol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00787</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acyclovir</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Acyclovir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00789</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gadopentetic acid</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Gadopentetic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00790</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perindopril</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Perindopril which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00800</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenoldopam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Fenoldopam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00804</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dicyclomine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Dicyclomine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00806</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentoxifylline</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pentoxifylline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00808</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indapamide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Indapamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00811</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ribavirin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ribavirin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00820</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tadalafil</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tadalafil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00828</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosfomycin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Fosfomycin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00829</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diazepam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Diazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00833</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefaclor</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Cefaclor which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00839</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolazamide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tolazamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00841</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dobutamine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Dobutamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00842</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxazepam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Oxazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00851</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dacarbazine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Dacarbazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00853</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temozolomide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Temozolomide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00861</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diflunisal</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Diflunisal which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00863</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ranitidine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ranitidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00871</drugbank-id>
      <name>Terbutaline</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Terbutaline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00887</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bumetanide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Bumetanide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00894</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testolactone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Testolactone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00897</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triazolam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Triazolam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00900</drugbank-id>
      <name>Didanosine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Didanosine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00909</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zonisamide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Zonisamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00911</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tinidazole</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tinidazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00915</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amantadine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Amantadine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00918</drugbank-id>
      <name>Almotriptan</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Almotriptan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00928</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azacitidine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Azacitidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00934</drugbank-id>
      <name>Maprotiline</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Maprotiline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00939</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meclofenamic acid</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Meclofenamic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00951</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isoniazid</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Isoniazid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00953</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rizatriptan</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Rizatriptan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00958</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carboplatin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Carboplatin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00960</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pindolol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pindolol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00961</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mepivacaine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Mepivacaine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00962</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zaleplon</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Zaleplon which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00968</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methyldopa</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Methyldopa which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00980</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ramelteon</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ramelteon which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00988</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dopamine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Dopamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00991</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxaprozin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Oxaprozin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00993</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azathioprine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Azathioprine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00995</drugbank-id>
      <name>Auranofin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Auranofin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01001</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salbutamol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Salbutamol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01002</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levobupivacaine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Levobupivacaine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01004</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ganciclovir</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ganciclovir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01009</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketoprofen</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ketoprofen which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01010</drugbank-id>
      <name>Edrophonium</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Edrophonium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01011</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metyrapone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Metyrapone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01015</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfamethoxazole</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Sulfamethoxazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01018</drugbank-id>
      <name>Guanfacine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Guanfacine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01020</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isosorbide mononitrate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Isosorbide mononitrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01022</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phylloquinone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Phylloquinone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01024</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mycophenolic acid</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Mycophenolic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01030</drugbank-id>
      <name>Topotecan</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Topotecan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01032</drugbank-id>
      <name>Probenecid</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Probenecid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01036</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolterodine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tolterodine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01039</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenofibrate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Fenofibrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01043</drugbank-id>
      <name>Memantine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Memantine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01046</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lubiprostone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Lubiprostone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01048</drugbank-id>
      <name>Abacavir</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Abacavir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01050</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibuprofen</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ibuprofen which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01060</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amoxicillin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Amoxicillin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01067</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glipizide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Glipizide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01068</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clonazepam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Clonazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01069</drugbank-id>
      <name>Promethazine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Promethazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01093</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dimethyl sulfoxide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Dimethyl sulfoxide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01099</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flucytosine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Flucytosine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01101</drugbank-id>
      <name>Capecitabine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Capecitabine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01105</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sibutramine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Sibutramine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01124</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolbutamide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tolbutamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01129</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rabeprazole</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Rabeprazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01135</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxacurium</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Doxacurium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01140</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefadroxil</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Cefadroxil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01148</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flavoxate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Flavoxate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01149</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nefazodone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Nefazodone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01156</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bupropion</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Bupropion which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01157</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimetrexate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Trimetrexate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01166</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cilostazol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Cilostazol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01170</drugbank-id>
      <name>Guanethidine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Guanethidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01181</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ifosfamide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ifosfamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01183</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naloxone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Naloxone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01203</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nadolol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Nadolol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01205</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flumazenil</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Flumazenil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01212</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftriaxone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ceftriaxone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fomepizole</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Fomepizole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01215</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estazolam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Estazolam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01221</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketamine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ketamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01222</drugbank-id>
      <name>Budesonide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Budesonide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01233</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metoclopramide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Metoclopramide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01240</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epoprostenol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Epoprostenol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01241</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemfibrozil</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Gemfibrozil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01249</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iodixanol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Iodixanol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01261</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sitagliptin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Sitagliptin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01273</drugbank-id>
      <name>Varenicline</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Varenicline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01274</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arformoterol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Arformoterol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01275</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydralazine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Hydralazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01330</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefotetan</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Cefotetan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01333</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefradine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Cefradine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01359</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penbutolol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Penbutolol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01367</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rasagiline</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Rasagiline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01394</drugbank-id>
      <name>Colchicine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Colchicine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01409</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiotropium</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tiotropium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01415</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftibuten</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ceftibuten which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01420</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone propionate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Testosterone propionate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01427</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amrinone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Amrinone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01428</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxybenzone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Oxybenzone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01431</drugbank-id>
      <name>Allylestrenol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Allylestrenol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01550</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenproporex</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Fenproporex which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01558</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bromazepam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Bromazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01563</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chloral hydrate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Chloral hydrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01577</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metamfetamine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Metamfetamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01587</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketazolam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ketazolam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01610</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valganciclovir</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Valganciclovir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01638</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sorbitol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Sorbitol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01656</drugbank-id>
      <name>Roflumilast</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Roflumilast which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01685</drugbank-id>
      <name>Topiroxostat</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Topiroxostat which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04574</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estrone sulfate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Estrone sulfate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04871</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lorcaserin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Lorcaserin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04895</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pegaptanib</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pegaptanib which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04896</drugbank-id>
      <name>Milnacipran</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Milnacipran which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04920</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clevidipine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Clevidipine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04948</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lofexidine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Lofexidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04953</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ezogabine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ezogabine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05018</drugbank-id>
      <name>Migalastat</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Migalastat which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05541</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brivaracetam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Brivaracetam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05676</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apremilast</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Apremilast which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06154</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentaerythritol tetranitrate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pentaerythritol tetranitrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06186</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ipilimumab</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ipilimumab which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06196</drugbank-id>
      <name>Icatibant</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Icatibant which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06203</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alogliptin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Alogliptin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06209</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prasugrel</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Prasugrel which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06211</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doripenem</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Doripenem which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06228</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rivaroxaban</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Rivaroxaban which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06230</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nalmefene</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Nalmefene which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06262</drugbank-id>
      <name>Droxidopa</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Droxidopa which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06282</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levocetirizine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Levocetirizine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06335</drugbank-id>
      <name>Saxagliptin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Saxagliptin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06480</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prucalopride</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Prucalopride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06623</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flupirtine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Flupirtine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06637</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dalfampridine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Dalfampridine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06695</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dabigatran etexilate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Dabigatran etexilate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06700</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desvenlafaxine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Desvenlafaxine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06702</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fesoterodine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Fesoterodine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06705</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gadofosveset trisodium</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Gadofosveset trisodium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06710</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methyltestosterone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Methyltestosterone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06736</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aceclofenac</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Aceclofenac which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06767</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ammonium chloride</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ammonium chloride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06782</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dimercaprol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Dimercaprol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06796</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mangafodipir</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Mangafodipir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06800</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylnaltrexone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Methylnaltrexone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06809</drugbank-id>
      <name>Plerixafor</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Plerixafor which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06813</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pralatrexate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pralatrexate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06823</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiopronin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tiopronin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06824</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triethylenetetramine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Triethylenetetramine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08824</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ioflupane I-123</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ioflupane I-123 which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08826</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deferiprone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Deferiprone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08840</drugbank-id>
      <name>N-methylnicotinamide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of N-methylnicotinamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08872</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gabapentin enacarbil</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Gabapentin enacarbil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08877</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ruxolitinib</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ruxolitinib which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08893</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mirabegron</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Mirabegron which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08894</drugbank-id>
      <name>Peginesatide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Peginesatide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08897</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aclidinium</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Aclidinium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08899</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enzalutamide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Enzalutamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08900</drugbank-id>
      <name>Teduglutide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Teduglutide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08904</drugbank-id>
      <name>Certolizumab pegol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Certolizumab pegol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08905</drugbank-id>
      <name>Formestane</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Formestane which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08907</drugbank-id>
      <name>Canagliflozin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Canagliflozin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08909</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glycerol phenylbutyrate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Glycerol phenylbutyrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08910</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pomalidomide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pomalidomide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08911</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trametinib</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Trametinib which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08918</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levomilnacipran</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Levomilnacipran which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08932</drugbank-id>
      <name>Macitentan</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Macitentan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08934</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sofosbuvir</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Sofosbuvir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08964</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemeprost</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Gemeprost which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09027</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ledipasvir</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ledipasvir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09038</drugbank-id>
      <name>Empagliflozin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Empagliflozin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09050</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftolozane</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ceftolozane which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09066</drugbank-id>
      <name>Corifollitropin alfa</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Corifollitropin alfa which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09068</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vortioxetine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Vortioxetine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09071</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tasimelteon</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tasimelteon which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09075</drugbank-id>
      <name>Edoxaban</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Edoxaban which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09081</drugbank-id>
      <name>Idebenone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Idebenone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09082</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vilanterol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Vilanterol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09084</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benzydamine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Benzydamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09089</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimebutine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Trimebutine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09091</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tixocortol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tixocortol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09103</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ancestim</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ancestim which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09104</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium hydroxide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Magnesium hydroxide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09106</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydroxyethyl Starch</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Hydroxyethyl Starch which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09111</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentastarch</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pentastarch which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09118</drugbank-id>
      <name>Stiripentol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Stiripentol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09121</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aurothioglucose</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Aurothioglucose which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09123</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dienogest</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Dienogest which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09129</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromic chloride</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Chromic chloride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09132</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gadoteric acid</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Gadoteric acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09133</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iothalamic acid</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Iothalamic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09134</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ioversol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ioversol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09135</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ioxilan</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ioxilan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09136</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isosulfan blue</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Isosulfan blue which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09137</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m mebrofenin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Technetium Tc-99m mebrofenin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09139</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m oxidronate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Technetium Tc-99m oxidronate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09148</drugbank-id>
      <name>Florbetaben (18F)</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Florbetaben (18F) which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09149</drugbank-id>
      <name>Florbetapir (18F)</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Florbetapir (18F) which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09156</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iopromide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Iopromide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09163</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m exametazime</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Technetium Tc-99m exametazime which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09164</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m disofenin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Technetium Tc-99m disofenin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09165</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m pyrophosphate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Technetium Tc-99m pyrophosphate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09185</drugbank-id>
      <name>Viloxazine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Viloxazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09194</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etoperidone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Etoperidone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09195</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lorpiprazole</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Lorpiprazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09204</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arotinolol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Arotinolol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09205</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moxisylyte</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Moxisylyte which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09209</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pholcodine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pholcodine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09210</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piracetam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Piracetam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09214</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexketoprofen</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Dexketoprofen which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09219</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bisoxatin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Bisoxatin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09220</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nicorandil</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Nicorandil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09223</drugbank-id>
      <name>Blonanserin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Blonanserin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09241</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylene blue</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Methylene blue which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09244</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pirlindole</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pirlindole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09245</drugbank-id>
      <name>Toloxatone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Toloxatone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09255</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dextran</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Dextran which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09256</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tegafur</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tegafur which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09257</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gimeracil</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Gimeracil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09262</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imidafenacin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Imidafenacin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Idarucizumab</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Idarucizumab which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09265</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lixisenatide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Lixisenatide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09268</drugbank-id>
      <name>Picosulfuric acid</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Picosulfuric acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09276</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium aurothiomalate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Sodium aurothiomalate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09277</drugbank-id>
      <name>Choline C 11</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Choline C 11 which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09281</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium trisilicate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Magnesium trisilicate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09288</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propacetamol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Propacetamol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09292</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sacubitril</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Sacubitril which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09301</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chondroitin sulfate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Chondroitin sulfate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens, A</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens, A which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09318</drugbank-id>
      <name>Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens, B</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens, B which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09320</drugbank-id>
      <name>Procaine benzylpenicillin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Procaine benzylpenicillin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09324</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulbactam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Sulbactam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09325</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium fluoride</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Sodium fluoride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09329</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antihemophilic Factor (Recombinant), PEGylated</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Antihemophilic Factor (Recombinant), PEGylated which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09338</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mersalyl</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Mersalyl which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09344</drugbank-id>
      <name>Invert sugar</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Invert sugar which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09357</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexpanthenol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Dexpanthenol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09394</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phosphoric acid</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Phosphoric acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09395</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium acetate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Sodium acetate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09407</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium chloride</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Magnesium chloride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09418</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium perchlorate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Potassium perchlorate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09472</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium sulfate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Sodium sulfate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09477</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enalaprilat</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Enalaprilat which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09481</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium carbonate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Magnesium carbonate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09488</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acrivastine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Acrivastine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09496</drugbank-id>
      <name>Octinoxate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Octinoxate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09502</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fludeoxyglucose (18F)</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Fludeoxyglucose (18F) which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09546</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iobenguane sulfate I-123</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Iobenguane sulfate I-123 which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09570</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ixazomib</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ixazomib which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11077</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polyethylene glycol 400</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Polyethylene glycol 400 which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11090</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium nitrate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Potassium nitrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11098</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium bicarbonate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Potassium bicarbonate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11102</drugbank-id>
      <name>N-acetyltyrosine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of N-acetyltyrosine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11114</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eucalyptus oil</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Eucalyptus oil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11127</drugbank-id>
      <name>Selenious acid</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Selenious acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11130</drugbank-id>
      <name>Opium</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Opium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11135</drugbank-id>
      <name>Selenium</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Selenium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11136</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromium</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Chromium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11145</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxyquinoline</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Oxyquinoline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11156</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pyrantel</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pyrantel which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11164</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bicisate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Bicisate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11251</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tocopherol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tocopherol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11278</drugbank-id>
      <name>DL-Methylephedrine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of DL-Methylephedrine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11328</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetradecyl hydrogen sulfate (ester)</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tetradecyl hydrogen sulfate (ester) which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11338</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clove oil</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Clove oil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11358</drugbank-id>
      <name>Evening primrose oil</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Evening primrose oil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11364</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pidotimod</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pidotimod which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11367</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefroxadine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Cefroxadine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11560</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lesinurad</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Lesinurad which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11577</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indigotindisulfonic acid</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Indigotindisulfonic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11587</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etafedrine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Etafedrine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11598</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antithrombin III human</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Antithrombin III human which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11691</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naldemedine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Naldemedine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11699</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tropisetron</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tropisetron which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Baricitinib</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Baricitinib which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11901</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apalutamide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Apalutamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11915</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valbenazine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Valbenazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11943</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delafloxacin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Delafloxacin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11989</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benznidazole</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Benznidazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12007</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isoflavone</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Isoflavone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12107</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vaborbactam</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Vaborbactam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12151</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brincidofovir</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Brincidofovir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12278</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propiverine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Propiverine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benserazide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Benserazide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13025</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiapride</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Tiapride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13139</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levosalbutamol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Levosalbutamol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13145</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nedaplatin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Nedaplatin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13156</drugbank-id>
      <name>Inosine pranobex</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Inosine pranobex which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13167</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alclofenac</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Alclofenac which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13178</drugbank-id>
      <name>Inositol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Inositol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13185</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxabolone cipionate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Oxabolone cipionate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13191</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phosphocreatine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Phosphocreatine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13269</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dichlorobenzyl alcohol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Dichlorobenzyl alcohol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13293</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ipecac</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Ipecac which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Almasilate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Almasilate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13873</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenofibric acid</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Fenofibric acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13884</drugbank-id>
      <name>Albutrepenonacog alfa</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Albutrepenonacog alfa which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13909</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bismuth subgallate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Bismuth subgallate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13943</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone cypionate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Testosterone cypionate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13944</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone enanthate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Testosterone enanthate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13946</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone undecanoate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Testosterone undecanoate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13952</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol acetate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Estradiol acetate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13954</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol cypionate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Estradiol cypionate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13955</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol dienanthate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Estradiol dienanthate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13956</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol valerate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Estradiol valerate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13967</drugbank-id>
      <name>Patent Blue</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Patent Blue which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14006</drugbank-id>
      <name>Choline salicylate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Choline salicylate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14007</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentetic acid</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pentetic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14184</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cinnamaldehyde</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Cinnamaldehyde which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14186</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cinnamyl alcohol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Cinnamyl alcohol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14498</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium acetate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Potassium acetate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14499</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium sulfate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Potassium sulfate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14526</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromic citrate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Chromic citrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14527</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromic nitrate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Chromic nitrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14528</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromium gluconate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Chromium gluconate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14529</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromium nicotinate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Chromium nicotinate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14530</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromous sulfate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Chromous sulfate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14754</drugbank-id>
      <name>Solriamfetol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Solriamfetol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06815</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pyrithione</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pyrithione which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11121</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chloroxylenol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Chloroxylenol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11085</drugbank-id>
      <name>Resorcinol</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Resorcinol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15593</drugbank-id>
      <name>Golodirsen</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Golodirsen which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00314</drugbank-id>
      <name>Capreomycin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Capreomycin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00318</drugbank-id>
      <name>Codeine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Codeine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00321</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amitriptyline</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Amitriptyline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00390</drugbank-id>
      <name>Digoxin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Digoxin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00454</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meperidine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Meperidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00458</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imipramine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Imipramine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00512</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vancomycin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Vancomycin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00515</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cisplatin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Cisplatin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00564</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbamazepine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Carbamazepine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00642</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pemetrexed</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Pemetrexed which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00682</drugbank-id>
      <name>Warfarin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Warfarin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00813</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fentanyl</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Fentanyl which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00879</drugbank-id>
      <name>Emtricitabine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Emtricitabine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00908</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinidine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Quinidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00982</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isotretinoin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Isotretinoin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01035</drugbank-id>
      <name>Procainamide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Procainamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01142</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxepin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Doxepin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01151</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desipramine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Desipramine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01242</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clomipramine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Clomipramine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01356</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium cation</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Lithium cation which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08996</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dimetacrine</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Dimetacrine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Plazomicin</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Plazomicin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14506</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium hydroxide</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Lithium hydroxide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14507</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium citrate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Lithium citrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14508</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium succinate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Lithium succinate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14509</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium carbonate</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Lithium carbonate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00781</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polymyxin B</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Polymyxin B.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00181</drugbank-id>
      <name>Baclofen</name>
      <description>Inotersen may decrease the excretion rate of Baclofen which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00656</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trazodone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Trazodone is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11986</drugbank-id>
      <name>Entrectinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Entrectinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11642</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pitolisant</name>
      <description>Inotersen may increase the QTc-prolonging activities of Pitolisant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12825</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lefamulin</name>
      <description>Lefamulin may increase the QTc-prolonging activities of Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00445</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epirubicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of QTc prolongation can be increased when Epirubicin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>Water Solubility</kind>
      <value>soluble </value>
      <source>https://www.ema.europa.eu/documents/product-information/tegsedi-epar-product-information_en.pdf</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Weight</kind>
      <value>7183.077</value>
      <source/>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Formula</kind>
      <value>C230H318N69O121P19S19</value>
      <source/>
    </property>
  </experimental-properties>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Drugs Product Database (DPD)</resource>
      <identifier>22997</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Wikipedia</resource>
      <identifier>Inotersen</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets>
    <target position="1">
      <id>BE0009563</id>
      <name>Transthyretin mRNA</name>
      <organism>Humans</organism>
      <actions>
        <action>inhibitor</action>
      </actions>
      <references>
        <articles>
          <article>
            <ref-id>A39493</ref-id>
            <pubmed-id>29972757</pubmed-id>
            <citation>Benson MD, Waddington-Cruz M, Berk JL, Polydefkis M, Dyck PJ, Wang AK, Plante-Bordeneuve V, Barroso FA, Merlini G, Obici L, Scheinberg M, Brannagan TH 3rd, Litchy WJ, Whelan C, Drachman BM, Adams D, Heitner SB, Conceicao I, Schmidt HH, Vita G, Campistol JM, Gamez J, Gorevic PD, Gane E, Shah AM, Solomon SD, Monia BP, Hughes SG, Kwoh TJ, McEvoy BW, Jung SW, Baker BF, Ackermann EJ, Gertz MA, Coelho T: Inotersen Treatment for Patients with Hereditary Transthyretin Amyloidosis. N Engl J Med. 2018 Jul 5;379(1):22-31. doi: 10.1056/NEJMoa1716793.</citation>
          </article>
          <article>
            <ref-id>A39494</ref-id>
            <pubmed-id>29240946</pubmed-id>
            <citation>Shen X, Corey DR: Chemistry, mechanism and clinical status of antisense oligonucleotides and duplex RNAs. Nucleic Acids Res. 2018 Feb 28;46(4):1584-1600. doi: 10.1093/nar/gkx1239.</citation>
          </article>
          <article>
            <ref-id>A39495</ref-id>
            <pubmed-id>29185862</pubmed-id>
            <citation>Crooke ST, Baker BF, Pham NC, Hughes SG, Kwoh TJ, Cai D, Tsimikas S, Geary RS, Bhanot S: The Effects of 2'-O-Methoxyethyl Oligonucleotides on Renal Function in Humans. Nucleic Acid Ther. 2018 Feb;28(1):10-22. doi: 10.1089/nat.2017.0693. Epub 2017 Nov 29.</citation>
          </article>
        </articles>
        <textbooks/>
        <links/>
        <attachments>
          <attachment>
            <ref-id>F1938</ref-id>
            <title>Tegsedi EMA label</title>
            <url>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/cite_this/attachments/files/000/001/938/original/tegsedi-epar-product-information_en.pdf?1539980614</url>
          </attachment>
        </attachments>
      </references>
      <known-action>yes</known-action>
    </target>
  </targets>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>