<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2010-09-14" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB06759</drugbank-id>
  <name>Fomivirsen</name>
  <description>Fomivirsen is a antisense 21 mer phosphorothioate oligonucleotide. It is an antiviral agent that was used in the treatment of cytomegalovirus retinitis (CMV) in immunocompromised patients, including those with AIDS. As a complementary nucleotide to the messenger RNA of the major immediate-early region proteins of human cytomegalovirus, it disrupts the replication of the virus through an antisense mechanism [L1428]. It was discovered by scientists at the National Institutes of Health (NIH) and was first developed by _Isis Pharmaceuticals_ and subsequently licensed to _Novartis_ [A31990]. The drug was withdrawn by the FDA because while there was a high unmet need for drugs to treat CMV when the drug was initially discovered and developed due to the CMV arising in people with AIDS, the development of HAART dramatically reduced the number of cases of CMV. Fomivirsen is marketed under the trade name Vitravene for intravitreal injection and was the first antisense drug to be approved by the Food and Drug Administration (FDA).</description>
  <cas-number>144245-52-3</cas-number>
  <unii>QX5LK7YCHV</unii>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
    <group>investigational</group>
    <group>withdrawn</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A31988</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>11978144</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Geary RS, Henry SP, Grillone LR: Fomivirsen: clinical pharmacology and potential drug interactions. Clin Pharmacokinet. 2002;41(4):255-60. doi: 10.2165/00003088-200241040-00002.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A31989</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>10611727</pubmed-id>
        <citation>de Smet MD, Meenken CJ, van den Horn GJ: Fomivirsen - a phosphorothioate oligonucleotide for the treatment of CMV retinitis. Ocul Immunol Inflamm. 1999 Dec;7(3-4):189-98.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A31990</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>11497353</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Orr RM: Technology evaluation: fomivirsen, Isis Pharmaceuticals Inc/CIBA vision. Curr Opin Mol Ther. 2001 Jun;3(3):288-94.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A32006</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>12610136</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Isomura H, Stinski MF: The human cytomegalovirus major immediate-early enhancer determines the efficiency of immediate-early gene transcription and viral replication in permissive cells at low multiplicity of infection. J Virol. 2003 Mar;77(6):3602-14.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A32009</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>11160686</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Marchini A, Liu H, Zhu H: Human cytomegalovirus with IE-2 (UL122) deleted fails to express early lytic genes. J Virol. 2001 Feb;75(4):1870-8. doi: 10.1128/JVI.75.4.1870-1878.2001.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L1428</ref-id>
        <title>EMA Label: Vitravene (fomivirsen sodium) Summary of Product Characteristics</title>
        <url>https://ec.europa.eu/health/documents/community-register/1999/199907293331/anx_3331_en.pdf</url>
      </link>
    </links>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Indicated for the local treatment of cytomegalovirus (CMV) retinitis in patients with acquired immunodeficiency syndrome (AIDS), when other therapy has been ineffective or is considered unsuitable [FDA Label, L1428].</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>Fomivirsen is an antiviral agent that inhibits CMV replication in a dose-dependent manner with a mean 50% inhibitory concentration between 0.03 and 0.2 μM in a number of _in vitro_ cell lines [A31989]. In human fibroblast cell lines, the median effective inhibitory concentration (EC50) of fomivirsen for virus antigen production was approximately 0.34±0.25 μM [L1428]. In a clinical trial, administration of fomivirsen in patients with newly diagnosed CMV retinitis resulted in an increased median time to disease progression in the immediate treatment group versus delayed treatment group [L1428].</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>Fomivirsen is a phosphorothioate oligonucleotide that inhibits the replication of human cytomegalovirus (HCMV) through an antisense mechanism. The nucleotide sequence is complementary to a sequence in mRNA transcripts of the major immediate early region 2 (IE2) of human CMV, which encodes several proteins responsible for regulation of viral gene expression that are essential for viral replication [L1428]. The IE2 gene is essential for early viral gene expression and viral replication [A32006]; it was shown that the IE2 gene transactivate most human CMV promoters [A32009]. Protein product from the IE2 region also acts as autorepressor that represses transcription of the IE1 and IE2 genes by binding the cis repression sequence (CRS) [A32006]. It is proposed that the IE2 region interacts with multiple basal and general transcription factors, as well as cell cycle regulators, and it also plays a critical role in controlling the entry of the virus into the lytic cycle from the latent state to further potentiate the infection cascade [A32009]. Upon binding to the target mRNA, fomivirsen inhibits the IE2 protein synthesis and disrupts viral replication [L1428]. </mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity>There has been one case of accidental overdose of fomivirsen with administration once bilaterally with 990 μg per eye; vision was restored with anterior chamber paracentesis performed bilaterally [L1428].&#13;
According to the findings in Salmonella/Microsome (Ames) and mouse lymphoma tests, fomivirsen was not shown to be mutagenic. In the in vivo mouse micronucleus assay, fomivirsen was not clastogenic. Animal reproductive studies or studies evaluating the carcinogenic potential of fomivirsen has not been conducted [FDA Label]. </toxicity>
  <metabolism>Fomivirsen undergoes metabolism mediated by endo- and exonuclease, where the resides from the terminal ends of the oligonucleotide are sequentially removed [FDA Label, L1428]. Resulting shortened oligonucleotides and mononucleotide metabolites can be detected in the retina and vitreous of animals [FDA Label]. Mononucleotides may also be further catabolized to endogenous nucleotides and excreted as low molecular weight metabolites [FDA Label].</metabolism>
  <absorption>Following intravitreal injection in rabbits and monkeys, peak concentrations in the vitreous was detectable immediately after injection with the concentrations increasing in a dose-proportional manner [L1428]. Due to low doses of intravitreal administration with slow disposition from the eye, there is limited absorption of the drug into the systemic circulation [A31988]. Fomivirsen is detectable in retina of rabbits within hours following administration and concentrations increase over 3 to 5 days. The concentrations of the drug were highest in the retina and iris [FDA Label]. </absorption>
  <half-life>Intravitreal drug clearance studies have revealed first-order kinetics [A31989]. Following intravitreal administration, fomivirsen is slowly cleared from vitreous with a half-life of approximately 55 hours in humans [A31988]. The half life from retina in monkeys following administration of 115 mcg fomivirsen is estimated to be 78 hours [A31988].</half-life>
  <protein-binding>Fomivirsen is approximately 40% bound to proteins according to the analysis of vitreous samples from treated rabbits and monkeys [FDA Label]. It is mostly bound to albumin and alpha2-macroglobulin in blood plasma [A31988]. </protein-binding>
  <route-of-elimination>In rabbits, 16% of total radiolabelled fomivirsen was detected in urine and 3% was detected in feces [FDA Label].</route-of-elimination>
  <volume-of-distribution>Preclinical studies show that fomivirsen distributes to retina [A31988].</volume-of-distribution>
  <clearance>Clearance from retina was shown to be similarly slow following loading from the vitreous [A31988].</clearance>
  <salts>
    <salt>
      <drugbank-id primary="true">DBSALT001455</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fomivirsen sodium</name>
      <unii>3Z6W3S36X5</unii>
      <cas-number>160369-77-7</cas-number>
      <inchikey/>
    </salt>
  </salts>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Anti-Infective Agents</category>
      <mesh-id>D000890</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Antisense Elements (Genetics)</category>
      <mesh-id>D016375</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Antiviral Agents</category>
      <mesh-id>D000998</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Carbohydrates</category>
      <mesh-id>D002241</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Compounds used in a research, industrial, or household setting</category>
      <mesh-id>D020313</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Diagnostic Uses of Chemicals</category>
      <mesh-id>D064907</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Glycosides</category>
      <mesh-id>D006027</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Laboratory Chemicals</category>
      <mesh-id>D019995</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Molecular Probes</category>
      <mesh-id>D015335</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nucleic Acid Probes</category>
      <mesh-id>D015341</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nucleic Acids</category>
      <mesh-id>D009696</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nucleic Acids, Nucleotides, and Nucleosides</category>
      <mesh-id>D009706</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nucleotides</category>
      <mesh-id>D009711</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Oligonucleotides</category>
      <mesh-id>D009841</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Oligonucleotides, Antisense</category>
      <mesh-id>D016376</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Ophthalmologicals</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Polynucleotides</category>
      <mesh-id>D011119</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Sensory Organs</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Sulfur Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D013457</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Human Cytomegalovirus</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes>
    <atc-code code="S01AD08">
      <level code="S01AD">Antivirals</level>
      <level code="S01A">ANTIINFECTIVES</level>
      <level code="S01">OPHTHALMOLOGICALS</level>
      <level code="S">SENSORY ORGANS</level>
    </atc-code>
  </atc-codes>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <fda-label>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/fda_labels/DB06759.pdf?1519419737</fda-label>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB10317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rubella virus vaccine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Rubella virus vaccine can be decreased when used in combination with Fomivirsen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB10343</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bacillus calmette-guerin substrain tice live antigen</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Bacillus calmette-guerin substrain tice live antigen can be decreased when used in combination with Fomivirsen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB10804</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bacillus calmette-guerin substrain connaught live antigen</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Bacillus calmette-guerin substrain connaught live antigen can be decreased when used in combination with Fomivirsen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB10805</drugbank-id>
      <name>Yellow Fever Vaccine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Yellow Fever Vaccine can be decreased when used in combination with Fomivirsen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11003</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anthrax vaccine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Anthrax vaccine can be decreased when used in combination with Fomivirsen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11050</drugbank-id>
      <name>Typhoid Vaccine Live</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Typhoid Vaccine Live can be decreased when used in combination with Fomivirsen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12386</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bacillus calmette-guerin substrain danish 1331 live antigen</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Bacillus calmette-guerin substrain danish 1331 live antigen can be decreased when used in combination with Fomivirsen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12768</drugbank-id>
      <name>BCG vaccine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of BCG vaccine can be decreased when used in combination with Fomivirsen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14409</drugbank-id>
      <name>Human adenovirus e serotype 4 strain cl-68578 antigen</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Human adenovirus e serotype 4 strain cl-68578 antigen can be decreased when used in combination with Fomivirsen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14443</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vibrio cholerae CVD 103-HgR strain live antigen</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Vibrio cholerae CVD 103-HgR strain live antigen can be decreased when used in combination with Fomivirsen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14685</drugbank-id>
      <name>Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Fomivirsen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB10318</drugbank-id>
      <name>Varicella Zoster Vaccine (Live/attenuated)</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Varicella Zoster Vaccine (Live/attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Fomivirsen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <sequences>
    <sequence format="FASTA">&gt;Whole oligonucleotide:
GCGTTTGCTCTTCTTCTTGCG</sequence>
  </sequences>
  <experimental-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Weight</kind>
      <value>7122.0</value>
      <source/>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Formula</kind>
      <value>C204H243N63O114P20S20Na20</value>
      <source/>
    </property>
  </experimental-properties>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910367</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>KEGG Drug</resource>
      <identifier>D02736</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Wikipedia</resource>
      <identifier>Fomivirsen</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEMBL</resource>
      <identifier>CHEMBL1201688</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets>
    <target position="1">
      <id>BE0009326</id>
      <name>30 kDa immediate-early protein 2</name>
      <organism>Human cytomegalovirus (strain Towne)</organism>
      <actions>
        <action>antisense oligonucleotide</action>
      </actions>
      <references>
        <articles>
          <article>
            <ref-id>A32007</ref-id>
            <pubmed-id>9559825</pubmed-id>
            <citation>Mulamba GB, Hu A, Azad RF, Anderson KP, Coen DM: Human cytomegalovirus mutant with sequence-dependent resistance to the phosphorothioate oligonucleotide fomivirsen (ISIS 2922). Antimicrob Agents Chemother. 1998 Apr;42(4):971-3.</citation>
          </article>
        </articles>
        <textbooks/>
        <links/>
        <attachments/>
      </references>
      <known-action>yes</known-action>
      <polypeptide id="P06434" source="Swiss-Prot">
        <name>30 kDa immediate-early protein 2</name>
        <general-function>Activates the E1.7 promoter. This activation is augmented by the IE1 protein. It down-regulates the transcription of genes under the control of the major IE promoter.</general-function>
        <specific-function/>
        <gene-name>UL122</gene-name>
        <locus/>
        <cellular-location/>
        <transmembrane-regions/>
        <signal-regions/>
        <theoretical-pi/>
        <molecular-weight>30328.565</molecular-weight>
        <chromosome-location/>
        <organism ncbi-taxonomy-id="10363">Human cytomegalovirus (strain Towne)</organism>
        <external-identifiers>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>UniProtKB</resource>
            <identifier>P06434</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>UniProt Accession</resource>
            <identifier>VIE3_HCMVT</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
        </external-identifiers>
        <synonyms>
          <synonym>IE2</synonym>
        </synonyms>
        <amino-acid-sequence format="FASTA">&gt;lcl|BSEQ0051578|30 kDa immediate-early protein 2
MLPLIKQEDIKPEPDFTIQYRNKIIDTAGCIVISDSEEEQGEEVETRGATASSPSTGSGT
PRVTSPTHPLSQMNHPPLPDPLGRPDEDSSSSSSSCSSASDSESESEEMKCSSGGGASVT
SSHHGRGGFGGAASSSLLSCGHQSSGGASTGPRKKKSKRISELDNEKVRNIMKDKNTPFC
TPNVQTRRGRVKIDEVSRMFRNTNRSLEYKNLPFTIPSMHQVLDEAIKACKTMQVNNKGI
QIIYTRNHEVKSEVDAVRCRLGTMCTWPSPLPSSWSTPCP</amino-acid-sequence>
        <gene-sequence format="FASTA"/>
        <pfams>
          <pfam>
            <identifier>PF03361</identifier>
            <name>Herpes_IE2_3</name>
          </pfam>
        </pfams>
        <go-classifiers>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>regulation of transcription, DNA-templated</description>
          </go-classifier>
        </go-classifiers>
      </polypeptide>
    </target>
    <target position="2">
      <id>BE0009327</id>
      <name>45 kDa immediate-early protein 2</name>
      <organism>Human cytomegalovirus (strain Towne)</organism>
      <actions>
        <action>antisense oligonucleotide</action>
      </actions>
      <references>
        <articles>
          <article>
            <ref-id>A32007</ref-id>
            <pubmed-id>9559825</pubmed-id>
            <citation>Mulamba GB, Hu A, Azad RF, Anderson KP, Coen DM: Human cytomegalovirus mutant with sequence-dependent resistance to the phosphorothioate oligonucleotide fomivirsen (ISIS 2922). Antimicrob Agents Chemother. 1998 Apr;42(4):971-3.</citation>
          </article>
        </articles>
        <textbooks/>
        <links/>
        <attachments/>
      </references>
      <known-action>yes</known-action>
      <polypeptide id="P06435" source="Swiss-Prot">
        <name>45 kDa immediate-early protein 2</name>
        <general-function>Activates the E1.7 promoter. This activation is augmented by the IE1 protein. It down-regulates the transcription of genes under the control of the major IE promoter.</general-function>
        <specific-function>Dna binding</specific-function>
        <gene-name>UL122</gene-name>
        <locus/>
        <cellular-location/>
        <transmembrane-regions/>
        <signal-regions/>
        <theoretical-pi/>
        <molecular-weight>44773.175</molecular-weight>
        <chromosome-location/>
        <organism ncbi-taxonomy-id="10363">Human cytomegalovirus (strain Towne)</organism>
        <external-identifiers>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>UniProtKB</resource>
            <identifier>P06435</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>UniProt Accession</resource>
            <identifier>IE247_HCMVT</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
        </external-identifiers>
        <synonyms>
          <synonym>IE2</synonym>
        </synonyms>
        <amino-acid-sequence format="FASTA">&gt;lcl|BSEQ0051579|45 kDa immediate-early protein 2
MLPLIKQEDIKPEPDFTIQYRNKIIDTAGCIVISDSEEEQGEEVETRGATASSPSTGSGT
PRVTSPTHPLSQMNHPPLPDPLGRPDEDSSSSSSSCSSASDSESESEEMKCSSGGGASVT
SSHHGRGGFGGAASSSLLSCGHQSSGGASTGPRKKKSKRISELDNEKVRNIMKDKNTPFC
TPNVQTRRGRVKIDEVSRMFRNTNRSLEYKNLPFTIPSMHQVLDEAIKACKTMQVNNKGI
QIIYTRNHEVKSEVDAVRCRLGTMCNLALSTPFLMEHTMPVTHPPKVAQRTADACNEGVK
AAWSLKELHTHQLCPRSSDYRNMIIHAATPVDLLGALNLCLPLMQKFPKQVMVRIFSTNQ
GGFMLPIYETATKAYAVGQFEQPTETPPEDLDTLSLAIEAAIQDLRNKSQ</amino-acid-sequence>
        <gene-sequence format="FASTA"/>
        <pfams>
          <pfam>
            <identifier>PF03361</identifier>
            <name>Herpes_IE2_3</name>
          </pfam>
        </pfams>
        <go-classifiers>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>function</category>
            <description>DNA binding</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>function</category>
            <description>metal ion binding</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>modulation by virus of host G0/G1 transition checkpoint</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>modulation by virus of host G1/S transition checkpoint</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>regulation of transcription, DNA-templated</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>transcription, DNA-templated</description>
          </go-classifier>
        </go-classifiers>
      </polypeptide>
    </target>
  </targets>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>