<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2007-10-21" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB04904</drugbank-id>
  <name>Amolimogene</name>
  <description>Amolimogene is an investigational therapeutic designed to specifically augment the body's defensive response to human papillomavirus (HPV). Amolimogene was biologically engineered as a targeted therapy for the treatment of cervical dysplasia.</description>
  <cas-number>676269-70-8</cas-number>
  <unii/>
  <state>liquid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A2909</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>15073670</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Crum CP, Beach KJ, Hedley ML, Yuan L, Lee KR, Wright TC, Urban RG: Dynamics of human papillomavirus infection between biopsy and excision of cervical intraepithelial neoplasia: results from the ZYC101a protocol. J Infect Dis. 2004 Apr 15;189(8):1348-54. Epub 2004 Mar 30.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A2910</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>14754702</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Garcia F, Petry KU, Muderspach L, Gold MA, Braly P, Crum CP, Magill M, Silverman M, Urban RG, Hedley ML, Beach KJ: ZYC101a for treatment of high-grade cervical intraepithelial neoplasia: a randomized controlled trial. Obstet Gynecol. 2004 Feb;103(2):317-26.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Intended for the treatment of cervical dysplasia associated with the human papillomavirus (HPV).</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>Amolimogene was shown to be well tolerated in all patients and to promote the resolution of CIN 2/3 in women younger than 25 years.</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>Amolimogene particles are injected into the leg muscle and encounter cells known as antigen presenting cells, which play a pivotal role in activating the immune system. Once inside the dendritic cells, amolimogene dissolves and the genetic information that codes for parts of the HPV virus is released. The information is then processed, attaches to a protein and transported to the surface of the dendritic cell, attracting immune cells known as T cells. The T cells attach to the protein holding the information and begin to divide, creating many HPV targeted T cells. These cells migrate to the cervix where they encounter HPV expressing cells. Once inside the cervix, the T cells surround and eliminate the abnormal precancerous cells that cause cervical dysplasia. The result can be normal, healthy tissue.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Nucleic Acids</category>
      <mesh-id>D009696</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nucleic Acids, Nucleotides, and Nucleosides</category>
      <mesh-id>D009706</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347909844</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>