<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-10-21" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05112</drugbank-id>
  <name>AP5280</name>
  <description>AP5280 is a novel N-(2-hydroxypropyl)methacrylamide (HPMA) copolymer-bound platinum (Pt) therapeutic designed to increase the therapeutic index relative to conventional, small-molecule platinum agents.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in solid tumors.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>&#13;
AP5280 was designed to take advantage of two independent mechanisms for attaining selectivity. The first of these is the enhanced permeability and retention effect by which high molecular weight polymers passively accumulate to high levels in tumors, and the second is the increased level of expression of proteases capable of cleaving the peptide linker between the polymer and the cytotoxic moiety that is characteristic of many tumors.&#13;
AP5280 is a chemotherapeutic agent that we believe has the potential to have significantly superior effectiveness in treating numerous cancers compared to platinum compounds currently in use. AP5280 seeks to achieve this goal by attaching a large polymer to a small platinum molecule. This method exploits the usually leaky or hyperpermeable nature of the cells that line the walls of blood vessels that&#13;
feed tumors by allowing the large AP5280 molecule to enter the tumor in preference to other tissue, which do not have leaky or hyperpermeable blood vessels. In addition, the capillary/lymphatic drainage system of tumors is not well developed and limited, so the drug gets trapped in the&#13;
tumor. This dual effect is called enhanced permeability and retention, or EPR. In addition, the polymer is designed to shield the platinum from interactions with normal cells while the drug circulates within the body, thereby reducing toxicity. The proposed mechanism of how AP5280 is taken up by tumor cells bypasses known membrane-associated mechanisms&#13;
for development of tumor resistance, a common cause of failure of chemo-therapeutic drugs over the course of treatment.&#13;
</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Acids, Acyclic</category>
      <mesh-id>D000144</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Acrylates</category>
      <mesh-id>D000179</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Amides</category>
      <mesh-id>D000577</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Drug Delivery Systems</category>
      <mesh-id>D016503</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Organometallic Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D009942</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347909952</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>