<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-11-18" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05799</drugbank-id>
  <name>NOX-100</name>
  <description>NOX-100 is the new nitric oxide (NO) neutralizing agent being developed by San Diego-based Medinox -- demonstrated its effectiveness and potential as a therapeutic to treat hemorrhagic shock. NOX-100 is the first in a series of proprietary NO neutralizing compounds Medinox is developing to bind and inactivate NO, a simple gas molecule that is a key biological messenger in the body.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii>3JWCT8LCME</unii>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3791</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>15043990</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Kagota S, Yamaguchi Y, Nakamura K, Shinozuka K, Kunitomo M: Chronic nitric oxide exposure alters the balance between endothelium-derived relaxing factors released from rat renal arteries: prevention by treatment with NOX-100, a NO scavenger. Life Sci. 2004 Apr 16;74(22):2757-67.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3792</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>10670631</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Roza AM, Cooper M, Pieper G, Hilton G, Dembny K, Lai CS, Lindholm P, Komorowski R, Felix C, Johnson C, Adams M: NOX 100, a nitric oxide scavenger, enhances cardiac allograft survival and promotes long-term graft acceptance. Transplantation. 2000 Jan 27;69(2):227-31.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in sepsis and septicemia.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>Under normal conditions, Nitric Oxide (NO) is produced in small amounts and plays many crucial maintenance roles including regulating blood pressure, facilitating memory and defending against pathogens. But when inflammation occurs, NO can be produced in excessive amounts and contributes to disease pathology.&#13;
 &#13;
NOX-100 binds excessive NO but do not remove the low levels needed to perform vital maintenance functions in the body. NOX-100 eliminates  excessive NO which is distinct from enzyme inhibitors, which block NO synthesis.&#13;
</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910238</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>