<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2007-10-21" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB04986</drugbank-id>
  <name>ZYC300</name>
  <description>ZYC300 is a plasmid DNA of CYP1B1 encapsulated in biodegradable poly-DL-lactide-coglycolide microparticles. It is designed as a vaccine, intended to increase immune system sensitivity to CYP1B1, an enzyme highly prevalent in tumor cells.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>liquid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3149</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>15958627</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Gribben JG, Ryan DP, Boyajian R, Urban RG, Hedley ML, Beach K, Nealon P, Matulonis U, Campos S, Gilligan TD, Richardson PG, Marshall B, Neuberg D, Nadler LM: Unexpected association between induction of immunity to the universal tumor antigen CYP1B1 and response to next therapy. Clin Cancer Res. 2005 Jun 15;11(12):4430-6.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>For the treatment of various forms of cancer.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>CYP1B1 is a unique extra-hepatic member of the cytochrome P450 family of monooxygenases. The CYP1B1 protein is over-expressed in all primary human tumors with minimal expression in critical normal tissues making this an attractive target for immunotherapy. CYP1B1-specific human T lymphocytes lyse tumor cells but not normal cells. To explore the potential clinical utility of elevated CYP1B1 immune responses, a pDNA-based immunogen was developed (ZYC300). The ZYC300 formulation is comprised of PLG microparticles containing a plasmid DNA with a CMV promoter that drives expression of mutated CYP1B1 protein.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347909875</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>