<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-11-18" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05918</drugbank-id>
  <name>LS11</name>
  <description>LS11(talaporfin sodium) is an agent consisting of chlorin e6, derived from chlorophyll, and L-aspartic acid with photosensitizing activity. After intratumoral activation by light emitting diodes, taporfin sodium forms an extended high energy conformational state that generates singlet oxygen, resulting in free radical-mediated cell death. It is used to treat many kinds of cancers.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in macular degeneration.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>Light Sciences Oncology (LSO) aims to en-light-en cancer patients. Light Sciences has developed Light Infusion Therapy (Litx) which is a novel treatment for solid tumors. The therapy involves inserting a flexible light-emitting diode (LED) into a tumor, followed by an injection of LS11 (talaporfin sodium), a light-activated drug. Once the LED activates LS11, molecular oxygen is converted into singlet oxygen, killing tissue within the LED's scope and shutting down the blood supply to the area. The treatment is designed for use on three types of cancers: hepatoma (liver cancer), metastatic colorectal cancer, and Gioma (brain tumor).</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910313</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>