<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2014-06-17" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB08999</drugbank-id>
  <name>Cyclopentamine</name>
  <description>Cyclopentamine is a sympathomimetic alkylamine, classified as a vasoconstrictor. Cyclopentamine was an over the counter treatment for nasal congestion in Europe and Australia. It has been widely discontinued due to the safety, effectiveness, and availability of a similar drug, propylhexedrine.</description>
  <cas-number>102-45-4</cas-number>
  <unii>WB9Q6M8O60</unii>
  <average-mass>141.258</average-mass>
  <monoisotopic-mass>141.151749616</monoisotopic-mass>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>withdrawn</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference>U.S. Patent 2,520,015.</synthesis-reference>
  <indication/>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action/>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description>This compound belongs to the class of organic compounds known as dialkylamines. These are organic compounds containing a dialkylamine group, characterized by two alkyl groups bonded to the amino nitrogen.</description>
    <direct-parent>Dialkylamines</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic nitrogen compounds</superclass>
    <class>Organonitrogen compounds</class>
    <subclass>Amines</subclass>
    <alternative-parent>Hydrocarbon derivatives</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Organopnictogen compounds</alternative-parent>
    <substituent>Aliphatic homomonocyclic compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Hydrocarbon derivative</substituent>
    <substituent>Organopnictogen compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Secondary aliphatic amine</substituent>
  </classification>
  <salts>
    <salt>
      <drugbank-id primary="true">DBSALT002451</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclopentamine hydrochloride</name>
      <unii>F551446KF3</unii>
      <cas-number>538-02-3</cas-number>
      <inchikey>XGZPRABQSGUFBL-UHFFFAOYSA-N</inchikey>
      <average-mass>177.72</average-mass>
      <monoisotopic-mass>177.1284273</monoisotopic-mass>
    </salt>
  </salts>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Cycloparaffins</category>
      <mesh-id>D003516</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Ganglion Blockers</category>
      <mesh-id>D005730</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nasal Preparations</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Sympathomimetics, Plain</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes>
    <atc-code code="R01AA02">
      <level code="R01AA">Sympathomimetics, plain</level>
      <level code="R01A">DECONGESTANTS AND OTHER NASAL PREPARATIONS FOR TOPICAL USE</level>
      <level code="R01">NASAL PREPARATIONS</level>
      <level code="R">RESPIRATORY SYSTEM</level>
    </atc-code>
  </atc-codes>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00203</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sildenafil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sildenafil is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00214</drugbank-id>
      <name>Torasemide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Torasemide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00232</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methyclothiazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Methyclothiazide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00263</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfisoxazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfisoxazole is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00310</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorthalidone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Chlorthalidone is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00311</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethoxzolamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ethoxzolamide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00359</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfadiazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfadiazine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00436</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bendroflumethiazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Bendroflumethiazide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00482</drugbank-id>
      <name>Celecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Celecoxib is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00524</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metolazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Metolazone is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00559</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bosentan</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Bosentan is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00562</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benzthiazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Benzthiazide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00576</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfamethizole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfamethizole is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00606</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclothiazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Cyclothiazide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00664</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfametopyrazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfametopyrazine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00669</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sumatriptan</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sumatriptan is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00695</drugbank-id>
      <name>Furosemide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Furosemide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00706</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tamsulosin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tamsulosin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00774</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydroflumethiazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Hydroflumethiazide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00795</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfasalazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfasalazine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00808</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indapamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Indapamide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00819</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetazolamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Acetazolamide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00880</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorothiazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Chlorothiazide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00887</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bumetanide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Bumetanide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00891</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfapyridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfapyridine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00909</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zonisamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Zonisamide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00999</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrochlorothiazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Hydrochlorothiazide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01015</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfamethoxazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfamethoxazole is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01021</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trichlormethiazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Trichlormethiazide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01032</drugbank-id>
      <name>Probenecid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Probenecid is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01098</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rosuvastatin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Rosuvastatin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01119</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diazoxide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Diazoxide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01144</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diclofenamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Diclofenamide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Darunavir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Darunavir is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01298</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfacytine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfacytine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01299</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfadoxine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfadoxine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01324</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polythiazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Polythiazide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01325</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinethazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Quinethazone is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01382</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glymidine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Glymidine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01581</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfamerazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfamerazine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01582</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfamethazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfamethazine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02925</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piretanide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Piretanide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04707</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydroxyfasudil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Hydroxyfasudil is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06150</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfadimethoxine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfadimethoxine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06290</drugbank-id>
      <name>Simeprevir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Simeprevir is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06729</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfaphenazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfaphenazole is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06821</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfameter</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfameter is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07996</drugbank-id>
      <name>5-(2-methylpiperazine-1-sulfonyl)isoquinoline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when 5-(2-methylpiperazine-1-sulfonyl)isoquinoline is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08162</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fasudil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Fasudil is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08798</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfamoxole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfamoxole is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08881</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vemurafenib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Vemurafenib is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08961</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azosemide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Azosemide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11389</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clorsulon</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Clorsulon is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11461</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfachlorpyridazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfachlorpyridazine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11462</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfaethoxypyridazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfaethoxypyridazine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11463</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfanitran</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfanitran is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11464</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfaquinoxaline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfaquinoxaline is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12051</drugbank-id>
      <name>Setrobuvir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Setrobuvir is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12921</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorsulfaquinoxaline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Chlorsulfaquinoxaline is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13214</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfadicramide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfadicramide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13248</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phthalylsulfathiazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Phthalylsulfathiazole is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13283</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfaisodimidine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfaisodimidine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13284</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meticrane</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Meticrane is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13320</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfaperin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfaperin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13405</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mefruside</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Mefruside is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13430</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mebutizide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Mebutizide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13485</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfametomidine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfametomidine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13532</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclopenthiazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Cyclopenthiazide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13547</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfatolamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfatolamide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13556</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfamazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfamazone is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13580</drugbank-id>
      <name>Succinylsulfathiazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Succinylsulfathiazole is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13617</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clorexolone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Clorexolone is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13663</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clofenamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Clofenamide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13699</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfathiourea</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfathiourea is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13708</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenquizone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Fenquizone is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13726</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfaguanidine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfaguanidine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13773</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfamethoxypyridazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulfamethoxypyridazine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13792</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clopamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Clopamide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13803</drugbank-id>
      <name>Xipamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Xipamide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14033</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetyl sulfisoxazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Acetyl sulfisoxazole is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14708</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tosylchloramide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tosylchloramide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00042</drugbank-id>
      <name>Botulinum Toxin Type B</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Botulinum Toxin Type B is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00083</drugbank-id>
      <name>Botulinum toxin type A</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Botulinum toxin type A is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00091</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclosporine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Cyclosporine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00254</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxycycline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Doxycycline is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00256</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lymecycline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Lymecycline is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00314</drugbank-id>
      <name>Capreomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Capreomycin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00319</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piperacillin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Piperacillin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00452</drugbank-id>
      <name>Framycetin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Framycetin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00453</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clomocycline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Clomocycline is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00468</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Quinine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00512</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vancomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Vancomycin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00560</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tigecycline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tigecycline is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxytetracycline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Oxytetracycline is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00608</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chloroquine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Chloroquine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00618</drugbank-id>
      <name>Demeclocycline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Demeclocycline is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00653</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium sulfate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium sulfate is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00657</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mecamylamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Mecamylamine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00684</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tobramycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tobramycin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00759</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetracycline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tetracycline is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00798</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gentamicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Gentamicin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00903</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etacrynic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Etacrynic acid is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00908</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinidine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Quinidine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00931</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metacycline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Metacycline is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00955</drugbank-id>
      <name>Netilmicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Netilmicin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00994</drugbank-id>
      <name>Neomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Neomycin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01017</drugbank-id>
      <name>Minocycline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Minocycline is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01035</drugbank-id>
      <name>Procainamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Procainamide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01082</drugbank-id>
      <name>Streptomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Streptomycin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01111</drugbank-id>
      <name>Colistimethate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Colistimethate is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01172</drugbank-id>
      <name>Kanamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Kanamycin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01190</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clindamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Clindamycin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01219</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dantrolene</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Dantrolene is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01301</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rolitetracycline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Rolitetracycline is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01377</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium oxide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium oxide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01378</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium cation</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium cation is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01421</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paromomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Paromomycin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01627</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lincomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Lincomycin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ribostamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ribostamycin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04263</drugbank-id>
      <name>Geneticin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Geneticin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04626</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apramycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Apramycin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04729</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gentamicin C1a</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Gentamicin C1a is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04808</drugbank-id>
      <name>Neamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Neamine is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06696</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arbekacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Arbekacin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06827</drugbank-id>
      <name>Viomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Viomycin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08437</drugbank-id>
      <name>Puromycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Puromycin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09104</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium hydroxide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium hydroxide is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09281</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium trisilicate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium trisilicate is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09407</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium chloride</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium chloride is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09409</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium acetate tetrahydrate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium acetate tetrahydrate is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09481</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium carbonate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium carbonate is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11110</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium citrate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium citrate is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11189</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium glycinate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium glycinate is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11230</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium Aluminum Silicate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium Aluminum Silicate is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11512</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dihydrostreptomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Dihydrostreptomycin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11520</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hygromycin B</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Hygromycin B is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12604</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sisomicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sisomicin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Plazomicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Plazomicin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13249</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium silicate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium silicate is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penimepicycline</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Penimepicycline is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13270</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dibekacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Dibekacin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13274</drugbank-id>
      <name>Micronomicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Micronomicin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13359</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium aspartate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium aspartate is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13540</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isepamicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Isepamicin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13673</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bekanamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Bekanamycin is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13749</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium gluconate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium gluconate is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13786</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium orotate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium orotate is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13862</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium phosphate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium phosphate is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13996</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium acetate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Magnesium acetate is combined with Cyclopentamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <calculated-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>2.86</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logS</kind>
      <value>-2.5</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Water Solubility</kind>
      <value>4.76e-01 g/l</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>2.26</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>(1-cyclopentylpropan-2-yl)(methyl)amine</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Traditional IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>sinos</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Weight</kind>
      <value>141.258</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Monoisotopic Weight</kind>
      <value>141.151749616</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>SMILES</kind>
      <value>CNC(C)CC1CCCC1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Formula</kind>
      <value>C9H19N</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChI</kind>
      <value>InChI=1S/C9H19N/c1-8(10-2)7-9-5-3-4-6-9/h8-10H,3-7H2,1-2H3</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChIKey</kind>
      <value>HFXKQSZZZPGLKQ-UHFFFAOYSA-N</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polar Surface Area (PSA)</kind>
      <value>12.03</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Refractivity</kind>
      <value>44.93</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polarizability</kind>
      <value>18.4</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rotatable Bond Count</kind>
      <value>3</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Acceptor Count</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Donor Count</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest basic)</kind>
      <value>10.61</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Physiological Charge</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Number of Rings</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Bioavailability</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rule of Five</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Ghose Filter</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>MDDR-Like Rule</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
  </calculated-properties>
  <experimental-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>Melting Point</kind>
      <value>113-115</value>
      <source>U.S. Patent 2,520,015.</source>
    </property>
  </experimental-properties>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEBI</resource>
      <identifier>134766</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Compound</resource>
      <identifier>7608</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>310264960</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>KEGG Drug</resource>
      <identifier>D07370</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChemSpider</resource>
      <identifier>7326</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>BindingDB</resource>
      <identifier>81456</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Wikipedia</resource>
      <identifier>Cyclopentamine</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEMBL</resource>
      <identifier>CHEMBL329203</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>