<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-11-18" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05384</drugbank-id>
  <name>Carbopol 974P</name>
  <description>Carbopol 974P is a highly carboxylated polymer composed of lightly cross-linked polyacrylic acid with a broad-spectrum mechanism based on acidification of pathogens. It was under development by ReProtect LLC. It is a gel that may help both block the spread of sexually transmitted diseases and reduce unwanted pregnancies. The compound, known as BufferGel, was in advanced clinical trials for its ability to prevent pregnancy, but was discontinued.</description>
  <cas-number>151687-96-6</cas-number>
  <unii>HHT01ZNK31</unii>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3416</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>11176265</pubmed-id>
        <citation>van De Wijgert J, Fullem A, Kelly C, Mehendale S, Rugpao S, Kumwenda N, Chirenje Z, Joshi S, Taha T, Padian N, Bollinger R, Nelson K: Phase 1 trial of the topical microbicide BufferGel: safety results from four international sites. J Acquir Immune Defic Syndr. 2001 Jan 1;26(1):21-7.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3417</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>12869836</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Tabet SR, Callahan MM, Mauck CK, Gai F, Coletti AS, Profy AT, Moench TR, Soto-Torres LE, Poindexter III AN, Frezieres RG, Walsh TL, Kelly CW, Richardson BA, Van Damme L, Celum CL: Safety and acceptability of penile application of 2 candidate topical microbicides: BufferGel and PRO 2000 Gel: 3 randomized trials in healthy low-risk men and HIV-positive men. J Acquir Immune Defic Syndr. 2003 Aug 1;33(4):476-83.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in contraception and HIV prevention.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>BufferGel is a microbicidal spermicide that provides sufficient buffering activity to maintain the mild, protective acidity of the vagina in the presence of semen. Sperm are acid-sensitive, so to assure fertility, semen provides a powerful alkalinizing action that abolishes the protective acidity of the vagina for several hours after intercourse.  This alkalinizing action of semen also enables acid-sensitive sexually transmitted diseases (STD) pathogens to transmit infection.  By blocking this action of semen, BufferGel prevents unwanted pregnancy, and shows promise for prevention of STDs, including HIV/AIDS.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Carbomer 974 (P)</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Carbomer 974P</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">carbomer homopolymer type b</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Carbomer homopolymer type B (allyl pentaerythritol crosslinked)</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Carbomer-974P</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Carbopol polymer</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products/>
  <international-brands>
    <international-brand>
      <name>BufferGel</name>
      <company/>
    </international-brand>
  </international-brands>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Compounds used in a research, industrial, or household setting</category>
      <mesh-id>D020313</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Macromolecular Substances</category>
      <mesh-id>D046911</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Plastics</category>
      <mesh-id>D010969</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Polymers</category>
      <mesh-id>D011108</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Resins, Synthetic</category>
      <mesh-id>D012117</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Spermatocidal Agents</category>
      <mesh-id>D013089</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06480</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prucalopride</name>
      <description>Prucalopride may increase the excretion rate of Carbopol 974P which could result in a lower serum level and potentially a reduction in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>175426991</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>