<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2007-10-21" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB04921</drugbank-id>
  <name>Dirucotide</name>
  <description>Dirucotide is a synthetically prepared peptide. In particular, the sequence prepared is a 17 amino acid chain that is identical to a section of myelin basic protein (MBP) that is found in humans. Dirucotide has been developed for the treatment of multiple sclerosis (MS). Developed at the University of Alberta, dirucotide is being investigated by BioMS Medical Corp.</description>
  <cas-number>152074-97-0</cas-number>
  <unii>26188K0CWH</unii>
  <state>liquid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A2961</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>16879301</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Warren KG, Catz I, Ferenczi LZ, Krantz MJ: Intravenous synthetic peptide MBP8298 delayed disease progression in an HLA Class II-defined cohort of patients with progressive multiple sclerosis: results of a 24-month double-blind placebo-controlled clinical trial and 5 years of follow-up treatment. Eur J Neurol. 2006 Aug;13(8):887-95.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>For the treatment of multiple sclerosis (MS).</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>MS is generally considered an autoimmune disease, caused by immune attack against normal components of the central nervous system. The specificity of the immune attack at the molecular level is determined in each case by the HLA type of the individual patient, and HLA type is known to be one factor that contributes to susceptibility to MS. The MBP8298 synthetic peptide is a molecular replicate of the site of attack that is dominant in MS patients with HLA haplotypes DR-2 or DR-4. These HLA types are found in 65-75% of all MS patients.</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>The apparent mechanism of action of MBP8298 is the induction or restoration of immunological tolerance with respect to ongoing immune attack at this molecular site. High doses of antigen delivered periodically by the intravenous route are expected to suppress immune responses to the administered substance. The potential benefit of MBP8298 for any individual patient is therefore expected to be related to the extent to which his or her disease process is dominated by autoimmune attack at the site represented by this synthetic peptide.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Proteins</category>
      <mesh-id>D000602</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Membrane Proteins</category>
      <mesh-id>D008565</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Myelin Proteins</category>
      <mesh-id>D009185</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nerve Tissue Proteins</category>
      <mesh-id>D009419</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Peptides</category>
      <mesh-id>D010455</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Proteins</category>
      <mesh-id>D011506</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences>
    <sequence format="FASTA">&gt;MBP8298 Sequence
DENPVVHFFKNIVTPRT</sequence>
  </sequences>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347909848</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Wikipedia</resource>
      <identifier>Dirucotide</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>