<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2008-03-19" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB06394</drugbank-id>
  <name>Riferminogene pecaplasmid</name>
  <description>Riferminogene pecaplasmid (non-viral fibroblast growth factor 1; NV1FGF) is a recombinant DNA plasmid in a pCOR backbone allowing expression of human FGF1.</description>
  <cas-number>1001859-46-6</cas-number>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A6805</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>18388929</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Nikol S, Baumgartner I, Van Belle E, Diehm C, Visona A, Capogrossi MC, Ferreira-Maldent N, Gallino A, Wyatt MG, Wijesinghe LD, Fusari M, Stephan D, Emmerich J, Pompilio G, Vermassen F, Pham E, Grek V, Coleman M, Meyer F: Therapeutic angiogenesis with intramuscular NV1FGF improves amputation-free survival in patients with critical limb ischemia. Mol Ther. 2008 May;16(5):972-8. doi: 10.1038/mt.2008.33. Epub 2008 Apr 1.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in amputation (limb) and peripheral vascular disease.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>NV1FGF is a novel pCOR DNA plasmid–based gene delivery system for local expression of FGF-1. The pCOR plasmid backbone has several features that increase biosafety. These attributes include replication in only a narrow host range of laboratory, but not wild type, Escherichia coli strains, absence of an antibiotic-resistance gene, and lack of the potentially immunostimulatory sequence motifs found in ColE1 plasmids. Preclinical studies of intramuscular administration of NV1FGF have demonstrated that local expression of FGF-1 persists for several weeks. The angiogenic effect of NV1FGF was confirmed in the more severe animal model. The administration of NV1FGF in the hypercholesterolemic hamster model of hindlimb ischemia significantly enhanced the formation of large conductance vessels as well as small resistance arteries in ischemia-injured muscles.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Non-viral fibroblast growth factor 1</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">NV1FGF</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="inn">Riferminogene pecaplasmid</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products/>
  <international-brands>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Temusi</name>
      <company>Sanofi</company>
    </international-brand>
  </international-brands>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers/>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>