<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-11-18" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05480</drugbank-id>
  <name>PBI-1402</name>
  <description>PBI-1402 is a small molecule synthetic compound with oral&#13;
Bioavailability. The compound activates neutrophils, enhancing their survival and activation with comparable efficacy to GM-CSF, G-CSF and EPO, which are currently used to treat anemia. However, it has been shown that when co-administered with these compounds, effects are additive, making PBI-1402 an excellent candidate for combination therapy and asserting its independent mechanism of action. PBI-1402 appears to work on the PMN pathway, but its specific binding properties are not known. PBI-1402 has a dual therapeutic action; as a chemoprotectant and hematopoietic progenitor stimulator. Since it stimulates immune activity, it has been considered as a candidate for cancer treatment as well as anemia.&#13;
</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in adverse effects (chemotherapy), anemia, and chemotherapy.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>PBI-1402 is a small molecule synthetic compound with oral&#13;
Bioavailability. The compound activates neutrophils, enhancing their survival and activation with comparable efficacy to GM-CSF, G-CSF and EPO, which are currently used to treat anemia. PBI-1402 has a dual therapeutic action; as a chemoprotectant and hematopoietic progenitor stimulator. </pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>PBI-1402 activates neutrophils, enhancing their survival and activation with comparable efficacy to GM-CSF, G-CSF and EPO, which are currently used to treat anemia. However, it has been shown that when co-administered with these compounds, effects are additive, making PBI-1402 an excellent candidate for combination therapy and asserting its independent mechanism of action. PBI-1402 appears to work on the PMN pathway, but its specific binding properties are not known.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910163</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>