<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-10-21" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05143</drugbank-id>
  <name>OXI-4503</name>
  <description>OXI-4503 is investigated in clinical trials for treating cancer/tumors. OXI-4503 is a solid. OXI-4503 blocks and destroys tumor vasculature, resulting in extensive tumor cell death and necrosis. OXI-4503 (combretastatin A1 di-phosphate / CA1P) is a unique and highly potent, dual-mechanism vascular disrupting agent (VDA). In addition, however, preclinical data demonstrates that OXI-4503 is metabolized by oxidative enzymes (e.g., tyrosinase and peroxidases), which are elevated in many solid tumors and tumor infiltrates, to an orthoquinone chemical species that has direct cytotoxic effects on tumor cells. Preclinical studies have demonstrated that OXI-4503 has (i) single-agent activity against a range of xenograft tumor models; and (ii) synergistic or additive effects when incorporated in various combination regimens with chemotherapy, molecularly-targeted therapies (including tumor-angiogenesis inhibitors), and radiation therapy.</description>
  <cas-number>288847-35-8</cas-number>
  <unii>JH6Z94GLUD</unii>
  <average-mass>492.31</average-mass>
  <monoisotopic-mass>492.058650144</monoisotopic-mass>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3268</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>18043126</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Chan LS, Malcontenti-Wilson C, Muralidharan V, Christophi C: Alterations in vascular architecture and permeability following OXi4503 treatment. Anticancer Drugs. 2008 Jan;19(1):17-22.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3269</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>18038290</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Hokland SL, Horsman MR: The new vascular disrupting agent combretastatin-A1-disodium-phosphate (OXi4503) enhances tumour response to mild hyperthermia and thermoradiosensitization. Int J Hyperthermia. 2007 Nov;23(7):599-606.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3270</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17695520</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Chan LS, Malcontenti-Wilson C, Muralidharan V, Christophi C: Effect of vascular targeting agent Oxi4503 on tumor cell kinetics in a mouse model of colorectal liver metastasis. Anticancer Res. 2007 Jul-Aug;27(4B):2317-23.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3271</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>16818709</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Salmon HW, Siemann DW: Effect of the second-generation vascular disrupting agent OXi4503 on tumor vascularity. Clin Cancer Res. 2006 Jul 1;12(13):4090-4.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in cancer/tumors (unspecified).</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>OXi4503 blocks and destroys tumor vasculature, resulting in extensive tumor cell death and necrosis. In addition, however, preclinical data demonstrates that OXi4503 is metabolized by oxidative enzymes (e.g., tyrosinase and peroxidases), which are elevated in many solid tumors and tumor infiltrates, to an orthoquinone chemical species that has direct cytotoxic effects on tumor cells.</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>OXi4503 blocks and destroys tumor vasculature, resulting in extensive tumor cell death and necrosis. It induced the shutdown of tumor blood vessels and affected peripheral tumor regions less than central regions.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description>This compound belongs to the class of organic compounds known as stilbenes. These are organic compounds containing a 1,2-diphenylethylene moiety. Stilbenes (C6-C2-C6 ) are derived from the common phenylpropene (C6-C3) skeleton building block. The introduction of one or more hydroxyl groups  to a phenyl ring lead to stilbenoids.</description>
    <direct-parent>Stilbenes</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Phenylpropanoids and polyketides</superclass>
    <class>Stilbenes</class>
    <subclass/>
    <alternative-parent>Alkyl aryl ethers</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Anisoles</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Hydrocarbon derivatives</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Methoxybenzenes</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Organic oxides</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Phenoxy compounds</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Phenyl phosphates</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Styrenes</alternative-parent>
    <substituent>Alkyl aryl ether</substituent>
    <substituent>Anisole</substituent>
    <substituent>Aromatic homomonocyclic compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Aryl phosphate</substituent>
    <substituent>Aryl phosphomonoester</substituent>
    <substituent>Benzenoid</substituent>
    <substituent>Ether</substituent>
    <substituent>Hydrocarbon derivative</substituent>
    <substituent>Methoxybenzene</substituent>
    <substituent>Monocyclic benzene moiety</substituent>
    <substituent>Organic oxide</substituent>
    <substituent>Organic oxygen compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Organic phosphoric acid derivative</substituent>
    <substituent>Organooxygen compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Phenol ether</substituent>
    <substituent>Phenoxy compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Phenyl phosphate</substituent>
    <substituent>Phosphoric acid ester</substituent>
    <substituent>Stilbene</substituent>
    <substituent>Styrene</substituent>
  </classification>
  <salts>
    <salt>
      <drugbank-id primary="true">DBSALT001872</drugbank-id>
      <name>OXI-4503 dipotassium</name>
      <unii>Q9F7QEH36F</unii>
      <cas-number>1014615-46-3</cas-number>
      <inchikey>IQYUGENRXZHYER-XNOMRPDFSA-L</inchikey>
      <average-mass>568.49</average-mass>
      <monoisotopic-mass>567.97041306</monoisotopic-mass>
    </salt>
  </salts>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">CA1P</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Combretastatin A-1 bis(phosphate)</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Combretastatin A1 diphosphate</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">OXI4503</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Acids</category>
      <mesh-id>D000143</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Acids, Noncarboxylic</category>
      <mesh-id>D000148</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Anions</category>
      <mesh-id>D000838</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Benzene Derivatives</category>
      <mesh-id>D001555</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Benzylidene Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D001597</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Electrolytes</category>
      <mesh-id>D004573</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Ions</category>
      <mesh-id>D007477</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Phosphate salts</category>
      <mesh-id>D010710</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Phosphoric Acids</category>
      <mesh-id>D010756</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Phosphorus Acids</category>
      <mesh-id>D017976</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Phosphorus Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D017553</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Polyphosphates</category>
      <mesh-id>D011122</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00258</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium acetate</name>
      <description>Calcium acetate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00326</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium glucoheptonate</name>
      <description>Calcium glucoheptonate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01164</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium chloride</name>
      <description>Calcium Chloride can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01373</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium</name>
      <description>Calcium can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06724</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium carbonate</name>
      <description>Calcium carbonate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11093</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium Citrate</name>
      <description>Calcium Citrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11126</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium gluconate</name>
      <description>Calcium gluconate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11348</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium Phosphate</name>
      <description>Calcium Phosphate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13142</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium glubionate anhydrous</name>
      <description>Calcium glubionate anhydrous can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13231</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium lactate</name>
      <description>Calcium lactate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13365</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium lactate gluconate</name>
      <description>Calcium lactate gluconate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13590</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium pangamate</name>
      <description>Calcium pangamate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14577</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium cation</name>
      <description>Calcium cation can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14684</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium polycarbophil</name>
      <description>Calcium polycarbophil can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00364</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sucralfate</name>
      <description>Sucralfate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00653</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium sulfate</name>
      <description>Magnesium sulfate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01397</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium salicylate</name>
      <description>Magnesium salicylate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08938</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magaldrate</name>
      <description>Magaldrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09407</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium chloride</name>
      <description>Magnesium chloride can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11110</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium citrate</name>
      <description>Magnesium citrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13322</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrotalcite</name>
      <description>Hydrotalcite can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13359</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium aspartate</name>
      <description>Magnesium aspartate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13749</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium gluconate</name>
      <description>Magnesium gluconate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13786</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium orotate</name>
      <description>Magnesium orotate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14513</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium</name>
      <description>Magnesium can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14514</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium levulinate</name>
      <description>Magnesium levulinate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14515</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium lactate</name>
      <description>Magnesium lactate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01370</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aluminium</name>
      <description>Aluminium can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01377</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium oxide</name>
      <description>Magnesium oxide can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06723</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aluminum hydroxide</name>
      <description>Aluminum hydroxide can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09104</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium hydroxide</name>
      <description>Magnesium hydroxide can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09281</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium trisilicate</name>
      <description>Magnesium trisilicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09481</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium carbonate</name>
      <description>Magnesium carbonate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13249</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium silicate</name>
      <description>Magnesium silicate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13280</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aluminium acetoacetate</name>
      <description>Aluminium acetoacetate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13486</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium peroxide</name>
      <description>Magnesium peroxide can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13626</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aluminium glycinate</name>
      <description>Aluminium glycinate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00325</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitroprusside</name>
      <description>Nitroprusside can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00893</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iron Dextran</name>
      <description>Iron Dextran can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01592</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iron</name>
      <description>Iron can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06215</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferumoxytol</name>
      <description>Ferumoxytol can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prussian blue</name>
      <description>Prussian blue can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08917</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric carboxymaltose</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09146</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iron sucrose</name>
      <description>Iron sucrose can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09147</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric pyrophosphate</name>
      <description>Ferric pyrophosphate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09501</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric ammonium citrate</name>
      <description>Ferric ammonium citrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09507</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferumoxsil</name>
      <description>Ferumoxsil can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09508</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferumoxides</name>
      <description>Ferumoxides can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11171</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric sulfate</name>
      <description>Ferric sulfate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11210</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous bisglycinate</name>
      <description>Ferrous bisglycinate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11417</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gleptoferron</name>
      <description>Gleptoferron can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11576</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric oxide</name>
      <description>Ferric oxide can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iron isomaltoside 1000</name>
      <description>Iron isomaltoside 1000 can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12821</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perflubutane</name>
      <description>Perflubutane can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13257</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous sulfate anhydrous</name>
      <description>Ferrous sulfate anhydrous can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13381</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium feredetate</name>
      <description>Sodium feredetate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13423</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric hydroxide</name>
      <description>Ferric hydroxide can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13569</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous chloride</name>
      <description>Ferrous chloride can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13949</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric cation</name>
      <description>Ferric cation can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14488</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous gluconate</name>
      <description>Ferrous gluconate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14489</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous succinate</name>
      <description>Ferrous succinate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14491</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferrous fumarate</name>
      <description>Ferrous fumarate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14520</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetraferric tricitrate decahydrate</name>
      <description>Tetraferric tricitrate decahydrate can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14695</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric oxyhydroxide</name>
      <description>Ferric oxyhydroxide can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <calculated-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>1.76</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logS</kind>
      <value>-4.3</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Water Solubility</kind>
      <value>2.68e-02 g/l</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>1.77</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>[3-methoxy-2-(phosphonooxy)-6-[(Z)-2-(3,4,5-trimethoxyphenyl)ethenyl]phenoxy]phosphonic acid</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Traditional IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>3-methoxy-2-(phosphonooxy)-6-[(Z)-2-(3,4,5-trimethoxyphenyl)ethenyl]phenoxyphosphonic acid</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Weight</kind>
      <value>492.31</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Monoisotopic Weight</kind>
      <value>492.058650144</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>SMILES</kind>
      <value>[H]\C(=C(/[H])C1=C(OP(O)(O)=O)C(OP(O)(O)=O)=C(OC)C=C1)C1=CC(OC)=C(OC)C(OC)=C1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Formula</kind>
      <value>C18H22O12P2</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChI</kind>
      <value>InChI=1S/C18H22O12P2/c1-25-13-8-7-12(16(29-31(19,20)21)18(13)30-32(22,23)24)6-5-11-9-14(26-2)17(28-4)15(10-11)27-3/h5-10H,1-4H3,(H2,19,20,21)(H2,22,23,24)/b6-5-</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChIKey</kind>
      <value>GSOXMQLWUDQTNT-WAYWQWQTSA-N</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polar Surface Area (PSA)</kind>
      <value>170.44</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Refractivity</kind>
      <value>113.07</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polarizability</kind>
      <value>43.31</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rotatable Bond Count</kind>
      <value>10</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Acceptor Count</kind>
      <value>10</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Donor Count</kind>
      <value>4</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest acidic)</kind>
      <value>1.31</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest basic)</kind>
      <value>-4.3</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Physiological Charge</kind>
      <value>-4</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Number of Rings</kind>
      <value>2</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Bioavailability</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rule of Five</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Ghose Filter</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>MDDR-Like Rule</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
  </calculated-properties>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Compound</resource>
      <identifier>6918546</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>175426952</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChemSpider</resource>
      <identifier>5293743</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>BindingDB</resource>
      <identifier>50236033</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEMBL</resource>
      <identifier>CHEMBL1205402</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>