<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2005-06-13" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB00479</drugbank-id>
  <drugbank-id>APRD00550</drugbank-id>
  <name>Amikacin</name>
  <description>Amikacin is a semi-synthetic aminoglycoside antibiotic that is derived from kanamycin A.[FDA label] Amikacin is synthesized by acylation with the l-(-)-γ-amino-α-hydroxybutyryl side chain at the C-1 amino group of the deoxystreptamine moiety of kanamycin A.[A39531]&#13;
&#13;
Amikacin's unique property is that it exerts activity against more resistant gram-negative bacilli such as Acinetobacter baumanii and Pseudomonas aeruginosa. Amikacin also exerts excellent activity against most aerobic gram-negative bacilli from the Enterobacteriaceae family, including Nocardia and some Mycobacterium (M. avium-intracellulare, M. chelonae, and M. fortuitum)[L4680]. M. avium-intracellulare (MAC) is a type of nontuberculous mycobacteria (NTM) found in water and soil. Symptoms of this disease include a persistent cough, fatigue, weight loss, night sweats, and shortness of breath and the coughing up of blood.[L4680]&#13;
&#13;
Several forms of amikacin are used currently, including an intravenous (IV) or intramuscular (IM) injection.[F1949] In September 2018, a liposomal inhalation suspension of this drug was approved by the FDA for the treatment of lung disease caused by Mycobacterium avium complex (MAC) bacteria in a small population of patients with the disease who do not respond to traditional treatment.[L4680,L4681]</description>
  <cas-number>37517-28-5</cas-number>
  <unii>84319SGC3C</unii>
  <average-mass>585.6025</average-mass>
  <monoisotopic-mass>585.285736487</monoisotopic-mass>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
    <group>investigational</group>
    <group>vet_approved</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A711</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>10319086</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Edson RS, Terrell CL: The aminoglycosides. Mayo Clin Proc. 1999 May;74(5):519-28.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A39531</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>29257114</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Ramirez MS, Tolmasky ME: Amikacin: Uses, Resistance, and Prospects for Inhibition. Molecules. 2017 Dec 19;22(12). pii: molecules22122267. doi: 10.3390/molecules22122267.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L4673</ref-id>
        <title>FDA Approves Arikayce</title>
        <url>https://www.drugs.com/newdrugs/fda-approves-arikayce-amikacin-liposome-inhalation-suspension-mycobacterium-avium-complex-mac-lung-4829.html</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L4680</ref-id>
        <title>Stat Pearls: Amikacin</title>
        <url>https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK430908/</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L4681</ref-id>
        <title>FDA approves a new antibacterial drug to treat a serious lung disease using a novel pathway to spur innovation</title>
        <url>https://www.fda.gov/NewsEvents/Newsroom/PressAnnouncements/ucm622048.htm</url>
      </link>
    </links>
    <attachments>
      <attachment>
        <ref-id>F1949</ref-id>
        <title>MedSafe NZ: Amikacin Injection</title>
        <url>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/cite_this/attachments/files/000/001/949/original/Amikacininj._MedSafe_NZ.pdf?1540245431</url>
      </attachment>
      <attachment>
        <ref-id>F1950</ref-id>
        <title>EMA Withdrawal document, Arikayce</title>
        <url>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/cite_this/attachments/files/000/001/950/original/withdrawal-assessment-report-arikayce_en.pdf?1540245524</url>
      </attachment>
      <attachment>
        <ref-id>F1954</ref-id>
        <title>Amikacin, DailyMed</title>
        <url>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/cite_this/attachments/files/000/001/954/original/20180501_f260ff2a-76a0-4672-9516-91c344b67890.pdf?1540315949</url>
      </attachment>
    </attachments>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference>Alberto Mangia, Vicenzo Giobbio, Giorgio Ornato, "Novel process for the synthesis of amikacin." U.S. Patent US4902790, issued August, 1984.</synthesis-reference>
  <indication>The amikacin sulfate injection is indicated in the short-term treatment of serious bacterial infections due to susceptible strains of gram-negative bacteria, including Pseudomonas species, Escherichia coli, species of indole-positive and indole-negative Proteus, Providencia species, Klebsiella-Enterobacter-Serratia species, as well as Acinetobacter (Mima-Herellea) species.[F1954]&#13;
&#13;
Clinical studies have shown amikacin sulfate injection to be effective in bacterial septicemia (including neonatal sepsis); in serious infections of the respiratory tract, bones and joints, central nervous system (including meningitis) and skin and soft tissue; intra-abdominal infections (including peritonitis); and in burns and postoperative infections (including post-vascular surgery).[F1954]&#13;
&#13;
Clinical studies have shown amikacin also to be effective in serious, complicated, and recurrent urinary tract infections due to the above organisms. Aminoglycosides, including amikacin, are not indicated in uncomplicated first-time episodes of urinary tract infections unless the causative organisms are not susceptible to antibiotics which are less toxic.[F1954]&#13;
&#13;
In September 2018, a new indication with a new dosage route was approved for this drug. Amikacin liposome inhalation suspension was approved for the treatment of lung disease caused by a group of bacteria, Mycobacterium avium complex (MAC) in a limited population of patients with the disease who do not respond to conventional treatment (refractory disease).[L4673] This indication is approved under accelerated approval based on achieving sputum culture conversion (defined as 3 consecutive negative monthly sputum cultures) by Month 6 of treatment. Clinical benefit has not yet been established.[Label]&#13;
&#13;
**Important notes regarding Staphylococcus and Sensitivity testing:**&#13;
&#13;
Staphylococcus aureus, including methicillin-resistant strains, is the principal Gram-positive organism sensitive to amikacin.&#13;
The use of amikacin in the treatment of staphylococcal infections should be restricted only to second-line therapy, and should be limited to only those patients suffering from severe infections caused by susceptible strains of staphylococcus species who have failed to show sensitivity to other available antibiotics.[F1949]&#13;
&#13;
Bacteriologic studies should be performed to identify causative organisms and their susceptibilities to amikacin. Amikacin may be used as initial therapy in suspected gram-negative infections and therapy may be initiated before obtaining the results of susceptibility testing.[Label,F1949,F1954]</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>Amikacin is an aminoglycoside antibiotic. Aminoglycosides bind to the bacteria, causing misreading of t-RNA, leaving bacteria unable to synthesize proteins vital to their growth. Aminoglycosides are useful mainly in the treatment infections involving aerobic, Gram-negative bacteria, such as Pseudomonas, Acinetobacter, and Enterobacter. In addition, some mycobacteria, including the bacteria that cause tuberculosis, are susceptible to aminoglycosides. Infections caused by Gram-positive bacteria can also be treated with aminoglycosides, however, other antibiotics may be more potent and less toxic to humans.[Label,F1949]</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>The primary mechanism of action of amikacin is the same as that for all aminoglycosides. It binds to bacterial 30S ribosomal subunits and interferes with mRNA binding and tRNA acceptor sites, interfering with bacterial growth. This leads to disruption of normal protein synthesis and production of non-functional or toxic peptides. Other actions have been postulated for drugs of this class.[Label,F1949,F1950] Amikacin, as well as the rest of the aminoglycosides, are generally bacteriocidal against gram-positive and gram-negative bacteria.[L4680,F1954]</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity>**Oral (LD50):** 6000 mg/kg (Mouse) [MSDS]. No antidote for toxicity is currently available. This drug is only 20% dialyzable; however, this is variable based on the type hemodialysis filter used.[L4680]&#13;
&#13;
**Nephrotoxicity** &#13;
&#13;
Mild and reversible nephrotoxicity may be observed in 5 - 25% of patients. Amikacin accumulates in the proximal renal tubular cells. Tubular cell regeneration occurs despite continued drug exposure. Toxicity most commonly occurs several days following initiation of therapy. Amikacin may exacerbate pre-existing renal disease.[Label]&#13;
&#13;
**Ototoxicity**&#13;
&#13;
May cause irreversible ototoxicity.[Label] Ototoxicity appears to be correlated to cumulative exposure. Drug accumulation in the endolymph and perilymph of the inner ear causes irreversible damage to hair cells of the cochlea or summit of ampullar cristae in the vestibular complex. High- frequency hearing is lost first with progression leading to loss of low-frequency hearing. Further toxicity may lead to retrograde degeneration of the 8th cranial (vestibulocochlear) nerve. Vestibular toxicity may cause vertigo, nausea, vomiting, dizziness, and loss of balance.[F1949,Label]&#13;
&#13;
**Neuromuscular blockade**&#13;
&#13;
In addition to the above, amikacin may exacerbate neuromuscular blockade, however, this is less common.[Label,L4680]&#13;
&#13;
**Use in Pregnancy**&#13;
&#13;
Category D. Gentamicin and other aminoglycosides are known to cross the placenta. There is evidence of selective uptake of gentamicin by the fetal kidney resulting in damage to immature nephrons. Eighth cranial nerve damage has also been reported after in-utero exposure to some of the aminoglycosides. Because of the chemical similarity, all aminoglycosides should be considered potentially nephrotoxic and ototoxic to the developing fetus. Therapeutic blood amikacin levels in the mother do not equate with safety for the fetus. In reproductive toxicity studies in mice and rats, no effects on fertility or fetal toxicity were observed.[F1949]&#13;
&#13;
**Use in Lactation**&#13;
&#13;
It is not known whether amikacin is excreted in breast milk. Since the possible harmful effect on the infant is not known, it is recommended that if nursing mothers must be given amikacin, the infants should not be breastfed during therapy.[F1949]</toxicity>
  <metabolism>Amikacin's structure has been altered to reduce the possible route of enzymatic deactivation, thus reducing bacterial resistance. Many strains of Gram-negative organisms resistant to gentamicin and tobramycin have shown to be sensitive to amikacin in vitro.[F1949]&#13;
</metabolism>
  <absorption>Rapidly absorbed after intramuscular administration. Rapid absorption occurs from the peritoneum and pleura. Poor oral and topical absorption. Poorly absorbed from bladder irrigations and intrathecal administration.[F1954,Label]&#13;
&#13;
The bioavailability of this drug is expected to vary primarily from individual differences in nebulizer efficiency and airway pathology.[Label]&#13;
&#13;
Following IM administration of a single dose of amikacin of 7.5 mg/kg in adults with normal renal function, peak plasma amikacin concentrations of 17-25 micrograms/mL are attained within 45 minutes to 2 hours.[F1949]&#13;
&#13;
Following IV infusion of the same dose given over 1 hour peak plasma concentrations of the drug average 38 micrograms/mL immediately following the infusion, 5.5 micrograms/mL at 4 hours, and 1.3 micrograms/mL at 8 hours.[F1949]</absorption>
  <half-life>The plasma elimination half-life of amikacin is usually 2-3 hours in adults with normal renal function and is reported to range from 30-86 hours in adults with severe renal impairment.[Label]</half-life>
  <protein-binding>The protein binding of amikacin in serum is ≤ 10%.[Label]</protein-binding>
  <route-of-elimination>This drug is eliminated by the kidneys. In adults with normal renal function, 94-98% of a single IM or IV dose of amikacin is excreted unchanged by glomerular filtration in the kidney within 24 hours. Amikacin can be completely recovered within approximately 10-20 days in patients with normal, healthy renal function.[F1949]&#13;
&#13;
In patients with impaired renal function, the clearance of amikacin is found to be decreased; the more severe the impairment, the slower the clearance. The interval between doses of amikacin should be adjusted according to the level of renal impairment. Endogenous creatinine clearance rate and serum creatinine which have a high correlation with serum half-life of amikacin, may be used as a guide for dosing.[F1949]</route-of-elimination>
  <volume-of-distribution>* 24 L (28% of body weight healthy adult subjects).[F1954]&#13;
&#13;
Following administration of usual dosages of amikacin, amikacin has been found in bone, heart, gallbladder, and lung tissue. Amikacin is also distributed into bile, sputum, bronchial secretions, and interstitial, pleural, and synovial fluids.[F1949]</volume-of-distribution>
  <clearance>The mean serum clearance rate is about 100 mL/min and the renal clearance rate is 94 mL/min in subjects with normal renal function.[F1954]</clearance>
  <classification>
    <description>This compound belongs to the class of organic compounds known as 4,6-disubstituted 2-deoxystreptamines. These are 2-deoxystreptamine aminoglycosides that a glycosidically linked to a pyranose of furanose unit at the C4- and C6-positions.</description>
    <direct-parent>4,6-disubstituted 2-deoxystreptamines</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic oxygen compounds</superclass>
    <class>Organooxygen compounds</class>
    <subclass>Carbohydrates and carbohydrate conjugates</subclass>
    <alternative-parent>1,2-aminoalcohols</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>1,3-aminoalcohols</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Acetals</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Aminocyclitols and derivatives</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Carbonyl compounds</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Cyclohexanols</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Cyclohexylamines</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Gamma amino acids and derivatives</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Hydrocarbon derivatives</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Monoalkylamines</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Monosaccharides</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>N-acyl amines</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>O-glycosyl compounds</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Organic oxides</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Organopnictogen compounds</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Oxacyclic compounds</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Oxanes</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Polyols</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Primary alcohols</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Secondary carboxylic acid amides</alternative-parent>
    <substituent>1,2-aminoalcohol</substituent>
    <substituent>1,3-aminoalcohol</substituent>
    <substituent>4,6-disubstituted 2-deoxystreptamine</substituent>
    <substituent>Acetal</substituent>
    <substituent>Alcohol</substituent>
    <substituent>Aliphatic heteromonocyclic compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Amine</substituent>
    <substituent>Amino acid or derivatives</substituent>
    <substituent>Aminocyclitol or derivatives</substituent>
    <substituent>Carbonyl group</substituent>
    <substituent>Carboxamide group</substituent>
    <substituent>Carboxylic acid derivative</substituent>
    <substituent>Cyclic alcohol</substituent>
    <substituent>Cyclitol or derivatives</substituent>
    <substituent>Cyclohexanol</substituent>
    <substituent>Cyclohexylamine</substituent>
    <substituent>Fatty acyl</substituent>
    <substituent>Fatty amide</substituent>
    <substituent>Gamma amino acid or derivatives</substituent>
    <substituent>Glycosyl compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Hydrocarbon derivative</substituent>
    <substituent>Monosaccharide</substituent>
    <substituent>N-acyl-amine</substituent>
    <substituent>O-glycosyl compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Organic nitrogen compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Organic oxide</substituent>
    <substituent>Organoheterocyclic compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Organonitrogen compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Organopnictogen compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Oxacycle</substituent>
    <substituent>Oxane</substituent>
    <substituent>Polyol</substituent>
    <substituent>Primary alcohol</substituent>
    <substituent>Primary aliphatic amine</substituent>
    <substituent>Primary amine</substituent>
    <substituent>Secondary alcohol</substituent>
    <substituent>Secondary carboxylic acid amide</substituent>
  </classification>
  <salts>
    <salt>
      <drugbank-id primary="true">DBSALT000351</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amikacin sulfate</name>
      <unii>N6M33094FD</unii>
      <cas-number>39831-55-5</cas-number>
      <inchikey>FXKSEJFHKVNEFI-GCZBSULCSA-N</inchikey>
      <average-mass>781.759</average-mass>
      <monoisotopic-mass>781.220494971</monoisotopic-mass>
    </salt>
  </salts>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">1-N-(L(−)-γ-amino-α-hydroxybutyryl)kanamycin A</synonym>
    <synonym language="english/german" coder="inn">Amikacin</synonym>
    <synonym language="spanish" coder="inn">Amikacina</synonym>
    <synonym language="french" coder="inn">Amikacine</synonym>
    <synonym language="latin" coder="inn">Amikacinum</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <labeller>Bedford Pharmaceuticals</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>55390-225</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1994-05-31</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2010-03-31</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>50 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>ANDA063313</fda-application-number>
      <generic>true</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <labeller>Bedford Pharmaceuticals</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>55390-226</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1994-05-31</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2015-06-30</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>250 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>ANDA063315</fda-application-number>
      <generic>true</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <labeller>Bedford Pharmaceuticals</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>55390-223</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1997-07-10</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2009-12-31</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>50 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>ANDA063313</fda-application-number>
      <generic>true</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <labeller>Bedford Pharmaceuticals</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>55390-224</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1997-06-10</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2010-03-31</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>250 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>ANDA063315</fda-application-number>
      <generic>true</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>AMIKACIN Sulfate</name>
      <labeller>Hospira, Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>0409-1955</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2005-02-28</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2010-10-01</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>100 mg/2mL</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>ANDA063263</fda-application-number>
      <generic>true</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>AMIKACIN Sulfate</name>
      <labeller>Hospira, Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>0409-1956</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2005-09-12</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2012-11-01</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>500 mg/2mL</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>ANDA063264</fda-application-number>
      <generic>true</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>AMIKACIN Sulfate</name>
      <labeller>Hospira, Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>0409-1957</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2005-09-30</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2010-10-01</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>1 g/4mL</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>ANDA063264</fda-application-number>
      <generic>true</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <labeller>Sagent Pharmaceuticals</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>25021-173</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2016-06-15</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>250 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>ANDA203323</fda-application-number>
      <generic>true</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <labeller>Fresenius Kabi USA, LLC</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>63323-816</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2015-12-09</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2015-12-14</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>50 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>ANDA205605</fda-application-number>
      <generic>true</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <labeller>West-Ward Pharmaceuticals Corp.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>0641-6166</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2015-08-01</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Injection</dosage-form>
      <strength>250 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>ANDA063315</fda-application-number>
      <generic>true</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <labeller>West-Ward Pharmaceuticals Corp.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>0641-6167</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2015-08-01</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Injection</dosage-form>
      <strength>250 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>ANDA063315</fda-application-number>
      <generic>true</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <labeller>Fresenius Kabi USA, LLC</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>63323-815</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2015-12-09</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>250 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>ANDA205604</fda-application-number>
      <generic>true</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <labeller>Heritage Pharmaceuticals Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>23155-290</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2013-12-24</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>250 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>ANDA204040</fda-application-number>
      <generic>true</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <labeller>Teva Parenteral Medicines, Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>0703-9032</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1993-10-01</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>500 mg/2mL</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>ANDA064045</fda-application-number>
      <generic>true</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <labeller>Teva Parenteral Medicines, Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>0703-9040</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1993-10-01</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>1 g/4mL</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>ANDA064045</fda-application-number>
      <generic>true</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate Injection</name>
      <labeller>Omega Laboratories Ltd</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>02486717</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2019-07-31</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Solution</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate Injection USP</name>
      <labeller>Sandoz Canada Incorporated</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>02242971</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2001-01-29</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Liquid</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate Injection USP</name>
      <labeller>Marcan Pharmaceuticals Inc</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>02481073</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2019-03-01</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Solution</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate Injection, 500 mg/2ml</name>
      <labeller>Prodigy Innovation, LLC.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>70297-996</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2019-02-07</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Injection</dosage-form>
      <strength>500 mg/1</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>false</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikin</name>
      <labeller>E.R. Squibb &amp; Sons, L.L.C.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>0015-3015</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2006-01-01</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2007-07-31</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>50 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>ANDA062311</fda-application-number>
      <generic>true</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikin</name>
      <labeller>E.R. Squibb &amp; Sons, L.L.C.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>0015-3020</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2006-01-01</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2007-08-31</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>250 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>ANDA062311</fda-application-number>
      <generic>true</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikin</name>
      <labeller>E.R. Squibb &amp; Sons, L.L.C.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>0015-3023</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2006-01-01</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2007-07-31</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>250 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>ANDA062311</fda-application-number>
      <generic>true</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Amikin</name>
      <labeller>Bristol Myers Squibb</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>00397415</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1977-12-31</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2006-05-29</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>250 mg</strength>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Arikayce</name>
      <labeller>Insmed Incorporated</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>71558-590</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2018-10-12</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Suspension</dosage-form>
      <strength>590 mg/8.4mL</strength>
      <route>Respiratory (inhalation)</route>
      <fda-application-number>NDA207356</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Erfa-amikacin</name>
      <labeller>Erfa Canada 2012 Inc</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>02489147</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on/>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Solution</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Amexel</name>
      <company>Abbott</company>
    </international-brand>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Amukin</name>
      <company>Bristol-Myers Squibb</company>
    </international-brand>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Biklin</name>
      <company>Bristol-Myers Squibb</company>
    </international-brand>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Erkacin</name>
      <company>Brown &amp; Burk</company>
    </international-brand>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Farcyclin</name>
      <company>Faran Laboratories</company>
    </international-brand>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Flexelite</name>
      <company>Bros</company>
    </international-brand>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Kamin</name>
      <company>Bosch</company>
    </international-brand>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Novamin</name>
      <company>Bristol-Myers Squibb</company>
    </international-brand>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Selaxa</name>
      <company>Proel</company>
    </international-brand>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Selemycin</name>
      <company>Medochemie</company>
    </international-brand>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Sikacin</name>
      <company>Shiteh Organic</company>
    </international-brand>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Tipkin</name>
      <company>T P Drug</company>
    </international-brand>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Tybikin</name>
      <company>M &amp; H</company>
    </international-brand>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Ukaject</name>
      <company>Unimed Pharm</company>
    </international-brand>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Unikin</name>
      <company>Union</company>
    </international-brand>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Uzix</name>
      <company>Rafarm</company>
    </international-brand>
    <international-brand>
      <name>Xylanal</name>
      <company>Epsilon</company>
    </international-brand>
  </international-brands>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikin</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikin</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikin</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>AMIKACIN Sulfate</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>AMIKACIN Sulfate</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>AMIKACIN Sulfate</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Arikayce</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate Injection, 500 mg/2ml</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate Injection USP</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikin</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate Injection USP</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Amikacin Sulfate Injection</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Erfa-amikacin</name>
      <ingredients>Amikacin</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers>
    <packager>
      <name>Bedford Labs</name>
      <url>http://www.bedfordlabs.com</url>
    </packager>
    <packager>
      <name>Ben Venue Laboratories Inc.</name>
      <url>http://www.benvenue.com</url>
    </packager>
    <packager>
      <name>Bristol-Myers Squibb Co.</name>
      <url>http://www.bms.com</url>
    </packager>
    <packager>
      <name>Hospira Inc.</name>
      <url>http://www.hospira.com</url>
    </packager>
    <packager>
      <name>Mead Johnson and Co.</name>
      <url>http://www.meadjohnson.com</url>
    </packager>
    <packager>
      <name>Medisca Inc.</name>
      <url>http://www.medisca.com</url>
    </packager>
    <packager>
      <name>Sicor Pharmaceuticals</name>
      <url/>
    </packager>
    <packager>
      <name>Teva Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd.</name>
      <url>http://www.tevapharm.com</url>
    </packager>
  </packagers>
  <manufacturers>
    <manufacturer generic="true" url="">Abbott laboratories</manufacturer>
    <manufacturer generic="true" url="">Abbott laboratories hosp products div</manufacturer>
    <manufacturer generic="true" url="">Astrazeneca lp</manufacturer>
    <manufacturer generic="true" url="">Baxter healthcare corp anesthesia and critical care</manufacturer>
    <manufacturer generic="true" url="">Bedford laboratories div ben venue laboratories inc</manufacturer>
    <manufacturer generic="true" url="">Hospira inc</manufacturer>
    <manufacturer generic="true" url="">Teva parenteral medicines inc</manufacturer>
    <manufacturer generic="false" url="">Apothecon inc div bristol myers squibb</manufacturer>
  </manufacturers>
  <prices>
    <price>
      <description>Amikacin (pf) 100 mg/2 ml</description>
      <cost currency="USD">1.8</cost>
      <unit>ml</unit>
    </price>
    <price>
      <description>Amikacin 250 mg/ml vial</description>
      <cost currency="USD">2.19</cost>
      <unit>ml</unit>
    </price>
    <price>
      <description>Amikacin (pf) 500 mg/2 ml</description>
      <cost currency="USD">2.53</cost>
      <unit>ml</unit>
    </price>
    <price>
      <description>Amikacin sulfate powder</description>
      <cost currency="USD">26.01</cost>
      <unit>g</unit>
    </price>
  </prices>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Aminoglycoside Antibacterials</category>
      <mesh-id>D000617</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Anti-Bacterial Agents</category>
      <mesh-id>D000900</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Anti-Infective Agents</category>
      <mesh-id>D000890</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Antibacterials for Systemic Use</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Antiinfectives for Systemic Use</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Glycosides</category>
      <mesh-id>D006027</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Narrow Therapeutic Index Drugs</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nephrotoxic agents</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
    <affected-organism>Enteric bacteria and other eubacteria</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Injection</form>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <strength>250 mg/1mL</strength>
    </dosage>
    <dosage>
      <form>Injection, solution</form>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <strength>1 g/4mL</strength>
    </dosage>
    <dosage>
      <form>Injection, solution</form>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <strength>100 mg/2mL</strength>
    </dosage>
    <dosage>
      <form>Injection, solution</form>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <strength>500 mg/2mL</strength>
    </dosage>
    <dosage>
      <form>Liquid</form>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <strength/>
    </dosage>
    <dosage>
      <form>Solution</form>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <strength/>
    </dosage>
    <dosage>
      <form>Injection</form>
      <route>Intramuscular</route>
      <strength>500 mg/1</strength>
    </dosage>
    <dosage>
      <form>Injection, solution</form>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <strength>250 mg/1mL</strength>
    </dosage>
    <dosage>
      <form>Injection, solution</form>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <strength>50 mg/1mL</strength>
    </dosage>
    <dosage>
      <form>Solution</form>
      <route>Intramuscular; Intravenous</route>
      <strength>250 mg</strength>
    </dosage>
    <dosage>
      <form>Suspension</form>
      <route>Respiratory (inhalation)</route>
      <strength>590 mg/8.4mL</strength>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes>
    <atc-code code="S01AA21">
      <level code="S01AA">Antibiotics</level>
      <level code="S01A">ANTIINFECTIVES</level>
      <level code="S01">OPHTHALMOLOGICALS</level>
      <level code="S">SENSORY ORGANS</level>
    </atc-code>
    <atc-code code="D06AX12">
      <level code="D06AX">Other antibiotics for topical use</level>
      <level code="D06A">ANTIBIOTICS FOR TOPICAL USE</level>
      <level code="D06">ANTIBIOTICS AND CHEMOTHERAPEUTICS FOR DERMATOLOGICAL USE</level>
      <level code="D">DERMATOLOGICALS</level>
    </atc-code>
    <atc-code code="J01GB06">
      <level code="J01GB">Other aminoglycosides</level>
      <level code="J01G">AMINOGLYCOSIDE ANTIBACTERIALS</level>
      <level code="J01">ANTIBACTERIALS FOR SYSTEMIC USE</level>
      <level code="J">ANTIINFECTIVES FOR SYSTEMIC USE</level>
    </atc-code>
    <atc-code code="J01RA06">
      <level code="J01RA">Combinations of antibacterials</level>
      <level code="J01R">COMBINATIONS OF ANTIBACTERIALS</level>
      <level code="J01">ANTIBACTERIALS FOR SYSTEMIC USE</level>
      <level code="J">ANTIINFECTIVES FOR SYSTEMIC USE</level>
    </atc-code>
  </atc-codes>
  <ahfs-codes>
    <ahfs-code>08:12.02</ahfs-code>
  </ahfs-codes>
  <pdb-entries>
    <pdb-entry>4p20</pdb-entry>
    <pdb-entry>6cgd</pdb-entry>
  </pdb-entries>
  <fda-label>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/fda_labels/DB00479.pdf?1540245531</fda-label>
  <msds>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/msds/DB00479.pdf?1265922742</msds>
  <patents>
    <patent>
      <number>8802137</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2014-08-12</approved>
      <expires>2024-04-08</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
    <patent>
      <number>7718189</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2010-05-18</approved>
      <expires>2025-06-06</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
    <patent>
      <number>8679532</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2014-03-25</approved>
      <expires>2026-12-05</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
    <patent>
      <number>9566234</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2017-02-14</approved>
      <expires>2034-01-18</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
    <patent>
      <number>9895385</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2018-02-20</approved>
      <expires>2035-05-15</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
    <patent>
      <number>8632804</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2014-01-21</approved>
      <expires>2026-12-05</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
    <patent>
      <number>9827317</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2017-11-28</approved>
      <expires>2024-04-08</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
    <patent>
      <number>8642075</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2014-02-04</approved>
      <expires>2026-12-05</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
    <patent>
      <number>8226975</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2012-07-24</approved>
      <expires>2028-08-15</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
    <patent>
      <number>10251900</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2019-04-09</approved>
      <expires>2035-05-15</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
  </patents>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00958</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carboplatin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of ototoxicity and nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Carboplatin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00529</drugbank-id>
      <name>Foscarnet</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Foscarnet.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00742</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mannitol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Mannitol is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00300</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenofovir disoproxil</name>
      <description>Amikacin may increase the nephrotoxic activities of Tenofovir disoproxil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09299</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenofovir alafenamide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may increase the nephrotoxic activities of Tenofovir alafenamide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14126</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenofovir</name>
      <description>Amikacin may increase the nephrotoxic activities of Tenofovir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00282</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pamidronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Pamidronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00399</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zoledronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Zoledronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00630</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alendronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Alendronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00710</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibandronate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Ibandronate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00720</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clodronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Clodronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00884</drugbank-id>
      <name>Risedronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Risedronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01077</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etidronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Etidronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01133</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiludronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Tiludronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06255</drugbank-id>
      <name>Incadronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00091</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclosporine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cyclosporine is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00229</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefotiam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefotiam is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00267</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefmenoxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefmenoxime is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00274</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefmetazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefmetazole is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00384</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triamterene</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Triamterene is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00430</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefpiramide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefpiramide is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00447</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loracarbef</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Loracarbef is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00452</drugbank-id>
      <name>Framycetin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Framycetin is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00456</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefalotin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefalotin is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00493</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefotaxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefotaxime.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00626</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bacitracin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Bacitracin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00681</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amphotericin B</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Amphotericin B.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00684</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tobramycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Tobramycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00689</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cephaloglycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cephaloglycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00718</drugbank-id>
      <name>Adefovir dipivoxil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Adefovir dipivoxil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00738</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentamidine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Pentamidine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00798</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gentamicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Gentamicin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00864</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tacrolimus</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Tacrolimus.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00923</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceforanide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Ceforanide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00955</drugbank-id>
      <name>Netilmicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Netilmicin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00994</drugbank-id>
      <name>Neomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Neomycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00999</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrochlorothiazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Hydrochlorothiazide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01066</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefditoren</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefditoren.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01072</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atazanavir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Atazanavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01082</drugbank-id>
      <name>Streptomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Streptomycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01111</drugbank-id>
      <name>Colistimethate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Colistimethate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01112</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefuroxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefuroxime.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01139</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefapirin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefapirin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01150</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefprozil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefprozil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01172</drugbank-id>
      <name>Kanamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Kanamycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01326</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefamandole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefamandole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01327</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefazolin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefazolin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01328</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefonicid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefonicid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01329</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefoperazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefoperazone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01331</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefoxitin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefoxitin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01332</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftizoxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Ceftizoxime.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01413</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefepime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefepime.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01414</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefacetrile</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefacetrile.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01416</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefpodoxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefpodoxime.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01421</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paromomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Paromomycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01601</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lopinavir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Lopinavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02247</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrolyzed Cephalothin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Hydrolyzed Cephalothin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03450</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cephalothin Group</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cephalothin Group.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ribostamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Ribostamycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04263</drugbank-id>
      <name>Geneticin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Geneticin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04570</drugbank-id>
      <name>Latamoxef</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Latamoxef.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04626</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apramycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Apramycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04729</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gentamicin C1a</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Gentamicin C1a.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04808</drugbank-id>
      <name>Neamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Neamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04918</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftobiprole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Ceftobiprole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06590</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftaroline fosamil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Ceftaroline fosamil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06696</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arbekacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Arbekacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08437</drugbank-id>
      <name>Puromycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Puromycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09008</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefaloridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefaloridine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09062</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefminox</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefminox.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11512</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dihydrostreptomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Dihydrostreptomycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11520</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hygromycin B</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Hygromycin B.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11935</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flomoxef</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Flomoxef.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12604</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sisomicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Sisomicin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13266</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefatrizine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefatrizine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13270</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dibekacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Dibekacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13274</drugbank-id>
      <name>Micronomicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Micronomicin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13461</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefcapene</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefcapene.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13470</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefodizime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefodizime.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13499</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefsulodin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefsulodin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13504</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefetamet</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefetamet.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13540</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isepamicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Isepamicin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13638</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefbuperazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefbuperazone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13667</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefozopran</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefozopran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13673</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bekanamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Bekanamycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13682</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefpirome</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefpirome.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13778</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefazedone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cefazedone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13821</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftezole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Ceftezole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13868</drugbank-id>
      <name>Adefovir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Adefovir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14713</drugbank-id>
      <name>Inotersen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Inotersen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01438</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenazopyridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Phenazopyridine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15066</drugbank-id>
      <name>Givosiran</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00159</drugbank-id>
      <name>Icosapent</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Icosapent is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00244</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mesalazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Mesalazine is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00328</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indomethacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Indomethacin is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00461</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nabumetone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Nabumetone is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00465</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketorolac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ketorolac is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00469</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenoxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tenoxicam is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00482</drugbank-id>
      <name>Celecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Celecoxib is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00500</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolmetin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tolmetin is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00533</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rofecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Rofecoxib is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00554</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piroxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Piroxicam is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00573</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Fenoprofen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00580</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valdecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Valdecoxib is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00586</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diclofenac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Diclofenac is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00605</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulindac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Sulindac is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00712</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flurbiprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Flurbiprofen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00749</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etodolac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Etodolac is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00784</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mefenamic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Mefenamic acid is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00788</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naproxen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Naproxen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00795</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfasalazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Sulfasalazine is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00812</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenylbutazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Phenylbutazone is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00814</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meloxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Meloxicam is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00821</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Carprofen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00861</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diflunisal</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Diflunisal is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00936</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salicylic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Salicylic acid is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00939</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meclofenamic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Meclofenamic acid is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00945</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetylsalicylic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Acetylsalicylic acid is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00991</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxaprozin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Oxaprozin is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01009</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ketoprofen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01014</drugbank-id>
      <name>Balsalazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Balsalazide is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01050</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibuprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ibuprofen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01250</drugbank-id>
      <name>Olsalazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Olsalazine is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01283</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lumiracoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Lumiracoxib is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01397</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium salicylate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Magnesium salicylate is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01399</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salsalate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Salsalate is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01401</drugbank-id>
      <name>Choline magnesium trisalicylate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Choline magnesium trisalicylate is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01419</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antrafenine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Antrafenine is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01424</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aminophenazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Aminophenazone is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01435</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antipyrine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Antipyrine is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01600</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiaprofenic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tiaprofenic acid is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01628</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etoricoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Etoricoxib is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02224</drugbank-id>
      <name>Taxifolin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Taxifolin is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03585</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxyphenbutazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Oxyphenbutazone is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04552</drugbank-id>
      <name>Niflumic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Niflumic acid is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04725</drugbank-id>
      <name>Licofelone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Licofelone is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04743</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nimesulide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Nimesulide is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04812</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benoxaprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Benoxaprofen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metamizole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Metamizole is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04828</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zomepirac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Zomepirac is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05095</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cimicoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cimicoxib is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06725</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lornoxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Lornoxicam is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06736</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aceclofenac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Aceclofenac is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06737</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zaltoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Zaltoprofen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07402</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azapropazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Azapropazone is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07477</drugbank-id>
      <name>Felbinac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Felbinac is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08439</drugbank-id>
      <name>Parecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Parecoxib is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08797</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salicylamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Salicylamide is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08940</drugbank-id>
      <name>Kebuzone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Kebuzone is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08942</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isoxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Isoxicam is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08951</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Indoprofen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08955</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibuproxam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ibuproxam is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08976</drugbank-id>
      <name>Floctafenine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Floctafenine is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08981</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenbufen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Fenbufen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08984</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etofenamate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Etofenamate is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08991</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epirizole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Epirizole is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09084</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benzydamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Benzydamine is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09212</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loxoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Loxoprofen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexibuprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Dexibuprofen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09214</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexketoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Dexketoprofen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09215</drugbank-id>
      <name>Droxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Droxicam is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09216</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolfenamic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tolfenamic acid is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09217</drugbank-id>
      <name>Firocoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Firocoxib is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clonixin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Clonixin is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09285</drugbank-id>
      <name>Morniflumate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Morniflumate is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09288</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propacetamol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Propacetamol is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09295</drugbank-id>
      <name>Talniflumate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Talniflumate is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11455</drugbank-id>
      <name>Robenacoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Robenacoxib is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11466</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tepoxalin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tepoxalin is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11518</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flunixin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Flunixin is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12399</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polmacoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Polmacoxib is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12445</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitroaspirin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Nitroaspirin is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12480</drugbank-id>
      <name>Betulinic Acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Betulinic Acid is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12545</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indobufen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Indobufen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12610</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ebselen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ebselen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13001</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tinoridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tinoridine is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13167</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alclofenac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Alclofenac is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13217</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fentiazac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Fentiazac is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13232</drugbank-id>
      <name>Suxibuzone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Suxibuzone is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13286</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bumadizone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Bumadizone is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13314</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alminoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Alminoprofen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flunoxaprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Flunoxaprofen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13364</drugbank-id>
      <name>Feprazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Feprazone is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13371</drugbank-id>
      <name>Difenpiramide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Difenpiramide is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13407</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nifenazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Nifenazone is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13432</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lonazolac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Lonazolac is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13481</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenidap</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tenidap is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13501</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bendazac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Bendazac is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13514</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pranoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Pranoprofen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13524</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propyphenazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Propyphenazone is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13527</drugbank-id>
      <name>Proglumetacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Proglumetacin is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13538</drugbank-id>
      <name>Guacetisal</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Guacetisal is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13544</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethenzamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ethenzamide is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13612</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbaspirin calcium</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Carbaspirin calcium is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13629</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mofebutazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Mofebutazone is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13649</drugbank-id>
      <name>Proquazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Proquazone is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13657</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benorilate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Benorilate is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13722</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pirprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Pirprofen is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acemetacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Acemetacin is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13860</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imidazole salicylate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Imidazole salicylate is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14059</drugbank-id>
      <name>SC-236</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when SC-236 is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14060</drugbank-id>
      <name>NS-398</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when NS-398 is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14938</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flurbiprofen axetil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Flurbiprofen axetil is combined with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00511</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetyldigitoxin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Acetyldigitoxin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01078</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deslanoside</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Deslanoside.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01092</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ouabain</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Ouabain.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01396</drugbank-id>
      <name>Digitoxin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Digitoxin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12843</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oleandrin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Oleandrin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13240</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cymarin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Cymarin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13307</drugbank-id>
      <name>Proscillaridin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Proscillaridin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13401</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metildigoxin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Metildigoxin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13467</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lanatoside C</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Lanatoside C.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13537</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gitoformate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Gitoformate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13691</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetyldigoxin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Acetyldigoxin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13756</drugbank-id>
      <name>Peruvoside</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Peruvoside.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00214</drugbank-id>
      <name>Torasemide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be increased when it is combined with Torasemide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00887</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bumetanide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be increased when it is combined with Bumetanide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00903</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etacrynic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be increased when it is combined with Etacrynic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02925</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piretanide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be increased when it is combined with Piretanide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08961</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azosemide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be increased when it is combined with Azosemide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00301</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flucloxacillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Flucloxacillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00319</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piperacillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Piperacillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00415</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ampicillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Ampicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00417</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenoxymethylpenicillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Phenoxymethylpenicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00485</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dicloxacillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Dicloxacillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00578</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbenicillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Carbenicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00607</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nafcillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Nafcillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00713</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxacillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Oxacillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00739</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hetacillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Hetacillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00895</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benzylpenicilloyl polylysine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Benzylpenicilloyl polylysine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00948</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mezlocillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Mezlocillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01000</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclacillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Cyclacillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01053</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benzylpenicillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Benzylpenicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01060</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amoxicillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Amoxicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01061</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azlocillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Azlocillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01147</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cloxacillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Cloxacillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01163</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amdinocillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Amdinocillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01602</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bacampicillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Bacampicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01603</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meticillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Meticillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01604</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pivampicillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Pivampicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01605</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pivmecillinam</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Pivmecillinam.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01607</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ticarcillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Ticarcillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08795</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azidocillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Azidocillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09319</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carindacillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Carindacillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09320</drugbank-id>
      <name>Procaine benzylpenicillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Procaine benzylpenicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12127</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sultamicillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Sultamicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12343</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temocillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Temocillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13300</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epicillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Epicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13337</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pheneticillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Pheneticillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13506</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carfecillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Carfecillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13660</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propicillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Propicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13686</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clometocillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Clometocillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13693</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulbenicillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Sulbenicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13739</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penamecillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Penamecillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13814</drugbank-id>
      <name>Talampicillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Talampicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13816</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aspoxicillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Aspoxicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13836</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metampicillin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amikacin can be decreased when it is combined with Metampicillin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12768</drugbank-id>
      <name>BCG vaccine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of BCG vaccine can be decreased when used in combination with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14022</drugbank-id>
      <name>Typhoid vaccine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Typhoid vaccine can be decreased when used in combination with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00184</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nicotine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Nicotine can be decreased when used in combination with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00411</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbamoylcholine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Carbamoylcholine can be decreased when used in combination with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01019</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bethanechol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Bethanechol can be decreased when used in combination with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01085</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pilocarpine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Pilocarpine can be decreased when used in combination with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03128</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetylcholine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Acetylcholine can be decreased when used in combination with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04365</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arecoline</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Arecoline can be decreased when used in combination with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05137</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lobeline</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Lobeline can be decreased when used in combination with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05152</drugbank-id>
      <name>NGX267</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of NGX267 can be decreased when used in combination with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05708</drugbank-id>
      <name>GTS-21</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of GTS-21 can be decreased when used in combination with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06709</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methacholine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Methacholine can be decreased when used in combination with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07720</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epibatidine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Epibatidine can be decreased when used in combination with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15357</drugbank-id>
      <name>Xanomeline</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Xanomeline can be decreased when used in combination with Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00407</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ardeparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Amikacin can be decreased when used in combination with Ardeparin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01109</drugbank-id>
      <name>Heparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Amikacin can be decreased when used in combination with Heparin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01225</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enoxaparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Amikacin can be decreased when used in combination with Enoxaparin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06271</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulodexide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Amikacin can be decreased when used in combination with Sulodexide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06294</drugbank-id>
      <name>Semuloparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Amikacin can be decreased when used in combination with Semuloparin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06754</drugbank-id>
      <name>Danaparoid</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Amikacin can be decreased when used in combination with Danaparoid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06779</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dalteparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Amikacin can be decreased when used in combination with Dalteparin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06822</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tinzaparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Amikacin can be decreased when used in combination with Tinzaparin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08813</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nadroparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Amikacin can be decreased when used in combination with Nadroparin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09258</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bemiparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Amikacin can be decreased when used in combination with Bemiparin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09259</drugbank-id>
      <name>Reviparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Amikacin can be decreased when used in combination with Reviparin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09260</drugbank-id>
      <name>Parnaparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Amikacin can be decreased when used in combination with Parnaparin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09261</drugbank-id>
      <name>Certoparin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Amikacin can be decreased when used in combination with Certoparin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00007</drugbank-id>
      <name>Leuprolide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Leuprolide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00014</drugbank-id>
      <name>Goserelin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Goserelin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00017</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salmon Calcitonin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Salmon Calcitonin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00035</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desmopressin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Desmopressin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00041</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aldesleukin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Aldesleukin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00080</drugbank-id>
      <name>Daptomycin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Daptomycin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00081</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tositumomab</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tositumomab which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00115</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyanocobalamin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Cyanocobalamin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00158</drugbank-id>
      <name>Folic acid</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Folic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00165</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pyridoxine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pyridoxine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00176</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluvoxamine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Fluvoxamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00182</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amphetamine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Amphetamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00185</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cevimeline</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Cevimeline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00186</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lorazepam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Lorazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00190</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbidopa</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Carbidopa which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00193</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tramadol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tramadol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00196</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluconazole</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Fluconazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00198</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oseltamivir</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Oseltamivir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00200</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydroxocobalamin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Hydroxocobalamin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00206</drugbank-id>
      <name>Reserpine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Reserpine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ticlopidine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ticlopidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pantoprazole</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pantoprazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00225</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gadodiamide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Gadodiamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00230</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pregabalin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pregabalin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00231</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temazepam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Temazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00235</drugbank-id>
      <name>Milrinone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Milrinone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00237</drugbank-id>
      <name>Butabarbital</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Butabarbital which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00243</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ranolazine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ranolazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00245</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benzatropine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Benzatropine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00254</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxycycline</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Doxycycline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00262</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carmustine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Carmustine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metoprolol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Metoprolol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00270</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isradipine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Isradipine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00271</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diatrizoate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Diatrizoate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00273</drugbank-id>
      <name>Topiramate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Topiramate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00279</drugbank-id>
      <name>Liothyronine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Liothyronine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00280</drugbank-id>
      <name>Disopyramide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Disopyramide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00284</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acarbose</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Acarbose which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00285</drugbank-id>
      <name>Venlafaxine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Venlafaxine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00286</drugbank-id>
      <name>Conjugated estrogens</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Conjugated estrogens which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00289</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atomoxetine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Atomoxetine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00290</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bleomycin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Bleomycin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00292</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etomidate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Etomidate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00294</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etonogestrel</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Etonogestrel which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00296</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ropivacaine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ropivacaine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00303</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ertapenem</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ertapenem which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00308</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibutilide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ibutilide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00312</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentobarbital</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pentobarbital which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00316</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetaminophen</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Acetaminophen which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00322</drugbank-id>
      <name>Floxuridine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Floxuridine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00323</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolcapone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tolcapone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00325</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitroprusside</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Nitroprusside which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00327</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydromorphone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Hydromorphone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00330</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethambutol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ethambutol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00331</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metformin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Metformin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00333</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methadone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Methadone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00339</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pyrazinamide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pyrazinamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00341</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cetirizine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Cetirizine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00349</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clobazam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Clobazam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00351</drugbank-id>
      <name>Megestrol acetate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Megestrol acetate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00355</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aztreonam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Aztreonam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00356</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorzoxazone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Chlorzoxazone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00359</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfadiazine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Sulfadiazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00363</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clozapine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Clozapine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00364</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sucralfate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Sucralfate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00369</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cidofovir</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Cidofovir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00372</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiethylperazine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Thiethylperazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00373</drugbank-id>
      <name>Timolol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Timolol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00377</drugbank-id>
      <name>Palonosetron</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Palonosetron which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00380</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexrazoxane</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Dexrazoxane which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00398</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sorafenib</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Sorafenib which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00401</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nisoldipine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Nisoldipine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00402</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eszopiclone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Eszopiclone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00404</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alprazolam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Alprazolam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00412</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rosiglitazone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Rosiglitazone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00413</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pramipexole</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pramipexole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00418</drugbank-id>
      <name>Secobarbital</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Secobarbital which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00422</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylphenidate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Methylphenidate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00432</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trifluridine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Trifluridine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00435</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitric Oxide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Nitric Oxide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00437</drugbank-id>
      <name>Allopurinol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Allopurinol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00438</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftazidime</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ceftazidime which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00440</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimethoprim</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Trimethoprim which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00441</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemcitabine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Gemcitabine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00476</drugbank-id>
      <name>Duloxetine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Duloxetine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00477</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorpromazine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Chlorpromazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00480</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lenalidomide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Lenalidomide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00490</drugbank-id>
      <name>Buspirone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Buspirone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00492</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosinopril</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Fosinopril which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00499</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flutamide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Flutamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00501</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cimetidine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Cimetidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00502</drugbank-id>
      <name>Haloperidol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Haloperidol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00524</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metolazone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Metolazone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00535</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefdinir</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Cefdinir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00537</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ciprofloxacin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ciprofloxacin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00548</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azelaic acid</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Azelaic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00552</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentostatin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pentostatin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00553</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methoxsalen</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Methoxsalen which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00555</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lamotrigine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Lamotrigine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00558</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zanamivir</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Zanamivir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00563</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methotrexate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Methotrexate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00567</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cephalexin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Cephalexin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00569</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fondaparinux</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Fondaparinux which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00571</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propranolol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Propranolol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00577</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valaciclovir</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Valaciclovir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00583</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levocarnitine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Levocarnitine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00591</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluocinolone acetonide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Fluocinolone acetonide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00597</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gadoteridol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Gadoteridol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00598</drugbank-id>
      <name>Labetalol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Labetalol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00603</drugbank-id>
      <name>Medroxyprogesterone acetate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Medroxyprogesterone acetate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00608</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chloroquine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Chloroquine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00612</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bisoprolol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Bisoprolol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00624</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Testosterone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00628</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clorazepic acid</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Clorazepic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00631</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clofarabine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Clofarabine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00633</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexmedetomidine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Dexmedetomidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00635</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Prednisone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00651</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dyphylline</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Dyphylline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00657</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mecamylamine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Mecamylamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00660</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metaxalone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Metaxalone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00661</drugbank-id>
      <name>Verapamil</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Verapamil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00665</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nilutamide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Nilutamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00669</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sumatriptan</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Sumatriptan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00672</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorpropamide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Chlorpropamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00674</drugbank-id>
      <name>Galantamine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Galantamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00683</drugbank-id>
      <name>Midazolam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Midazolam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00688</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mycophenolate mofetil</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Mycophenolate mofetil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00690</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flurazepam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Flurazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00692</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phentolamine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Phentolamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00698</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitrofurantoin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Nitrofurantoin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00706</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tamsulosin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tamsulosin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00709</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lamivudine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Lamivudine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00716</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nedocromil</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Nedocromil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00722</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lisinopril</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Lisinopril which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00730</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiabendazole</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Thiabendazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00731</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nateglinide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Nateglinide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00733</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pralidoxime</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pralidoxime which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00743</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gadobenic acid</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Gadobenic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00759</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetracycline</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tetracycline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00760</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meropenem</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Meropenem which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00761</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium chloride</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Potassium chloride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00763</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methimazole</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Methimazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00775</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tirofiban</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tirofiban which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00780</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenelzine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Phenelzine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00782</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propantheline</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Propantheline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Estradiol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00787</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acyclovir</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Acyclovir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00789</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gadopentetic acid</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Gadopentetic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00790</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perindopril</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Perindopril which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00800</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenoldopam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Fenoldopam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00804</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dicyclomine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Dicyclomine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00806</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentoxifylline</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pentoxifylline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00808</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indapamide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Indapamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00811</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ribavirin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ribavirin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00820</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tadalafil</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tadalafil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00828</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosfomycin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Fosfomycin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00829</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diazepam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Diazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00833</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefaclor</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Cefaclor which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00839</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolazamide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tolazamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00841</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dobutamine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Dobutamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00842</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxazepam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Oxazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00851</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dacarbazine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Dacarbazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00853</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temozolomide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Temozolomide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00863</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ranitidine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ranitidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00871</drugbank-id>
      <name>Terbutaline</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Terbutaline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00894</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testolactone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Testolactone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00897</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triazolam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Triazolam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00900</drugbank-id>
      <name>Didanosine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Didanosine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00909</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zonisamide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Zonisamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00911</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tinidazole</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tinidazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00915</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amantadine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Amantadine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00918</drugbank-id>
      <name>Almotriptan</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Almotriptan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00928</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azacitidine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Azacitidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00934</drugbank-id>
      <name>Maprotiline</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Maprotiline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00951</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isoniazid</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Isoniazid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00953</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rizatriptan</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Rizatriptan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00960</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pindolol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pindolol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00961</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mepivacaine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Mepivacaine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00962</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zaleplon</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Zaleplon which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00968</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methyldopa</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Methyldopa which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00980</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ramelteon</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ramelteon which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00988</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dopamine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Dopamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00993</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azathioprine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Azathioprine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00995</drugbank-id>
      <name>Auranofin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Auranofin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01001</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salbutamol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Salbutamol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01002</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levobupivacaine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Levobupivacaine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01004</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ganciclovir</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ganciclovir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01010</drugbank-id>
      <name>Edrophonium</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Edrophonium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01011</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metyrapone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Metyrapone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01015</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfamethoxazole</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Sulfamethoxazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01018</drugbank-id>
      <name>Guanfacine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Guanfacine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01020</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isosorbide mononitrate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Isosorbide mononitrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01022</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phylloquinone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Phylloquinone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01024</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mycophenolic acid</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Mycophenolic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01030</drugbank-id>
      <name>Topotecan</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Topotecan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01032</drugbank-id>
      <name>Probenecid</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Probenecid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01036</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolterodine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tolterodine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01039</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenofibrate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Fenofibrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01043</drugbank-id>
      <name>Memantine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Memantine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01046</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lubiprostone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Lubiprostone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01048</drugbank-id>
      <name>Abacavir</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Abacavir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01067</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glipizide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Glipizide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01068</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clonazepam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Clonazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01069</drugbank-id>
      <name>Promethazine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Promethazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01093</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dimethyl sulfoxide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Dimethyl sulfoxide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01099</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flucytosine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Flucytosine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01101</drugbank-id>
      <name>Capecitabine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Capecitabine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01105</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sibutramine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Sibutramine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01115</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nifedipine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Nifedipine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01124</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolbutamide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tolbutamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01129</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rabeprazole</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Rabeprazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01135</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxacurium</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Doxacurium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01137</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levofloxacin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Levofloxacin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01140</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefadroxil</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Cefadroxil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01148</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flavoxate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Flavoxate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01149</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nefazodone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Nefazodone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01156</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bupropion</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Bupropion which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01157</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimetrexate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Trimetrexate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01166</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cilostazol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Cilostazol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01169</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arsenic trioxide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Arsenic trioxide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01170</drugbank-id>
      <name>Guanethidine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Guanethidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01181</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ifosfamide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ifosfamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01183</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naloxone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Naloxone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01203</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nadolol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Nadolol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01205</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flumazenil</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Flumazenil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01212</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftriaxone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ceftriaxone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fomepizole</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Fomepizole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01215</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estazolam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Estazolam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01221</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketamine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ketamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01222</drugbank-id>
      <name>Budesonide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Budesonide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01224</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quetiapine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Quetiapine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01233</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metoclopramide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Metoclopramide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01240</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epoprostenol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Epoprostenol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01241</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemfibrozil</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Gemfibrozil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01249</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iodixanol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Iodixanol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01261</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sitagliptin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Sitagliptin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01267</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paliperidone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Paliperidone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01273</drugbank-id>
      <name>Varenicline</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Varenicline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01274</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arformoterol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Arformoterol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01275</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydralazine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Hydralazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01330</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefotetan</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Cefotetan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01333</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefradine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Cefradine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01359</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penbutolol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Penbutolol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01367</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rasagiline</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Rasagiline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01394</drugbank-id>
      <name>Colchicine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Colchicine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01409</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiotropium</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tiotropium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01415</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftibuten</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ceftibuten which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01420</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone propionate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Testosterone propionate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01427</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amrinone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Amrinone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01428</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxybenzone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Oxybenzone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01431</drugbank-id>
      <name>Allylestrenol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Allylestrenol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01550</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenproporex</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Fenproporex which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01558</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bromazepam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Bromazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01563</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chloral hydrate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Chloral hydrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01577</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metamfetamine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Metamfetamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01587</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketazolam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ketazolam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01610</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valganciclovir</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Valganciclovir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01638</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sorbitol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Sorbitol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01656</drugbank-id>
      <name>Roflumilast</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Roflumilast which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01685</drugbank-id>
      <name>Topiroxostat</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Topiroxostat which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04574</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estrone sulfate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Estrone sulfate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04871</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lorcaserin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Lorcaserin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04895</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pegaptanib</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pegaptanib which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04896</drugbank-id>
      <name>Milnacipran</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Milnacipran which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04920</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clevidipine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Clevidipine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04948</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lofexidine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Lofexidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04953</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ezogabine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ezogabine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05018</drugbank-id>
      <name>Migalastat</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Migalastat which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05541</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brivaracetam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Brivaracetam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05676</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apremilast</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Apremilast which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06154</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentaerythritol tetranitrate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pentaerythritol tetranitrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06186</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ipilimumab</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ipilimumab which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06196</drugbank-id>
      <name>Icatibant</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Icatibant which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06203</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alogliptin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Alogliptin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06209</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prasugrel</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Prasugrel which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06211</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doripenem</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Doripenem which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06228</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rivaroxaban</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Rivaroxaban which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06230</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nalmefene</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Nalmefene which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06262</drugbank-id>
      <name>Droxidopa</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Droxidopa which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06282</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levocetirizine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Levocetirizine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06335</drugbank-id>
      <name>Saxagliptin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Saxagliptin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06402</drugbank-id>
      <name>Telavancin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Telavancin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06480</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prucalopride</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Prucalopride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06623</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flupirtine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Flupirtine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06637</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dalfampridine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Dalfampridine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06695</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dabigatran etexilate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Dabigatran etexilate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06700</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desvenlafaxine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Desvenlafaxine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06702</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fesoterodine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Fesoterodine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06705</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gadofosveset trisodium</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Gadofosveset trisodium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06710</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methyltestosterone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Methyltestosterone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06767</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ammonium chloride</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ammonium chloride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06782</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dimercaprol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Dimercaprol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06796</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mangafodipir</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Mangafodipir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06800</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylnaltrexone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Methylnaltrexone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06809</drugbank-id>
      <name>Plerixafor</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Plerixafor which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06813</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pralatrexate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pralatrexate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06823</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiopronin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tiopronin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06824</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triethylenetetramine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Triethylenetetramine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08824</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ioflupane I-123</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ioflupane I-123 which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08826</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deferiprone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Deferiprone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08840</drugbank-id>
      <name>N-methylnicotinamide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of N-methylnicotinamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08872</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gabapentin enacarbil</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Gabapentin enacarbil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08877</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ruxolitinib</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ruxolitinib which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08893</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mirabegron</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Mirabegron which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08894</drugbank-id>
      <name>Peginesatide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Peginesatide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08897</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aclidinium</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Aclidinium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08899</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enzalutamide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Enzalutamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08900</drugbank-id>
      <name>Teduglutide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Teduglutide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08904</drugbank-id>
      <name>Certolizumab pegol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Certolizumab pegol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08905</drugbank-id>
      <name>Formestane</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Formestane which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08907</drugbank-id>
      <name>Canagliflozin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Canagliflozin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08909</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glycerol phenylbutyrate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Glycerol phenylbutyrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08910</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pomalidomide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pomalidomide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08911</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trametinib</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Trametinib which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08918</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levomilnacipran</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Levomilnacipran which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08932</drugbank-id>
      <name>Macitentan</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Macitentan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08934</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sofosbuvir</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Sofosbuvir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08964</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemeprost</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Gemeprost which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09027</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ledipasvir</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ledipasvir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09038</drugbank-id>
      <name>Empagliflozin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Empagliflozin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09050</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftolozane</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ceftolozane which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09066</drugbank-id>
      <name>Corifollitropin alfa</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Corifollitropin alfa which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09068</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vortioxetine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Vortioxetine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09071</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tasimelteon</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tasimelteon which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09075</drugbank-id>
      <name>Edoxaban</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Edoxaban which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09081</drugbank-id>
      <name>Idebenone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Idebenone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09082</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vilanterol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Vilanterol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09089</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimebutine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Trimebutine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09091</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tixocortol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tixocortol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09103</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ancestim</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ancestim which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09104</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium hydroxide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Magnesium hydroxide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09106</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydroxyethyl Starch</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Hydroxyethyl Starch which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09111</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentastarch</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pentastarch which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09118</drugbank-id>
      <name>Stiripentol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Stiripentol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09121</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aurothioglucose</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Aurothioglucose which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09123</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dienogest</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Dienogest which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09129</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromic chloride</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Chromic chloride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09132</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gadoteric acid</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Gadoteric acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09133</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iothalamic acid</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Iothalamic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09134</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ioversol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ioversol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09135</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ioxilan</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ioxilan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09136</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isosulfan blue</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Isosulfan blue which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09137</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m mebrofenin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Technetium Tc-99m mebrofenin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09139</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m oxidronate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Technetium Tc-99m oxidronate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09148</drugbank-id>
      <name>Florbetaben (18F)</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Florbetaben (18F) which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09149</drugbank-id>
      <name>Florbetapir (18F)</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Florbetapir (18F) which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09156</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iopromide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Iopromide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09163</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m exametazime</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Technetium Tc-99m exametazime which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09164</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m disofenin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Technetium Tc-99m disofenin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09165</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m pyrophosphate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Technetium Tc-99m pyrophosphate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09185</drugbank-id>
      <name>Viloxazine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Viloxazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09194</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etoperidone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Etoperidone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09195</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lorpiprazole</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Lorpiprazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09204</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arotinolol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Arotinolol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09205</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moxisylyte</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Moxisylyte which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09209</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pholcodine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pholcodine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09210</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piracetam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Piracetam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09219</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bisoxatin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Bisoxatin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09220</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nicorandil</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Nicorandil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09223</drugbank-id>
      <name>Blonanserin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Blonanserin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09224</drugbank-id>
      <name>Melperone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Melperone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09241</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylene blue</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Methylene blue which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09244</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pirlindole</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pirlindole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09245</drugbank-id>
      <name>Toloxatone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Toloxatone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09255</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dextran</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Dextran which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09256</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tegafur</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tegafur which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09257</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gimeracil</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Gimeracil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09262</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imidafenacin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Imidafenacin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Idarucizumab</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Idarucizumab which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09265</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lixisenatide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Lixisenatide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09268</drugbank-id>
      <name>Picosulfuric acid</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Picosulfuric acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09276</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium aurothiomalate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Sodium aurothiomalate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09277</drugbank-id>
      <name>Choline C 11</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Choline C 11 which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09281</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium trisilicate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Magnesium trisilicate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09292</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sacubitril</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Sacubitril which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09301</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chondroitin sulfate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Chondroitin sulfate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens, A</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens, A which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09318</drugbank-id>
      <name>Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens, B</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens, B which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09324</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulbactam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Sulbactam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09325</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium fluoride</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Sodium fluoride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09329</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antihemophilic Factor (Recombinant), PEGylated</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Antihemophilic Factor (Recombinant), PEGylated which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09338</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mersalyl</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Mersalyl which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09344</drugbank-id>
      <name>Invert sugar</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Invert sugar which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09357</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexpanthenol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Dexpanthenol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09394</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phosphoric acid</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Phosphoric acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09395</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium acetate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Sodium acetate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09407</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium chloride</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Magnesium chloride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09418</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium perchlorate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Potassium perchlorate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09472</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium sulfate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Sodium sulfate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09477</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enalaprilat</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Enalaprilat which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09481</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium carbonate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Magnesium carbonate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09488</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acrivastine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Acrivastine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09496</drugbank-id>
      <name>Octinoxate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Octinoxate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09502</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fludeoxyglucose (18F)</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Fludeoxyglucose (18F) which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09546</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iobenguane sulfate I-123</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Iobenguane sulfate I-123 which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09570</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ixazomib</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ixazomib which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11077</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polyethylene glycol 400</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Polyethylene glycol 400 which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11090</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium nitrate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Potassium nitrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11098</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium bicarbonate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Potassium bicarbonate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11102</drugbank-id>
      <name>N-acetyltyrosine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of N-acetyltyrosine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11114</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eucalyptus oil</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Eucalyptus oil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11127</drugbank-id>
      <name>Selenious acid</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Selenious acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11130</drugbank-id>
      <name>Opium</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Opium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11135</drugbank-id>
      <name>Selenium</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Selenium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11136</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromium</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Chromium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11145</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxyquinoline</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Oxyquinoline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11156</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pyrantel</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pyrantel which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11164</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bicisate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Bicisate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11251</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tocopherol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tocopherol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11278</drugbank-id>
      <name>DL-Methylephedrine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of DL-Methylephedrine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11328</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetradecyl hydrogen sulfate (ester)</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tetradecyl hydrogen sulfate (ester) which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11338</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clove oil</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Clove oil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11358</drugbank-id>
      <name>Evening primrose oil</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Evening primrose oil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11364</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pidotimod</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pidotimod which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11367</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefroxadine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Cefroxadine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11560</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lesinurad</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Lesinurad which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11577</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indigotindisulfonic acid</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Indigotindisulfonic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11587</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etafedrine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Etafedrine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11598</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antithrombin III human</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Antithrombin III human which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11642</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pitolisant</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pitolisant which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11691</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naldemedine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Naldemedine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11699</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tropisetron</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tropisetron which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Baricitinib</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Baricitinib which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11901</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apalutamide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Apalutamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11915</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valbenazine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Valbenazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11943</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delafloxacin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Delafloxacin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11989</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benznidazole</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Benznidazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12007</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isoflavone</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Isoflavone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12107</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vaborbactam</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Vaborbactam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12151</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brincidofovir</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Brincidofovir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12161</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deutetrabenazine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Deutetrabenazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12278</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propiverine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Propiverine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benserazide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Benserazide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13025</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiapride</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Tiapride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13139</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levosalbutamol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Levosalbutamol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13145</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nedaplatin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Nedaplatin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13156</drugbank-id>
      <name>Inosine pranobex</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Inosine pranobex which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13178</drugbank-id>
      <name>Inositol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Inositol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13185</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxabolone cipionate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Oxabolone cipionate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13191</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phosphocreatine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Phosphocreatine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13269</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dichlorobenzyl alcohol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Dichlorobenzyl alcohol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13293</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ipecac</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Ipecac which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Almasilate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Almasilate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13873</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenofibric acid</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Fenofibric acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13884</drugbank-id>
      <name>Albutrepenonacog alfa</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Albutrepenonacog alfa which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13909</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bismuth subgallate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Bismuth subgallate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13943</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone cypionate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Testosterone cypionate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13944</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone enanthate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Testosterone enanthate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13946</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone undecanoate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Testosterone undecanoate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13952</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol acetate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Estradiol acetate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13954</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol cypionate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Estradiol cypionate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13955</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol dienanthate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Estradiol dienanthate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13956</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol valerate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Estradiol valerate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13967</drugbank-id>
      <name>Patent Blue</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Patent Blue which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14006</drugbank-id>
      <name>Choline salicylate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Choline salicylate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14007</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentetic acid</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pentetic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14184</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cinnamaldehyde</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Cinnamaldehyde which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14186</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cinnamyl alcohol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Cinnamyl alcohol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14498</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium acetate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Potassium acetate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14499</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium sulfate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Potassium sulfate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14526</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromic citrate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Chromic citrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14527</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromic nitrate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Chromic nitrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14528</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromium gluconate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Chromium gluconate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14529</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromium nicotinate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Chromium nicotinate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14530</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromous sulfate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Chromous sulfate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14754</drugbank-id>
      <name>Solriamfetol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Solriamfetol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06815</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pyrithione</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pyrithione which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11121</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chloroxylenol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Chloroxylenol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11085</drugbank-id>
      <name>Resorcinol</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Resorcinol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15593</drugbank-id>
      <name>Golodirsen</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Golodirsen which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00314</drugbank-id>
      <name>Capreomycin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Capreomycin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00318</drugbank-id>
      <name>Codeine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Codeine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00321</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amitriptyline</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Amitriptyline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00390</drugbank-id>
      <name>Digoxin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Digoxin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00454</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meperidine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Meperidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00458</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imipramine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Imipramine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00512</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vancomycin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Vancomycin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00515</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cisplatin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Cisplatin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00564</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbamazepine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Carbamazepine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00642</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pemetrexed</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Pemetrexed which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00682</drugbank-id>
      <name>Warfarin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Warfarin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00813</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fentanyl</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Fentanyl which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00879</drugbank-id>
      <name>Emtricitabine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Emtricitabine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00908</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinidine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Quinidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00982</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isotretinoin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Isotretinoin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01035</drugbank-id>
      <name>Procainamide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Procainamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01142</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxepin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Doxepin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01151</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desipramine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Desipramine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01242</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clomipramine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Clomipramine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01356</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium cation</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Lithium cation which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08996</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dimetacrine</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Dimetacrine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Plazomicin</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Plazomicin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14506</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium hydroxide</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Lithium hydroxide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14507</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium citrate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Lithium citrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14508</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium succinate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Lithium succinate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14509</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium carbonate</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Lithium carbonate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00266</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dicoumarol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Dicoumarol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00498</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenindione</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Phenindione.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00946</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenprocoumon</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Phenprocoumon.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01418</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acenocoumarol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Acenocoumarol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03410</drugbank-id>
      <name>4-hydroxycoumarin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Amikacin is combined with 4-hydroxycoumarin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04665</drugbank-id>
      <name>Coumarin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Coumarin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08496</drugbank-id>
      <name>(R)-warfarin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Amikacin is combined with (R)-warfarin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08794</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethyl biscoumacetate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Ethyl biscoumacetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13136</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluindione</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Fluindione.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13275</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clorindione</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Clorindione.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13347</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diphenadione</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Diphenadione.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13451</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tioclomarol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Tioclomarol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14055</drugbank-id>
      <name>(S)-Warfarin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of bleeding can be increased when Amikacin is combined with (S)-Warfarin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00781</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polymyxin B</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Polymyxin B.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00181</drugbank-id>
      <name>Baclofen</name>
      <description>Amikacin may decrease the excretion rate of Baclofen which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01606</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tazobactam</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Amikacin can be decreased when used in combination with Tazobactam.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00695</drugbank-id>
      <name>Furosemide</name>
      <description>Furosemide may increase the ototoxic activities of Amikacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <calculated-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>-3.2</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logS</kind>
      <value>-1.1</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Water Solubility</kind>
      <value>4.97e+01 g/l</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>-8.6</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>(2S)-4-amino-N-[(1R,2S,3S,4R,5S)-5-amino-2-{[(2S,3R,4S,5S,6R)-4-amino-3,5-dihydroxy-6-(hydroxymethyl)oxan-2-yl]oxy}-4-{[(2R,3R,4S,5S,6R)-6-(aminomethyl)-3,4,5-trihydroxyoxan-2-yl]oxy}-3-hydroxycyclohexyl]-2-hydroxybutanamide</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Traditional IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>amikacin</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Weight</kind>
      <value>585.6025</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Monoisotopic Weight</kind>
      <value>585.285736487</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>SMILES</kind>
      <value>NCC[C@H](O)C(=O)N[C@@H]1C[C@H](N)[C@@H](O[C@H]2O[C@H](CN)[C@@H](O)[C@H](O)[C@H]2O)[C@H](O)[C@H]1O[C@H]1O[C@H](CO)[C@@H](O)[C@H](N)[C@H]1O</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Formula</kind>
      <value>C22H43N5O13</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChI</kind>
      <value>InChI=1S/C22H43N5O13/c23-2-1-8(29)20(36)27-7-3-6(25)18(39-22-16(34)15(33)13(31)9(4-24)37-22)17(35)19(7)40-21-14(32)11(26)12(30)10(5-28)38-21/h6-19,21-22,28-35H,1-5,23-26H2,(H,27,36)/t6-,7+,8-,9+,10+,11-,12+,13+,14+,15-,16+,17-,18+,19-,21+,22+/m0/s1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChIKey</kind>
      <value>LKCWBDHBTVXHDL-RMDFUYIESA-N</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polar Surface Area (PSA)</kind>
      <value>331.94</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Refractivity</kind>
      <value>129.84</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polarizability</kind>
      <value>58.06</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rotatable Bond Count</kind>
      <value>10</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Acceptor Count</kind>
      <value>17</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Donor Count</kind>
      <value>13</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest acidic)</kind>
      <value>12.1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest basic)</kind>
      <value>9.79</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Physiological Charge</kind>
      <value>4</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Number of Rings</kind>
      <value>3</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Bioavailability</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rule of Five</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Ghose Filter</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>MDDR-Like Rule</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
  </calculated-properties>
  <experimental-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>Water Solubility</kind>
      <value>50 mg/ml</value>
      <source>https://www.sigmaaldrich.com/content/dam/sigma-aldrich/docs/Sigma/Product_Information_Sheet/a1774pis.pdf</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Melting Point</kind>
      <value>214</value>
      <source>MSDS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Boiling Point</kind>
      <value>632.23</value>
      <source>https://www.chemicalbook.com/ChemicalProductProperty_US_CB8146049.aspx</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logS</kind>
      <value>-0.5</value>
      <source>ADME Research, USCD: https://pubchem.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/compound/amikacin#section=Solubility</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa</kind>
      <value>8.1</value>
      <source>http://www.druginfosys.com/drug.aspx?drugcode=45&amp;type=1</source>
    </property>
  </experimental-properties>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Drugs Product Database (DPD)</resource>
      <identifier>11178</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Drugs Product Database (DPD)</resource>
      <identifier>2168</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEBI</resource>
      <identifier>2637</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Compound</resource>
      <identifier>37768</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>46506386</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>KEGG Compound</resource>
      <identifier>C06820</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>KEGG Drug</resource>
      <identifier>D02543</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChemSpider</resource>
      <identifier>34635</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>BindingDB</resource>
      <identifier>50237603</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PharmGKB</resource>
      <identifier>PA164744372</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PDB</resource>
      <identifier>AKN</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Therapeutic Targets Database</resource>
      <identifier>DAP000400</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Wikipedia</resource>
      <identifier>Amikacin</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEMBL</resource>
      <identifier>CHEMBL177</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links>
    <external-link>
      <resource>RxList</resource>
      <url>http://www.rxlist.com/cgi/generic3/amikacin.htm</url>
    </external-link>
    <external-link>
      <resource>Drugs.com</resource>
      <url>http://www.drugs.com/cdi/amikacin.html</url>
    </external-link>
  </external-links>
  <pathways>
    <pathway>
      <smpdb-id>SMP0000253</smpdb-id>
      <name>Amikacin Action Pathway</name>
      <category>drug_action</category>
      <drugs>
        <drug>
          <drugbank-id>DB00117</drugbank-id>
          <name>Histidine</name>
        </drug>
        <drug>
          <drugbank-id>DB00131</drugbank-id>
          <name>Adenosine phosphate</name>
        </drug>
        <drug>
          <drugbank-id>DB00134</drugbank-id>
          <name>Methionine</name>
        </drug>
        <drug>
          <drugbank-id>DB00149</drugbank-id>
          <name>L-Leucine</name>
        </drug>
        <drug>
          <drugbank-id>DB00156</drugbank-id>
          <name>L-Threonine</name>
        </drug>
        <drug>
          <drugbank-id>DB00160</drugbank-id>
          <name>L-Alanine</name>
        </drug>
        <drug>
          <drugbank-id>DB00161</drugbank-id>
          <name>L-Valine</name>
        </drug>
        <drug>
          <drugbank-id>DB00167</drugbank-id>
          <name>Isoleucine</name>
        </drug>
        <drug>
          <drugbank-id>DB00171</drugbank-id>
          <name>ATP</name>
        </drug>
        <drug>
          <drugbank-id>DB00172</drugbank-id>
          <name>Proline</name>
        </drug>
        <drug>
          <drugbank-id>DB00174</drugbank-id>
          <name>Asparagine</name>
        </drug>
        <drug>
          <drugbank-id>DB00479</drugbank-id>
          <name>Amikacin</name>
        </drug>
        <drug>
          <drugbank-id>DB01972</drugbank-id>
          <name>Guanosine-5'-Monophosphate</name>
        </drug>
        <drug>
          <drugbank-id>DB02431</drugbank-id>
          <name>Cytidine-5'-Triphosphate</name>
        </drug>
        <drug>
          <drugbank-id>DB03685</drugbank-id>
          <name>Uridine monophosphate</name>
        </drug>
        <drug>
          <drugbank-id>DB03929</drugbank-id>
          <name>D-Serine</name>
        </drug>
        <drug>
          <drugbank-id>DB04160</drugbank-id>
          <name>Pyrophosphoric acid</name>
        </drug>
      </drugs>
      <enzymes/>
    </pathway>
  </pathways>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets>
    <target>
      <id>BE0000279</id>
      <name>30S ribosomal protein S12</name>
      <organism>Escherichia coli (strain K12)</organism>
      <actions>
        <action>inhibitor</action>
      </actions>
      <references>
        <articles>
          <article>
            <ref-id>A1713</ref-id>
            <pubmed-id>17139284</pubmed-id>
            <citation>Overington JP, Al-Lazikani B, Hopkins AL: How many drug targets are there? Nat Rev Drug Discov. 2006 Dec;5(12):993-6.</citation>
          </article>
          <article>
            <ref-id>A1715</ref-id>
            <pubmed-id>17016423</pubmed-id>
            <citation>Imming P, Sinning C, Meyer A: Drugs, their targets and the nature and number of drug targets. Nat Rev Drug Discov. 2006 Oct;5(10):821-34.</citation>
          </article>
          <article>
            <ref-id>A4972</ref-id>
            <pubmed-id>10702385</pubmed-id>
            <citation>Tolmasky ME: Bacterial resistance to aminoglycosides and beta-lactams: the Tn1331 transposon paradigm. Front Biosci. 2000 Jan 1;5:D20-9.</citation>
          </article>
        </articles>
        <textbooks/>
        <links/>
        <attachments>
          <attachment>
            <ref-id>F1954</ref-id>
            <title>Amikacin, DailyMed</title>
            <url>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/cite_this/attachments/files/000/001/954/original/20180501_f260ff2a-76a0-4672-9516-91c344b67890.pdf?1540315949</url>
          </attachment>
          <attachment>
            <ref-id>F1949</ref-id>
            <title>MedSafe NZ: Amikacin Injection</title>
            <url>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/cite_this/attachments/files/000/001/949/original/Amikacininj._MedSafe_NZ.pdf?1540245431</url>
          </attachment>
        </attachments>
      </references>
      <known-action>yes</known-action>
      <polypeptide id="P0A7S3" source="Swiss-Prot">
        <name>30S ribosomal protein S12</name>
        <general-function>Trna binding</general-function>
        <specific-function>With S4 and S5 plays an important role in translational accuracy.Interacts with and stabilizes bases of the 16S rRNA that are involved in tRNA selection in the A site and with the mRNA backbone. Located at the interface of the 30S and 50S subunits, it traverses the body of the 30S subunit contacting proteins on the other side and probably holding the rRNA structure together. The combined cluster of proteins S8, S12 and S17 appears to hold together the shoulder and platform of the 30S subunit (By similarity).Cryo-EM studies suggest that S12 contacts the EF-Tu bound tRNA in the A-site during codon-recognition. This contact is most likely broken as the aminoacyl-tRNA moves into the peptidyl transferase center in the 50S subunit.</specific-function>
        <gene-name>rpsL</gene-name>
        <locus/>
        <cellular-location>Cytoplasmic</cellular-location>
        <transmembrane-regions/>
        <signal-regions/>
        <theoretical-pi>11.49</theoretical-pi>
        <molecular-weight>13736.995</molecular-weight>
        <chromosome-location/>
        <organism ncbi-taxonomy-id="83333">Escherichia coli (strain K12)</organism>
        <external-identifiers>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>GenBank Gene Database</resource>
            <identifier>V00355</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>GenBank Protein Database</resource>
            <identifier>43010</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>UniProtKB</resource>
            <identifier>P0A7S3</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>UniProt Accession</resource>
            <identifier>RS12_ECOLI</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
        </external-identifiers>
        <synonyms>
          <synonym>strA</synonym>
        </synonyms>
        <amino-acid-sequence format="FASTA">&gt;lcl|BSEQ0010058|30S ribosomal protein S12
MATVNQLVRKPRARKVAKSNVPALEACPQKRGVCTRVYTTTPKKPNSALRKVCRVRLTNG
FEVTSYIGGEGHNLQEHSVILIRGGRVKDLPGVRYHTVRGALDCSGVKDRKQARSKYGVK
RPKA</amino-acid-sequence>
        <gene-sequence format="FASTA">&gt;lcl|BSEQ0010059|30S ribosomal protein S12 (rpsL)
ATGGCAACAGTTAACCAGCTGGTACGCAAACCACGTGCTCGCAAAGTTGCGAAAAGCAAC
GTGCCTGCGCTGGAAGCATGCCCGCAAAAACGTGGCGTATGTACTCGTGTATATACTACC
ACTCCTAAAAAACCGAACTCCGCGCTGCGTAAAGTATGCCGTGTTCGTCTGACTAACGGT
TTCGAAGTGACTTCCTACATCGGTGGTGAAGGTCACAACCTGCAGGAGCACTCCGTGATC
CTGATCCGTGGCGGTCGTGTTAAAGACCTCCCGGGTGTTCGTTACCACACCGTACGTGGT
GCGCTTGACTGCTCCGGCGTTAAAGACCGTAAGCAGGCTCGTTCCAAGTATGGCGTGAAG
CGTCCTAAGGCTTAA</gene-sequence>
        <pfams>
          <pfam>
            <identifier>PF00164</identifier>
            <name>Ribosom_S12_S23</name>
          </pfam>
        </pfams>
        <go-classifiers>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>component</category>
            <description>cytosol</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>component</category>
            <description>cytosolic small ribosomal subunit</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>function</category>
            <description>misfolded RNA binding</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>function</category>
            <description>rRNA binding</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>function</category>
            <description>structural constituent of ribosome</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>function</category>
            <description>tRNA binding</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>Group I intron splicing</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>positive regulation of RNA splicing</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>response to antibiotic</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>RNA folding</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>translation</description>
          </go-classifier>
        </go-classifiers>
      </polypeptide>
    </target>
  </targets>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>