<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-10-21" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05244</drugbank-id>
  <name>G4544</name>
  <description>G4544 is an oral gallium compound that enables oral absorption of the active ingredient contained in Ganite&amp;trade; (gallium nitrate injection). It targets bone tissue and is actively incorporated into bone mineral at sites where bone is metabolically active.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>For treatment of non-Hodgkin's lymphoma, bone metastases, Paget's disease, and osteoporosis</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>G4544 is one of a class of gallium containing compounds that were originally developed by the U.S. National Cancer Institute. In investigational studies, high doses of gallium nitrate demonstrated consistent antitumor activity in patients with non Hodgkin's lymphoma. However, experimental work by Genta personnel and others established that lower doses of gallium directly inhibited calcium release from bone, principally by decreasing bone resorption and possibly by also stimulating bone formation.</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>G4544 reduces bone loss by inhibiting calcium resorption from bone.  Preclinical evidence suggests that the mechanism of G4544 action is multifactorial and different from other current therapies used to treat bone loss, such as estrogen or selective estrogen receptor modulators (SERMs), calcitonin, or bisphosphonates (e.g., Zometa or Fosamax).  G4544 preferentially accumulates in metabolically active regions of bone, inhibits osteoclast-mediated bone resorption, and favorably alters bone mineral composition and properties.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption>Orally bioavailable.</absorption>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910047</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>