<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2007-10-21" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05140</drugbank-id>
  <name>RAV12</name>
  <description>RAV12 is investigated for use/treatment in solid tumors. RAV12 is a solid. RAV12 is a chimeric antibody that recognizes RAAG12, an N-linked carbohydrate antigen found on gastric, colon, pancreatic, prostate, ovarian, breast, and kidney cancer cells.&#13;
</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3266</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17363480</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Loo D, Pryer N, Young P, Liang T, Coberly S, King KL, Kang K, Roberts P, Tsao M, Xu X, Potts B, Mather JP: The glycotope-specific RAV12 monoclonal antibody induces oncosis in vitro and has antitumor activity against gastrointestinal adenocarcinoma tumor xenografts in vivo. Mol Cancer Ther. 2007 Mar;6(3):856-65.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3267</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17875727</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Li JC, Li R: RAV12 accelerates the desensitization of Akt/PKB pathway of insulin-like growth factor I receptor signaling in COLO205. Cancer Res. 2007 Sep 15;67(18):8856-64.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in solid tumors.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>RAV12 is a high affinity IgG1 chimeric antibody. RAAG12, the antigen target of RAV12 is a carbohydrate moiety whose expression is limited to primates. The structure of the RAV12 epitope is Galß 1-3GlcNacß 1-3Gal. Multiple RAV12 binding sites exist per sugar side-chain resulting in a very high apparent affinity and a nearly unmeasurable dissociation rate. Adenocarcinomas arising in breast, endometrial, ovarian, lung and prostate, display the RAA12 antigen to varying degrees. RAAG12 expression in normal tissues is generally limited to the apical membranes of certain epithelia of the GI track and the hepatobiliary system. Preclinical in vitro and in vivo experiments have suggested that RAV12 may have several anti-tumor activities, including direct cytotoxicity by a mechanism termed oncosis, antibody-dependent cellular cytotoxicity, complement mediated cytotoxicity, and alterations of cell survivability through down regulation of growth factor receptors. Oncosis is a form of cell death, distinct from apoptosis, that is characterized by loss of membrane integrity, followed by cell and organellar swelling, and death.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347909973</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>