<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2015-12-01" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB11054</drugbank-id>
  <name>Human cord blood hematopoietic progenitor cell</name>
  <description>Human cord blood hematopoietic progenitor cells consist of hematopoietic progenitor cells, monocytes, lymphocytes, and granulocytes from human cord blood. They are used during allogeneic unrelated and related hematopoietic stem cell transplantation procedures in patients with disorders affecting the hematopoietic system that are inherited, acquired, or result from myeloablative treatment. Human umbilical cord is a rich source of hematopoietic stem cells and progenitor cells that are capable of proliferation _in vitro_. Active and viable hematopoietic progenitor cells, or hematopoietic stem cells (HSCs) express the cell surface marker CD34 which is critical for cell identification [A32216]. Upon division and maturation at the bone marrow following intravenous administration to the patient, hematopoietic progenitor cells enter the systemic circulation to restore blood counts and function [FDA Label].&#13;
&#13;
After the first cord blood transplant in 1988 in a patient with Fanconi anemia [A32220], the use of umbilical cord blood transplantation was increased in clinical settings. Human cord blood hematopoietic progenitor cells can be collected from both related or unrelated donors. The unrelated donor transplant setting has several advantages over related donor transplant and bone marrow transplantation; it allows shorter time to transplant and tolerance of 1–2 human leukocyte antigen mismatch due to expanded donor pool, which increases the chance of finding a suitable donor, particularly in patients requiring urgent transplantation [A32219]. Other advantages of HSC transplantation include a lower risk of transmitting infections by latent viruses and improved targeting of ethnic minorities increased pool of rare haplotypes [A32219]. Umbilical cord blood cell transplantation was also associated with reduced incidence and severity of graft versus host disease (GVHD) thus improved survival rates of transplant patients compared to allogeneic bone marrow transplant setting, which may be due to "naive" nature of lymphocytes [A32223]. Hemacord is marketed in the U.S. as an allogeneic cord blood hematopoietic progenitor cell therapy for intravenous use.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii>XU53VK93MC</unii>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A32216</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>19277981</pubmed-id>
        <citation>da Silva CL, Goncalves R, Porada CD, Ascensao JL, Zanjani ED, Cabral JM, Almeida-Porada G: Differences amid bone marrow and cord blood hematopoietic stem/progenitor cell division kinetics. J Cell Physiol. 2009 Jul;220(1):102-11. doi: 10.1002/jcp.21736.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A32219</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>16399582</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Rocha V, Gluckman E: Clinical use of umbilical cord blood hematopoietic stem cells. Biol Blood Marrow Transplant. 2006 Jan;12(1 Suppl 1):34-41. doi: 10.1016/j.bbmt.2005.09.006.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A32220</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>16081348</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Gluckman E, Rocha V: History of the clinical use of umbilical cord blood hematopoietic cells. Cytotherapy. 2005;7(3):219-27. doi: 10.1080/14653240510027136.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A32223</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>16933834</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Bojanic I, Golubic Cepulic B: [Umbilical cord blood as a source of stem cells]. Acta Med Croatica. 2006 Jun;60(3):215-25.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Indicated for use in unrelated donor hematopoietic progenitor cell transplantation procedures in conjunction with an appropriate preparative regimen for hematopoietic and immunologic reconstitution in patients with disorders affecting the hematopoietic system that are inherited, acquired, or result from myeloablative treatment [FDA Label]. </indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>Human cord blood hematopoietic progenitor cells constitute the hematopoietic progenitor cells, monocytes, lymphocytes, and granulocytes that are isolated from red blood cells and plasma volume that are collected from the human umbilical cord and placenta [FDA Label]. According to the findings of retrospective data reviews and a single-arm prospective study, patients with hematologic malignancy who are receiving human cord blood hematopoietic progenitor cell transplantation achieved recovery of neutrophil counts, platelet counts, erythrocyte counts at rates of 76-83 %, 57-77 %, and 46-77 %, respectively [FDA Label]. </pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>Upon collection, the blood from human umbilical cord or placenta volume reduced and partially depleted of red blood cells and plasma. The remaining cells consist of hematopoietic progenitor cells (HPCs), monocytes, lymphocytes, and granulocytes. HPCs express the CD34 surface antigen; this allows distinct identification and characterization of those cells. With the evidence of CD34+ cells being able to engraft, CD34+ cells have been selected and widely used both for human autologous and allogeneic transplantations [A32216]. &#13;
&#13;
Human cord blood HPCs, that are intravenously administered, travel to the bone marrow of the transplant recipient where they undergo cell division and maturation. Mature cells are then released from the bone marrow where they enter the systemic bloodstream to circulate and travel to tissue sites. Mature cells serve to partially or fully restore hematologic function in patients with hematologic disorders by improving the counts and function of blood-borne cell, including immune cells, that originate from the bone marrow [FDA Label]. It is also suggested that mature leukocytes from HPC transplantation may synthesize enzymes that are able to circulate and improve cellular functions of some native tissues in patients with enzymatic abnormalities arising from types of storage disorders. Clear mechanism of this effect is not fully elucidated [FDA Label]. </mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity>There has been no cases of overdose with human cord blood hematopoietic progenitor cell therapy, and single doses up to 57.6 x 107 TNC/kg have been administered. Higher doses of dimethyl sulfoxide (DMSO) in the infusion mixture may induce altered mental status and coma. For DMSO overdosage, general supportive care is recommended [FDA Label].</toxicity>
  <metabolism>Pharmacokinetic parameters do not apply for human cord blood hematopoietic progenitor cells.</metabolism>
  <absorption>Intravenous administration achieves complete bioavailability. </absorption>
  <half-life>Pharmacokinetic parameters do not apply for human cord blood hematopoietic progenitor cells.</half-life>
  <protein-binding>Pharmacokinetic parameters do not apply for human cord blood hematopoietic progenitor cells.</protein-binding>
  <route-of-elimination>Pharmacokinetic parameters do not apply for human cord blood hematopoietic progenitor cells.</route-of-elimination>
  <volume-of-distribution>Pharmacokinetic parameters do not apply for human cord blood hematopoietic progenitor cells.</volume-of-distribution>
  <clearance>Pharmacokinetic parameters do not apply for human cord blood hematopoietic progenitor cells.</clearance>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>HemaCord</name>
      <labeller>New York Blood Center</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>76489-001</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2011-11-10</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Injection</dosage-form>
      <strength>500000000 1/25mL</strength>
      <route>Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>BLA125397</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>HemaCord</name>
      <ingredients>Human cord blood hematopoietic progenitor cell</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Allogeneic Cord Blood Hematopoietic Progenitor Cell Therapy</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Injection</form>
      <route>Intravenous</route>
      <strength>500000000 1/25mL</strength>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <fda-label>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/fda_labels/DB11054.pdf?1508438734</fda-label>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347911095</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>