<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2018-09-11" updated="2019-11-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB14685</drugbank-id>
  <name>Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live</name>
  <description/>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii>TM54L796SN</unii>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication/>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action/>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Human adenovirus B serotype 7 strain 55142 antigen</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>Adenovirus Type 4 and Type 7 Vaccine, Live</name>
      <labeller>Teva Women's Health, Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>51285-138</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2011-09-16</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form/>
      <strength/>
      <route>Oral</route>
      <fda-application-number>BLA125296</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>Adenovirus Type 4 and Type 7 Vaccine, Live</name>
      <ingredients>Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live + Human adenovirus e serotype 4 strain cl-68578 antigen</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Actively Acquired Immunity</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Adenovirus Vaccines</category>
      <mesh-id>D062705</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Live Human Adenovirus Type 7 Vaccine</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Live vaccines</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Vaccines</category>
      <mesh-id>D014612</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form/>
      <route>Oral</route>
      <strength/>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00005</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etanercept</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Etanercept.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00008</drugbank-id>
      <name>Peginterferon alfa-2a</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Peginterferon alfa-2a.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00011</drugbank-id>
      <name>Interferon alfa-n1</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Interferon alfa-n1.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00018</drugbank-id>
      <name>Interferon alfa-n3</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Interferon alfa-n3.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00022</drugbank-id>
      <name>Peginterferon alfa-2b</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Peginterferon alfa-2b.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00026</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anakinra</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Anakinra.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00033</drugbank-id>
      <name>Interferon gamma-1b</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Interferon gamma-1b.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00034</drugbank-id>
      <name>Interferon alfa-2a, Recombinant</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Interferon alfa-2a, Recombinant.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00041</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aldesleukin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Aldesleukin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00051</drugbank-id>
      <name>Adalimumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Adalimumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00056</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemtuzumab ozogamicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Gemtuzumab ozogamicin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00059</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pegaspargase</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Pegaspargase.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00065</drugbank-id>
      <name>Infliximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Infliximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00068</drugbank-id>
      <name>Interferon beta-1b</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Interferon beta-1b.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00069</drugbank-id>
      <name>Interferon alfacon-1</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Interferon alfacon-1.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00072</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trastuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Trastuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00073</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rituximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Rituximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00074</drugbank-id>
      <name>Basiliximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Basiliximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00075</drugbank-id>
      <name>Muromonab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Muromonab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00078</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibritumomab tiuxetan</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Ibritumomab tiuxetan.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00081</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tositumomab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Tositumomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00087</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alemtuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Alemtuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00091</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclosporine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Cyclosporine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00092</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alefacept</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Alefacept.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00095</drugbank-id>
      <name>Efalizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Efalizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00098</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antithymocyte immunoglobulin (rabbit)</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Antithymocyte immunoglobulin (rabbit).</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00105</drugbank-id>
      <name>Interferon alfa-2b</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Interferon alfa-2b.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00108</drugbank-id>
      <name>Natalizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Natalizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00111</drugbank-id>
      <name>Daclizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Daclizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00112</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bevacizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Bevacizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00120</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenylalanine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Phenylalanine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00188</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bortezomib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Bortezomib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00242</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cladribine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Cladribine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00262</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carmustine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Carmustine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00276</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amsacrine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Amsacrine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00290</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bleomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Bleomycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00291</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorambucil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Chlorambucil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00293</drugbank-id>
      <name>Raltitrexed</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Raltitrexed.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00305</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mitomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Mitomycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00307</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bexarotene</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Bexarotene.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00309</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vindesine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Vindesine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00322</drugbank-id>
      <name>Floxuridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Floxuridine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00328</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indomethacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Indomethacin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00352</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tioguanine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Tioguanine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00361</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vinorelbine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Vinorelbine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00380</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexrazoxane</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Dexrazoxane.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00398</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sorafenib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Sorafenib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00428</drugbank-id>
      <name>Streptozocin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Streptozocin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00432</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trifluridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Trifluridine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00441</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemcitabine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Gemcitabine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00444</drugbank-id>
      <name>Teniposide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Teniposide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00445</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epirubicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Epirubicin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00446</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chloramphenicol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Chloramphenicol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00480</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lenalidomide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Lenalidomide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00488</drugbank-id>
      <name>Altretamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Altretamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00495</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zidovudine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Zidovudine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00515</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cisplatin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Cisplatin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00526</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxaliplatin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Oxaliplatin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00531</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclophosphamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Cyclophosphamide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00541</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vincristine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Vincristine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00544</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluorouracil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Fluorouracil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00550</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propylthiouracil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Propylthiouracil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00552</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentostatin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Pentostatin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00563</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methotrexate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Methotrexate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00564</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbamazepine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Carbamazepine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00570</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vinblastine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Vinblastine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00601</drugbank-id>
      <name>Linezolid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Linezolid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00619</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imatinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Imatinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00631</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clofarabine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Clofarabine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00642</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pemetrexed</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Pemetrexed.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00688</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mycophenolate mofetil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Mycophenolate mofetil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00694</drugbank-id>
      <name>Daunorubicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Daunorubicin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00755</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tretinoin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Tretinoin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00762</drugbank-id>
      <name>Irinotecan</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Irinotecan.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00763</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methimazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Methimazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00773</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etoposide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Etoposide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00795</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfasalazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Sulfasalazine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00851</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dacarbazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Dacarbazine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00853</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temozolomide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Temozolomide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00859</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penicillamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Penicillamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00864</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tacrolimus</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Tacrolimus.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00877</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sirolimus</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Sirolimus.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00888</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mechlorethamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Mechlorethamine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00928</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azacitidine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Azacitidine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00958</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carboplatin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Carboplatin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00970</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dactinomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Dactinomycin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00987</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cytarabine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Cytarabine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00993</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azathioprine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Azathioprine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00997</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxorubicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Doxorubicin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01005</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydroxyurea</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Hydroxyurea.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01008</drugbank-id>
      <name>Busulfan</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Busulfan.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01024</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mycophenolic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Mycophenolic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01030</drugbank-id>
      <name>Topotecan</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Topotecan.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01033</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mercaptopurine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Mercaptopurine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01041</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thalidomide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Thalidomide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01042</drugbank-id>
      <name>Melphalan</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Melphalan.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01073</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fludarabine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Fludarabine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01097</drugbank-id>
      <name>Leflunomide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Leflunomide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01099</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flucytosine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Flucytosine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01101</drugbank-id>
      <name>Capecitabine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Capecitabine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01168</drugbank-id>
      <name>Procarbazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Procarbazine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01169</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arsenic trioxide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Arsenic trioxide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01177</drugbank-id>
      <name>Idarubicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Idarubicin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01181</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ifosfamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Ifosfamide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01196</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estramustine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Estramustine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01204</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mitoxantrone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Mitoxantrone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01206</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lomustine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Lomustine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01229</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paclitaxel</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Paclitaxel.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01248</drugbank-id>
      <name>Docetaxel</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Docetaxel.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01254</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dasatinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Dasatinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01257</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eculizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Eculizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01262</drugbank-id>
      <name>Decitabine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Decitabine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01268</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sunitinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Sunitinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01280</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nelarabine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Nelarabine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01281</drugbank-id>
      <name>Abatacept</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Abatacept.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01394</drugbank-id>
      <name>Colchicine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Colchicine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01423</drugbank-id>
      <name>Stepronin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Stepronin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01590</drugbank-id>
      <name>Everolimus</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Everolimus.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01611</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydroxychloroquine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Hydroxychloroquine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01816</drugbank-id>
      <name>Castanospermine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Castanospermine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02546</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vorinostat</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Vorinostat.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02806</drugbank-id>
      <name>2-Methoxyethanol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with 2-Methoxyethanol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03523</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brequinar</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Brequinar.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04572</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiotepa</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Thiotepa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04845</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ixabepilone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Ixabepilone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04868</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nilotinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Nilotinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04951</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pirfenidone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Pirfenidone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04956</drugbank-id>
      <name>Afelimomab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Afelimomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05015</drugbank-id>
      <name>Belinostat</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Belinostat.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05109</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trabectedin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Trabectedin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05258</drugbank-id>
      <name>Interferon alfa</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Interferon alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05259</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glatiramer</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Glatiramer.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05260</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gallium nitrate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Gallium nitrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05459</drugbank-id>
      <name>Briakinumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Briakinumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05472</drugbank-id>
      <name>omega interferon</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with omega interferon.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05676</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apremilast</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Apremilast.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05773</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trastuzumab emtansine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Trastuzumab emtansine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06168</drugbank-id>
      <name>Canakinumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Canakinumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06273</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tocilizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Tocilizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06287</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temsirolimus</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Temsirolimus.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06372</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rilonacept</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Rilonacept.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06589</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pazopanib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Pazopanib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06603</drugbank-id>
      <name>Panobinostat</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Panobinostat.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06612</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mepolizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Mepolizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06616</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bosutinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Bosutinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06643</drugbank-id>
      <name>Denosumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Denosumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06662</drugbank-id>
      <name>Abetimus</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Abetimus.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06674</drugbank-id>
      <name>Golimumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Golimumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06681</drugbank-id>
      <name>Belatacept</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Belatacept.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06769</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bendamustine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Bendamustine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06772</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cabazitaxel</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Cabazitaxel.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06813</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pralatrexate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Pralatrexate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08059</drugbank-id>
      <name>Wortmannin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Wortmannin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08868</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fingolimod</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Fingolimod.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08870</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brentuximab vedotin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Brentuximab vedotin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08871</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eribulin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Eribulin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08877</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ruxolitinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Ruxolitinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08879</drugbank-id>
      <name>Belimumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Belimumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08880</drugbank-id>
      <name>Teriflunomide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Teriflunomide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08889</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carfilzomib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Carfilzomib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08895</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tofacitinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Tofacitinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08901</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ponatinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Ponatinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08904</drugbank-id>
      <name>Certolizumab pegol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Certolizumab pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08908</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dimethyl fumarate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Dimethyl fumarate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08910</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pomalidomide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Pomalidomide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08935</drugbank-id>
      <name>Obinutuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Obinutuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09029</drugbank-id>
      <name>Secukinumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Secukinumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09033</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vedolizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Vedolizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09036</drugbank-id>
      <name>Siltuximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Siltuximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09042</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tedizolid phosphate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Tedizolid phosphate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09052</drugbank-id>
      <name>Blinatumomab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Blinatumomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09053</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibrutinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Ibrutinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09054</drugbank-id>
      <name>Idelalisib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Idelalisib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09073</drugbank-id>
      <name>Palbociclib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Palbociclib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09074</drugbank-id>
      <name>Olaparib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Olaparib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09077</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dinutuximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Dinutuximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09082</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vilanterol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Vilanterol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09122</drugbank-id>
      <name>Peginterferon beta-1a</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Peginterferon beta-1a.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09312</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antilymphocyte immunoglobulin (horse)</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Antilymphocyte immunoglobulin (horse).</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11466</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tepoxalin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Tepoxalin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11569</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ixekizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Ixekizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11580</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ravulizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Ravulizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11616</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pirarubicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Pirarubicin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11693</drugbank-id>
      <name>Voclosporin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Voclosporin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11708</drugbank-id>
      <name>Peficitinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Peficitinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11767</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sarilumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Sarilumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11776</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brodalumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Brodalumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11803</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sirukumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Sirukumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Baricitinib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Baricitinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11834</drugbank-id>
      <name>Guselkumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Guselkumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11988</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ocrelizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Ocrelizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12025</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triptolide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Triptolide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12612</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ozanimod</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Ozanimod.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12617</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mizoribine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Mizoribine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12692</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gusperimus</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Gusperimus.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12814</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cepeginterferon alfa-2B</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Cepeginterferon alfa-2B.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12902</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trofosfamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Trofosfamide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12947</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxifluridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Doxifluridine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12991</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deoxyspergualin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Deoxyspergualin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12996</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acteoside</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Acteoside.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13014</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hypericin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Hypericin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13068</drugbank-id>
      <name>9-(N-methyl-L-isoleucine)-cyclosporin A</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with 9-(N-methyl-L-isoleucine)-cyclosporin A.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13241</drugbank-id>
      <name>Begelomab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Begelomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14066</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetrandrine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Tetrandrine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14219</drugbank-id>
      <name>Monomethyl fumarate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Monomethyl fumarate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14724</drugbank-id>
      <name>Emapalumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Emapalumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14919</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rozanolixizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Rozanolixizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15253</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bleselumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of infection can be increased when Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live is combined with Bleselumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00198</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oseltamivir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Oseltamivir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00558</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zanamivir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Zanamivir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06614</drugbank-id>
      <name>Peramivir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Peramivir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00478</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rimantadine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Rimantadine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00915</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amantadine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Amantadine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14039</drugbank-id>
      <name>Erenumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Erenumab is combined with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00277</drugbank-id>
      <name>Theophylline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Theophylline can be increased when it is combined with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12371</drugbank-id>
      <name>Siponimod</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Siponimod.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14762</drugbank-id>
      <name>Risankizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Risankizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12159</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dupilumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Dupilumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15528</drugbank-id>
      <name>Onasemnogene abeparvovec</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Onasemnogene abeparvovec.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14681</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cortisone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Cortisone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00180</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flunisolide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Flunisolide can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00394</drugbank-id>
      <name>Beclomethasone dipropionate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Beclomethasone dipropionate can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00443</drugbank-id>
      <name>Betamethasone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Betamethasone can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00588</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluticasone propionate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Fluticasone propionate can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00591</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluocinolone acetonide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Fluocinolone acetonide can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00620</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triamcinolone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Triamcinolone can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00635</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Prednisone can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00687</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fludrocortisone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Fludrocortisone can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00741</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrocortisone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Hydrocortisone can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00764</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mometasone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Mometasone can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00860</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisolone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Prednisolone can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00959</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylprednisolone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Methylprednisolone can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01108</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trilostane</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Trilostane can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01222</drugbank-id>
      <name>Budesonide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Budesonide can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01234</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexamethasone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Dexamethasone can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01285</drugbank-id>
      <name>Corticotropin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Corticotropin can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01380</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cortisone acetate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Cortisone acetate can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01384</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paramethasone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Paramethasone can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01410</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ciclesonide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ciclesonide can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04630</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aldosterone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Aldosterone can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08906</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluticasone furoate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Fluticasone furoate can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08970</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluprednidene</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Fluprednidene can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08971</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluocortolone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Fluocortolone can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09091</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tixocortol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Tixocortol can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09378</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluprednisolone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Fluprednisolone can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09383</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meprednisone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Meprednisone can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11487</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexamethasone isonicotinate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Dexamethasone isonicotinate can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11529</drugbank-id>
      <name>Melengestrol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Melengestrol can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11750</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clobetasol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Clobetasol can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11921</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deflazacort</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Deflazacort can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13003</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cortivazol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Cortivazol can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednylidene</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Prednylidene can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13223</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluocortin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Fluocortin can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13491</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluperolone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Fluperolone can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13664</drugbank-id>
      <name>Formocortal</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Formocortal can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13728</drugbank-id>
      <name>Halometasone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Halometasone can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13843</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cloprednol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Cloprednol can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13856</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluclorolone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Fluclorolone can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13867</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluticasone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Fluticasone can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14512</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mometasone furoate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Mometasone furoate can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14538</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrocortisone aceponate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Hydrocortisone aceponate can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14539</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrocortisone acetate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Hydrocortisone acetate can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14545</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrocortisone succinate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Hydrocortisone succinate can be decreased when used in combination with Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00223</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diflorasone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Diflorasone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00240</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alclometasone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Alclometasone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00253</drugbank-id>
      <name>Medrysone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Medrysone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00288</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amcinonide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Amcinonide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00324</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluorometholone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Fluorometholone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00547</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desoximetasone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Desoximetasone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00596</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ulobetasol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Ulobetasol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00663</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flumethasone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Flumethasone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00838</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clocortolone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Clocortolone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00846</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flurandrenolide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Flurandrenolide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14596</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loteprednol etabonate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Loteprednol etabonate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00896</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rimexolone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Rimexolone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01013</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clobetasol propionate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Clobetasol propionate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01047</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluocinonide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Fluocinonide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01130</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednicarbate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Prednicarbate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01260</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desonide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Desonide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06781</drugbank-id>
      <name>Difluprednate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Difluprednate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06786</drugbank-id>
      <name>Halcinonide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Halcinonide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09095</drugbank-id>
      <name>Difluocortolone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Difluocortolone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13158</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clobetasone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Clobetasone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14540</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrocortisone butyrate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Hydrocortisone butyrate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14541</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrocortisone cypionate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Hydrocortisone cypionate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14543</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrocortisone probutate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Hydrocortisone probutate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14544</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrocortisone valerate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Hydrocortisone valerate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00873</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loteprednol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Loteprednol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14631</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisolone phosphate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Prednisolone phosphate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14633</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisolone hemisuccinate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Prednisolone hemisuccinate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14634</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluprednidene acetate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Fluprednidene acetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14643</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylprednisolone aceponate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Methylprednisolone aceponate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14644</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylprednisolone hemisuccinate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Methylprednisolone hemisuccinate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14646</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisone acetate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Prednisone acetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14652</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clocortolone acetate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Clocortolone acetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14659</drugbank-id>
      <name>Melengestrol acetate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Melengestrol acetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14669</drugbank-id>
      <name>Betamethasone phosphate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Betamethasone phosphate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15566</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisolone acetate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Prednisolone acetate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00060</drugbank-id>
      <name>Interferon beta-1a</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Interferon beta-1a.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00109</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enfuvirtide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Enfuvirtide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00110</drugbank-id>
      <name>Palivizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Palivizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00220</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nelfinavir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Nelfinavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00224</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indinavir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Indinavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00238</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nevirapine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Nevirapine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00300</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenofovir disoproxil</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Tenofovir disoproxil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00369</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cidofovir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Cidofovir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00426</drugbank-id>
      <name>Famciclovir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Famciclovir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00442</drugbank-id>
      <name>Entecavir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Entecavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00503</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ritonavir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Ritonavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00529</drugbank-id>
      <name>Foscarnet</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Foscarnet.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00577</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valaciclovir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Valaciclovir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00625</drugbank-id>
      <name>Efavirenz</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Efavirenz.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00649</drugbank-id>
      <name>Stavudine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Stavudine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00701</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amprenavir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Amprenavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00705</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delavirdine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Delavirdine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00709</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lamivudine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Lamivudine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00718</drugbank-id>
      <name>Adefovir dipivoxil</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Adefovir dipivoxil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00787</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acyclovir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Acyclovir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00811</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ribavirin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Ribavirin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00879</drugbank-id>
      <name>Emtricitabine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Emtricitabine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00900</drugbank-id>
      <name>Didanosine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Didanosine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00932</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tipranavir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Tipranavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00943</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zalcitabine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Zalcitabine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01004</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ganciclovir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Ganciclovir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01048</drugbank-id>
      <name>Abacavir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Abacavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01072</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atazanavir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Atazanavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01232</drugbank-id>
      <name>Saquinavir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Saquinavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Darunavir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Darunavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01265</drugbank-id>
      <name>Telbivudine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Telbivudine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01319</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosamprenavir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Fosamprenavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01601</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lopinavir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Lopinavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01610</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valganciclovir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Valganciclovir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02600</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oseltamivir acid</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Oseltamivir acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03312</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brivudine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Brivudine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04835</drugbank-id>
      <name>Maraviroc</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Maraviroc.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04886</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calanolide A</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Calanolide A.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05102</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rupintrivir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Rupintrivir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05105</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pleconaril</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Pleconaril.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05521</drugbank-id>
      <name>Telaprevir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Telaprevir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05532</drugbank-id>
      <name>BMS-488043</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with BMS-488043.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05871</drugbank-id>
      <name>UC-781</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with UC-781.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05941</drugbank-id>
      <name>Leronlimab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Leronlimab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06198</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alovudine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Alovudine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06234</drugbank-id>
      <name>Maribavir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Maribavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06236</drugbank-id>
      <name>Elvucitabine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Elvucitabine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06290</drugbank-id>
      <name>Simeprevir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Simeprevir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06408</drugbank-id>
      <name>Taribavirin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Taribavirin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06414</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etravirine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Etravirine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06683</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clevudine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Clevudine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06759</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fomivirsen</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Fomivirsen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Raltegravir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Raltegravir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08188</drugbank-id>
      <name>Emivirine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Emivirine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08502</drugbank-id>
      <name>Capravirine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Capravirine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08639</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dapivirine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Dapivirine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08864</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rilpivirine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Rilpivirine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08873</drugbank-id>
      <name>Boceprevir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Boceprevir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08930</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dolutegravir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Dolutegravir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08934</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sofosbuvir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Sofosbuvir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09027</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ledipasvir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Ledipasvir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09101</drugbank-id>
      <name>Elvitegravir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Elvitegravir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09102</drugbank-id>
      <name>Daclatasvir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Daclatasvir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09183</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dasabuvir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Dasabuvir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09296</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ombitasvir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Ombitasvir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09297</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paritaprevir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Paritaprevir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09299</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenofovir alafenamide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Tenofovir alafenamide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11574</drugbank-id>
      <name>Elbasvir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Elbasvir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11575</drugbank-id>
      <name>Grazoprevir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Grazoprevir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11586</drugbank-id>
      <name>Asunaprevir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Asunaprevir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11613</drugbank-id>
      <name>Velpatasvir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Velpatasvir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11713</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ruzasvir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Ruzasvir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11758</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cenicriviroc</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Cenicriviroc.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11799</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bictegravir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Bictegravir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11808</drugbank-id>
      <name>Faldaprevir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Faldaprevir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11844</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pritelivir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Pritelivir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11888</drugbank-id>
      <name>Laninamivir octanoate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Laninamivir octanoate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11944</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ingavirin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Ingavirin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11948</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lapachone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Lapachone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11998</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sorivudine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Sorivudine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12020</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tecovirimat</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Tecovirimat.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12026</drugbank-id>
      <name>Voxilaprevir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Voxilaprevir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12037</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vedroprevir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Vedroprevir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12070</drugbank-id>
      <name>Letermovir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Letermovir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12225</drugbank-id>
      <name>Beclabuvir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Beclabuvir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atevirdine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Atevirdine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12301</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doravirine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Doravirine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12470</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexelvucitabine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Dexelvucitabine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12480</drugbank-id>
      <name>Betulinic Acid</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Betulinic Acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12531</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lobucavir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Lobucavir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12687</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vesatolimod</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Vesatolimod.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12698</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibalizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Ibalizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12753</drugbank-id>
      <name>Racivir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Racivir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12791</drugbank-id>
      <name>Laninamivir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Laninamivir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12901</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fiacitabine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Fiacitabine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13041</drugbank-id>
      <name>Odalasvir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Odalasvir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13156</drugbank-id>
      <name>Inosine pranobex</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Inosine pranobex.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13288</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tromantadine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Tromantadine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13597</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moroxydine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Moroxydine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13609</drugbank-id>
      <name>Umifenovir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Umifenovir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13641</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metisazone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Metisazone.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13776</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibacitabine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Ibacitabine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13868</drugbank-id>
      <name>Adefovir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Adefovir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13878</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pibrentasvir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Pibrentasvir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13879</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glecaprevir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Glecaprevir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13997</drugbank-id>
      <name>Baloxavir marboxil</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Baloxavir marboxil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14126</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenofovir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Tenofovir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14813</drugbank-id>
      <name>PF-232798</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with PF-232798.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14906</drugbank-id>
      <name>Adafosbuvir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Adafosbuvir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14930</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alovudine F-18</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Alovudine F-18.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15193</drugbank-id>
      <name>BMS-955176</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with BMS-955176.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15206</drugbank-id>
      <name>Uprifosbuvir</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Uprifosbuvir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15332</drugbank-id>
      <name>Radavirsen</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Radavirsen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15427</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fialuridine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Adenovirus type 7 vaccine live can be decreased when used in combination with Fialuridine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers/>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>