<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2019-05-20" updated="2019-12-19">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB15066</drugbank-id>
  <name>Givosiran</name>
  <description>Givosiran is a small interfering RNA (siRNA) directed towards 5-aminolevulinic acid synthase, a critical enzyme in the heme biosynthesis pathway.[L10202] It is manufactured by Alnylam Pharmaceuticals and was first approved for use in the United States in November 2019 for the treatment of adults with acute hepatic porphyria, a genetic disorder in which the overproduction of toxic heme intermediates leads to neuro-, nephro-, and gastrotoxicity.[L10202] Givosiran represents an important step forward in the treatment of acute hepatic porphyria as it is the first approved pharmacotherapy for the prevention of acute attacks - previous strategies involved non-therapeutic measures (e.g. trigger avoidance), intravenous [hemin] for the treatment of attacks, and liver transplantation in refractory cases.[A187991] Givosiran is the second-ever FDA-approved member of the siRNA drug class (the first being [patisiran]), a new class of drugs promising an important and exciting step forward in the treatment of genetic disorders.</description>
  <cas-number>1639325-43-1</cas-number>
  <unii>ROV204583W</unii>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A187982</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>26528940</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Chan A, Liebow A, Yasuda M, Gan L, Racie T, Maier M, Kuchimanchi S, Foster D, Milstein S, Charisse K, Sehgal A, Manoharan M, Meyers R, Fitzgerald K, Simon A, Desnick RJ, Querbes W: Preclinical Development of a Subcutaneous ALAS1 RNAi Therapeutic for Treatment of Hepatic Porphyrias Using Circulating RNA Quantification. Mol Ther Nucleic Acids. 2015 Nov 3;4:e263. doi: 10.1038/mtna.2015.36.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A187988</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>30987916</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Bonkovsky HL, Dixon N, Rudnick S: Pathogenesis and clinical features of the acute hepatic porphyrias (AHPs). Mol Genet Metab. 2019 Mar 6. pii: S1096-7192(19)30084-8. doi: 10.1016/j.ymgme.2019.03.002.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A187991</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>30726693</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Sardh E, Harper P, Balwani M, Stein P, Rees D, Bissell DM, Desnick R, Parker C, Phillips J, Bonkovsky HL, Vassiliou D, Penz C, Chan-Daniels A, He Q, Querbes W, Fitzgerald K, Kim JB, Garg P, Vaishnaw A, Simon AR, Anderson KE: Phase 1 Trial of an RNA Interference Therapy for Acute Intermittent Porphyria. N Engl J Med. 2019 Feb 7;380(6):549-558. doi: 10.1056/NEJMoa1807838.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A188015</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>31102718</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Fontanellas A, Avila MA, Anderson KE, Deybach JC: Current and innovative emerging therapies for porphyrias with hepatic involvement. J Hepatol. 2019 Aug;71(2):422-433. doi: 10.1016/j.jhep.2019.05.003. Epub 2019 May 16.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L10202</ref-id>
        <title>FDA Approved Drug Products: Givlaari subcutaneous injection</title>
        <url>https://www.accessdata.fda.gov/drugsatfda_docs/label/2019/0212194s000lbl.pdf</url>
      </link>
    </links>
    <attachments>
      <attachment>
        <ref-id>F4724</ref-id>
        <title>Supplementary Appendix for Phase 1 trial of an RNA interference therapy for acute intermittent porphyria</title>
        <url>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/cite_this/attachments/files/000/004/724/original/supplement_to_30726693.pdf?1574362854</url>
      </attachment>
      <attachment>
        <ref-id>F4727</ref-id>
        <title>Study Protocol for Phase 1 trial of an RNA interference therapy for acute intermittent porphyria</title>
        <url>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/cite_this/attachments/files/000/004/727/original/protocol_for_phase_1_trial.pdf?1574375964</url>
      </attachment>
    </attachments>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference>Brian Bettencourt, Kevin Fitzgerald, William Querbes, Robert J. Desnick, Makiko Yasuda, "Compositions and methods for inhibiting expression of the ALAS1 gene." US Patent US10119143B2, issued November, 2018.</synthesis-reference>
  <indication>Givosiran is indicated for the treatment of adults with acute hepatic porphyria.[L10202]</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>Givosiran decreases the rate at which toxic byproducts of heme synthesis are produced in the livers of patients with acute hepatic porphyria, thus preventing their accumulation and associated neuro-, nephro-, and gastrotoxicity.[L10202,A187988] As givosiran works at the transcriptional level, it has a long duration of action and can be administered subcutaneously on a monthly basis. Although givosiran appears to be relatively well-tolerated, hepatic and renal toxicity were noted during clinical trials. Patients receiving therapy with givosiran should undergo routine laboratory monitoring of liver and kidney function.[L10202]</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>Acute hepatic porphyrias are a class of genetic disorders involving deficiencies in the pathway responsible for heme synthesis in liver hepatocytes.[A187988] The rate-limiting step in heme synthesis is the first enzyme in the pathway, 5-aminolevulinic acid synthase (ALAS1), which is controlled via a negative feedback loop by the presence of heme end-product in the liver.[A187988] Deficiencies in later enzymes in the pathway result in low circulating levels of heme, which in turn stimulates the up-regulation of ALAS1. The overexpression of ALAS1, in combination with downstream enzyme deficiencies, leads to the overproduction and accumulation of toxic heme intermediates which are ultimately responsible for the neurovisceral symptoms characteristic of acute hepatic porphyrias.[L10202,A187988]&#13;
&#13;
Givosiran is a double-stranded small interfering RNA (siRNA) directed at ALAS1 mRNA in hepatocytes.[L10202] It is covalently bound to a ligand containing three N-acetylgalactosamine (GalNAc) residues that facilitate uptake into hepatocytes via asialoglycoprotein receptors (ASPGRs), which are highly expressed on the cell surface of hepatocytes and are selective for glycoproteins containing GalNAc residues.[F4727] Following endocytosis into hepatocytes, the antisense strand of givosiran is loaded into an enzyme complex called the RNA-induced silencing complex (RISC), which uses the antisense strand to seek out and selectively cleave the complementary mRNA sequence (in this case found between nucleotide 918 and 937 of the ALAS1 mRNA).[F4727] Cleavage of the ALAS1 mRNA results in its degradation, preventing the synthesis of the ALAS1 enzyme and ultimately leading to reduced circulating levels of neurotoxic heme intermediates.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity>Little information is currently available regarding the toxicity of givosiran. Weekly subcutaneous dosing of up to 30 mg/kg in both female and male rats resulted in no apparent effects on fertility or reproductive function.[L10202]</toxicity>
  <metabolism>Givosiran is metabolized to shorter oligonucleotides by nuclease enzymes. Its active metabolite, AS(N-1)3' givosiran, carries equal potency to the parent drug and its AUC&lt;sub&gt;0-24&lt;/sub&gt; comprises approximately 45% of the parent drug AUC at the recommended givosiran dosage.[L10202] _In vitro_ studies suggest that givosiran is not a substrate of the CYP enzyme system.[L10202]</metabolism>
  <absorption>The mean steady-state C&lt;sub&gt;max&lt;/sub&gt; and AUC&lt;sub&gt;24&lt;/sub&gt; of givosiran are 321 ng/mL and 4130 ng·h/mL, respectively, and increase proportionally over the dosing range.[L10202] The T&lt;sub&gt;max&lt;/sub&gt; following subcutaneous injection is approximately 3 hours.[L10202] </absorption>
  <half-life>Both givosiran and its active metabolite, AS(N-1)3' givosiran, have an elimination half-life of 6 hours.[L10202]</half-life>
  <protein-binding>Plasma protein binding is inversely proportional to givosiran concentration, ranging from 92% at 1 μg/mL to 21% at 50 μg/mL.[L10202] The specific plasma protein to which givosiran is bound is unclear.</protein-binding>
  <route-of-elimination>Approximately 5-14% of the dose recovered in urine is unchanged parent drug, and 4-13% is AS(N-1)3' givosiran.[L10202]</route-of-elimination>
  <volume-of-distribution>The apparent central volume of distribution is 10.4 L.[L10202] Both givosiran and AS(N-1)3' givosiran distribute primarily to the liver following subcutaneous administration.[L10202]</volume-of-distribution>
  <clearance>The apparent clearance of givosiran is 35.1 L/hr.[L10202]</clearance>
  <salts>
    <salt>
      <drugbank-id primary="true">DBSALT002906</drugbank-id>
      <name>Givosiran sodium</name>
      <unii>5XE21E41RT</unii>
      <cas-number/>
      <inchikey/>
    </salt>
  </salts>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="inn/usan">Givosiran</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>Givlaari</name>
      <labeller>Alnylam Pharmaceuticals, Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>71336-1001</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2019-12-12</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>189 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Subcutaneous</route>
      <fda-application-number>NDA212194</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>Givlaari</name>
      <ingredients>Givosiran</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Hepatotoxic Agents</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nephrotoxic agents</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Oligonucleotides</category>
      <mesh-id>D009841</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Oligonucleotides, Antisense</category>
      <mesh-id>D016376</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>RNA, Antisense</category>
      <mesh-id>D016372</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Injection, solution</form>
      <route>Subcutaneous</route>
      <strength>189 mg/1mL</strength>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00529</drugbank-id>
      <name>Foscarnet</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Givosiran is combined with Foscarnet.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00742</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mannitol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Mannitol is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00300</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenofovir disoproxil</name>
      <description>Givosiran may increase the nephrotoxic activities of Tenofovir disoproxil.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09299</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenofovir alafenamide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may increase the nephrotoxic activities of Tenofovir alafenamide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14126</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenofovir</name>
      <description>Givosiran may increase the nephrotoxic activities of Tenofovir.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00091</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclosporine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cyclosporine is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00159</drugbank-id>
      <name>Icosapent</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Icosapent is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00229</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefotiam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefotiam is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00244</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mesalazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Mesalazine is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00267</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefmenoxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefmenoxime is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00274</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefmetazole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefmetazole is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00282</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pamidronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Pamidronic acid is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00328</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indomethacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Indomethacin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00369</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cidofovir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cidofovir is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00430</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefpiramide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefpiramide is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00438</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftazidime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ceftazidime is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00447</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loracarbef</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Loracarbef is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00452</drugbank-id>
      <name>Framycetin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Framycetin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00456</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefalotin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefalotin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00465</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketorolac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ketorolac is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00469</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenoxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tenoxicam is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00479</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amikacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amikacin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00493</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefotaxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefotaxime is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00500</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolmetin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tolmetin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00554</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piroxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Piroxicam is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00563</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methotrexate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Methotrexate is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00567</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cephalexin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cephalexin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00573</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Fenoprofen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00577</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valaciclovir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Valaciclovir is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00580</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valdecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Valdecoxib is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00605</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulindac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Sulindac is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00626</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bacitracin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Bacitracin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00681</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amphotericin B</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Amphotericin B is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00684</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tobramycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tobramycin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00689</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cephaloglycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cephaloglycin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00695</drugbank-id>
      <name>Furosemide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Furosemide is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00712</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flurbiprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Flurbiprofen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00718</drugbank-id>
      <name>Adefovir dipivoxil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Adefovir dipivoxil is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00749</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etodolac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Etodolac is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00784</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mefenamic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Mefenamic acid is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00795</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfasalazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Sulfasalazine is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00798</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gentamicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Gentamicin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00812</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenylbutazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Phenylbutazone is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00814</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meloxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Meloxicam is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00821</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Carprofen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00833</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefaclor</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefaclor is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00861</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diflunisal</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Diflunisal is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00864</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tacrolimus</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tacrolimus is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00887</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bumetanide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Bumetanide is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00903</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etacrynic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Etacrynic acid is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00923</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceforanide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ceforanide is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00936</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salicylic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Salicylic acid is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00939</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meclofenamic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Meclofenamic acid is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00945</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetylsalicylic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Acetylsalicylic acid is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00955</drugbank-id>
      <name>Netilmicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Netilmicin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00958</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carboplatin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Carboplatin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00991</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxaprozin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Oxaprozin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00994</drugbank-id>
      <name>Neomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Neomycin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00999</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrochlorothiazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Hydrochlorothiazide is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01009</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ketoprofen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01014</drugbank-id>
      <name>Balsalazide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Balsalazide is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01050</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibuprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ibuprofen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01066</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefditoren</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefditoren is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01072</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atazanavir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Atazanavir is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01082</drugbank-id>
      <name>Streptomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Streptomycin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01111</drugbank-id>
      <name>Colistimethate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Colistimethate is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01112</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefuroxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefuroxime is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01139</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefapirin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefapirin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01140</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefadroxil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefadroxil is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01150</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefprozil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefprozil is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01172</drugbank-id>
      <name>Kanamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Kanamycin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01212</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftriaxone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ceftriaxone is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01250</drugbank-id>
      <name>Olsalazine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Olsalazine is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01283</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lumiracoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Lumiracoxib is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01326</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefamandole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefamandole is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01327</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefazolin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefazolin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01328</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefonicid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefonicid is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01329</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefoperazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefoperazone is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01330</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefotetan</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefotetan is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01331</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefoxitin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefoxitin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01332</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftizoxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ceftizoxime is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01333</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefradine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefradine is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01397</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium salicylate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Magnesium salicylate is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01399</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salsalate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Salsalate is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01401</drugbank-id>
      <name>Choline magnesium trisalicylate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Choline magnesium trisalicylate is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01413</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefepime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefepime is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01414</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefacetrile</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefacetrile is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01415</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftibuten</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ceftibuten is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01416</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefpodoxime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefpodoxime is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01419</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antrafenine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Antrafenine is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01421</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paromomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Paromomycin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01438</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenazopyridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Phenazopyridine is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01600</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiaprofenic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tiaprofenic acid is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01601</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lopinavir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Lopinavir is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02247</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrolyzed Cephalothin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Hydrolyzed Cephalothin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03450</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cephalothin Group</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cephalothin Group is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03585</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxyphenbutazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Oxyphenbutazone is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ribostamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ribostamycin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04263</drugbank-id>
      <name>Geneticin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Geneticin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04552</drugbank-id>
      <name>Niflumic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Niflumic acid is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04570</drugbank-id>
      <name>Latamoxef</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Latamoxef is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04626</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apramycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Apramycin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04729</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gentamicin C1a</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Gentamicin C1a is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04743</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nimesulide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Nimesulide is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04808</drugbank-id>
      <name>Neamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Neamine is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04812</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benoxaprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Benoxaprofen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metamizole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Metamizole is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04828</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zomepirac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Zomepirac is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04918</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftobiprole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ceftobiprole is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05095</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cimicoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cimicoxib is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06590</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftaroline fosamil</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ceftaroline fosamil is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06696</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arbekacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Arbekacin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06725</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lornoxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Lornoxicam is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06736</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aceclofenac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Aceclofenac is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06737</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zaltoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Zaltoprofen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07402</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azapropazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Azapropazone is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07477</drugbank-id>
      <name>Felbinac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Felbinac is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08437</drugbank-id>
      <name>Puromycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Puromycin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08439</drugbank-id>
      <name>Parecoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Parecoxib is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08797</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salicylamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Salicylamide is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08940</drugbank-id>
      <name>Kebuzone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Kebuzone is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08942</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isoxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Isoxicam is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08951</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Indoprofen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08955</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibuproxam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ibuproxam is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08976</drugbank-id>
      <name>Floctafenine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Floctafenine is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08981</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenbufen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Fenbufen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08984</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etofenamate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Etofenamate is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08991</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epirizole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Epirizole is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09008</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefaloridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefaloridine is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09062</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefminox</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefminox is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09084</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benzydamine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Benzydamine is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09212</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loxoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Loxoprofen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexibuprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Dexibuprofen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09214</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexketoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Dexketoprofen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09215</drugbank-id>
      <name>Droxicam</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Droxicam is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09216</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolfenamic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tolfenamic acid is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09217</drugbank-id>
      <name>Firocoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Firocoxib is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clonixin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Clonixin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09285</drugbank-id>
      <name>Morniflumate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Morniflumate is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09295</drugbank-id>
      <name>Talniflumate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Talniflumate is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11367</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefroxadine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefroxadine is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11455</drugbank-id>
      <name>Robenacoxib</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Robenacoxib is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11466</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tepoxalin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tepoxalin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11512</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dihydrostreptomycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Dihydrostreptomycin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11518</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flunixin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Flunixin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11520</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hygromycin B</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Hygromycin B is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11935</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flomoxef</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Flomoxef is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12151</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brincidofovir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Brincidofovir is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12445</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitroaspirin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Nitroaspirin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12545</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indobufen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Indobufen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12604</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sisomicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Sisomicin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13001</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tinoridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tinoridine is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13167</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alclofenac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Alclofenac is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13217</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fentiazac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Fentiazac is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13232</drugbank-id>
      <name>Suxibuzone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Suxibuzone is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13266</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefatrizine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefatrizine is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13270</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dibekacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Dibekacin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13274</drugbank-id>
      <name>Micronomicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Micronomicin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13286</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bumadizone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Bumadizone is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13314</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alminoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Alminoprofen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flunoxaprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Flunoxaprofen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13364</drugbank-id>
      <name>Feprazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Feprazone is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13371</drugbank-id>
      <name>Difenpiramide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Difenpiramide is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13407</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nifenazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Nifenazone is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13432</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lonazolac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Lonazolac is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13461</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefcapene</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefcapene is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13470</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefodizime</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefodizime is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13481</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tenidap</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Tenidap is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13499</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefsulodin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefsulodin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13501</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bendazac</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Bendazac is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13504</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefetamet</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefetamet is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13514</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pranoprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Pranoprofen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13524</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propyphenazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Propyphenazone is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13527</drugbank-id>
      <name>Proglumetacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Proglumetacin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13538</drugbank-id>
      <name>Guacetisal</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Guacetisal is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13540</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isepamicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Isepamicin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13544</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethenzamide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ethenzamide is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13612</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbaspirin calcium</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Carbaspirin calcium is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13629</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mofebutazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Mofebutazone is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13638</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefbuperazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefbuperazone is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13649</drugbank-id>
      <name>Proquazone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Proquazone is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13657</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benorilate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Benorilate is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13667</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefozopran</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefozopran is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13673</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bekanamycin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Bekanamycin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13682</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefpirome</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefpirome is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13722</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pirprofen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Pirprofen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13778</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefazedone</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Cefazedone is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acemetacin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Acemetacin is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13821</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftezole</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Ceftezole is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13860</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imidazole salicylate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Imidazole salicylate is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13868</drugbank-id>
      <name>Adefovir</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Adefovir is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14059</drugbank-id>
      <name>SC-236</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when SC-236 is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14060</drugbank-id>
      <name>NS-398</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when NS-398 is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14713</drugbank-id>
      <name>Inotersen</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity can be increased when Inotersen is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00399</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zoledronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Givosiran is combined with Zoledronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00630</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alendronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Givosiran is combined with Alendronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00710</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibandronate</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Givosiran is combined with Ibandronate.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00720</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clodronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Givosiran is combined with Clodronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00884</drugbank-id>
      <name>Risedronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Givosiran is combined with Risedronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01077</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etidronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Givosiran is combined with Etidronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01133</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiludronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Givosiran is combined with Tiludronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06255</drugbank-id>
      <name>Incadronic acid</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of nephrotoxicity and hypocalcemia can be increased when Givosiran is combined with Incadronic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00007</drugbank-id>
      <name>Leuprolide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Leuprolide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00014</drugbank-id>
      <name>Goserelin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Goserelin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00017</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salmon Calcitonin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Salmon Calcitonin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00035</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desmopressin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Desmopressin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00041</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aldesleukin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Aldesleukin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00080</drugbank-id>
      <name>Daptomycin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Daptomycin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00081</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tositumomab</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Tositumomab which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00115</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyanocobalamin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Cyanocobalamin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00158</drugbank-id>
      <name>Folic acid</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Folic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00165</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pyridoxine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Pyridoxine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00186</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lorazepam</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Lorazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00190</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbidopa</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Carbidopa which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00196</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluconazole</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Fluconazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00198</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oseltamivir</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Oseltamivir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00200</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydroxocobalamin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Hydroxocobalamin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00206</drugbank-id>
      <name>Reserpine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Reserpine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pantoprazole</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Pantoprazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00225</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gadodiamide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Gadodiamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00230</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pregabalin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Pregabalin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00231</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temazepam</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Temazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00235</drugbank-id>
      <name>Milrinone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Milrinone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00237</drugbank-id>
      <name>Butabarbital</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Butabarbital which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00254</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxycycline</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Doxycycline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00270</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isradipine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Isradipine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00271</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diatrizoate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Diatrizoate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00273</drugbank-id>
      <name>Topiramate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Topiramate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00279</drugbank-id>
      <name>Liothyronine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Liothyronine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00284</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acarbose</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Acarbose which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00290</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bleomycin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Bleomycin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00292</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etomidate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Etomidate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00294</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etonogestrel</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Etonogestrel which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00303</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ertapenem</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ertapenem which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00308</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibutilide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ibutilide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00312</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentobarbital</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Pentobarbital which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00319</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piperacillin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Piperacillin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00322</drugbank-id>
      <name>Floxuridine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Floxuridine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00323</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolcapone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Tolcapone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00325</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitroprusside</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Nitroprusside which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00327</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydromorphone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Hydromorphone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00330</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethambutol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ethambutol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00331</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metformin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Metformin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00339</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pyrazinamide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Pyrazinamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00341</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cetirizine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Cetirizine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00349</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clobazam</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Clobazam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00351</drugbank-id>
      <name>Megestrol acetate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Megestrol acetate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00355</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aztreonam</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Aztreonam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00359</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfadiazine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Sulfadiazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00364</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sucralfate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Sucralfate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00372</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiethylperazine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Thiethylperazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00380</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexrazoxane</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Dexrazoxane which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00401</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nisoldipine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Nisoldipine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00402</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eszopiclone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Eszopiclone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00404</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alprazolam</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Alprazolam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00412</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rosiglitazone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Rosiglitazone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00413</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pramipexole</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Pramipexole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00415</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ampicillin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ampicillin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00418</drugbank-id>
      <name>Secobarbital</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Secobarbital which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00422</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylphenidate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Methylphenidate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00432</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trifluridine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Trifluridine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00435</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitric Oxide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Nitric Oxide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00437</drugbank-id>
      <name>Allopurinol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Allopurinol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00440</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimethoprim</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Trimethoprim which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00441</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemcitabine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Gemcitabine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00480</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lenalidomide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Lenalidomide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00492</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosinopril</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Fosinopril which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00501</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cimetidine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Cimetidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00524</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metolazone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Metolazone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00535</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cefdinir</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Cefdinir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00537</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ciprofloxacin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ciprofloxacin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00548</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azelaic acid</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Azelaic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00552</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentostatin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Pentostatin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00553</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methoxsalen</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Methoxsalen which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00555</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lamotrigine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Lamotrigine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00558</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zanamivir</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Zanamivir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00569</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fondaparinux</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Fondaparinux which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00583</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levocarnitine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Levocarnitine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00591</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluocinolone acetonide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Fluocinolone acetonide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00597</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gadoteridol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Gadoteridol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00603</drugbank-id>
      <name>Medroxyprogesterone acetate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Medroxyprogesterone acetate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00612</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bisoprolol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Bisoprolol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00624</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Testosterone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00628</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clorazepic acid</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Clorazepic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00631</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clofarabine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Clofarabine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00633</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexmedetomidine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Dexmedetomidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00635</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prednisone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Prednisone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00651</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dyphylline</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Dyphylline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00657</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mecamylamine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Mecamylamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00660</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metaxalone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Metaxalone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00665</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nilutamide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Nilutamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00669</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sumatriptan</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Sumatriptan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00672</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorpropamide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Chlorpropamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00683</drugbank-id>
      <name>Midazolam</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Midazolam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00688</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mycophenolate mofetil</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Mycophenolate mofetil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00690</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flurazepam</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Flurazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00692</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phentolamine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Phentolamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00698</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitrofurantoin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Nitrofurantoin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00709</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lamivudine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Lamivudine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00713</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxacillin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Oxacillin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00716</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nedocromil</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Nedocromil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00722</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lisinopril</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Lisinopril which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00733</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pralidoxime</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Pralidoxime which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00743</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gadobenic acid</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Gadobenic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00759</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetracycline</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Tetracycline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00760</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meropenem</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Meropenem which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00761</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium chloride</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Potassium chloride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00763</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methimazole</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Methimazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00775</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tirofiban</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Tirofiban which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00780</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenelzine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Phenelzine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00782</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propantheline</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Propantheline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00789</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gadopentetic acid</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Gadopentetic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00790</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perindopril</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Perindopril which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00800</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenoldopam</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Fenoldopam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00804</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dicyclomine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Dicyclomine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00808</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indapamide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Indapamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00811</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ribavirin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ribavirin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00820</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tadalafil</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Tadalafil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00828</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosfomycin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Fosfomycin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00829</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diazepam</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Diazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00839</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolazamide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Tolazamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00841</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dobutamine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Dobutamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00842</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxazepam</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Oxazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00853</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temozolomide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Temozolomide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00871</drugbank-id>
      <name>Terbutaline</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Terbutaline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00894</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testolactone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Testolactone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00897</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triazolam</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Triazolam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00900</drugbank-id>
      <name>Didanosine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Didanosine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00909</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zonisamide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Zonisamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00911</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tinidazole</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Tinidazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00915</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amantadine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Amantadine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00928</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azacitidine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Azacitidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00951</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isoniazid</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Isoniazid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00953</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rizatriptan</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Rizatriptan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00961</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mepivacaine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Mepivacaine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00962</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zaleplon</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Zaleplon which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00968</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methyldopa</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Methyldopa which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00988</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dopamine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Dopamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00995</drugbank-id>
      <name>Auranofin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Auranofin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01001</drugbank-id>
      <name>Salbutamol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Salbutamol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01004</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ganciclovir</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ganciclovir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01010</drugbank-id>
      <name>Edrophonium</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Edrophonium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01011</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metyrapone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Metyrapone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01015</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulfamethoxazole</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Sulfamethoxazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01018</drugbank-id>
      <name>Guanfacine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Guanfacine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01020</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isosorbide mononitrate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Isosorbide mononitrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01022</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phylloquinone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Phylloquinone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01024</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mycophenolic acid</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Mycophenolic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01030</drugbank-id>
      <name>Topotecan</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Topotecan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01032</drugbank-id>
      <name>Probenecid</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Probenecid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01039</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenofibrate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Fenofibrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01043</drugbank-id>
      <name>Memantine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Memantine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01046</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lubiprostone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Lubiprostone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01048</drugbank-id>
      <name>Abacavir</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Abacavir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01060</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amoxicillin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Amoxicillin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01067</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glipizide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Glipizide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01068</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clonazepam</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Clonazepam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01093</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dimethyl sulfoxide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Dimethyl sulfoxide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01099</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flucytosine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Flucytosine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01101</drugbank-id>
      <name>Capecitabine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Capecitabine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01105</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sibutramine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Sibutramine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01124</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolbutamide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Tolbutamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01129</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rabeprazole</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Rabeprazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01135</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxacurium</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Doxacurium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01137</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levofloxacin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Levofloxacin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01148</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flavoxate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Flavoxate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01156</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bupropion</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Bupropion which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01157</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimetrexate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Trimetrexate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01169</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arsenic trioxide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Arsenic trioxide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01170</drugbank-id>
      <name>Guanethidine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Guanethidine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01181</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ifosfamide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ifosfamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01183</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naloxone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Naloxone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01205</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flumazenil</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Flumazenil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fomepizole</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Fomepizole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01215</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estazolam</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Estazolam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01221</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketamine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ketamine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01222</drugbank-id>
      <name>Budesonide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Budesonide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01240</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epoprostenol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Epoprostenol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01241</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemfibrozil</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Gemfibrozil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01249</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iodixanol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Iodixanol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01261</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sitagliptin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Sitagliptin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01273</drugbank-id>
      <name>Varenicline</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Varenicline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01275</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydralazine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Hydralazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01394</drugbank-id>
      <name>Colchicine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Colchicine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01420</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone propionate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Testosterone propionate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01427</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amrinone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Amrinone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01428</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxybenzone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Oxybenzone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01431</drugbank-id>
      <name>Allylestrenol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Allylestrenol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01550</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenproporex</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Fenproporex which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01563</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chloral hydrate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Chloral hydrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01587</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ketazolam</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ketazolam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01610</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valganciclovir</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Valganciclovir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01638</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sorbitol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Sorbitol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01656</drugbank-id>
      <name>Roflumilast</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Roflumilast which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01685</drugbank-id>
      <name>Topiroxostat</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Topiroxostat which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04895</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pegaptanib</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Pegaptanib which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04896</drugbank-id>
      <name>Milnacipran</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Milnacipran which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04953</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ezogabine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ezogabine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05018</drugbank-id>
      <name>Migalastat</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Migalastat which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05541</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brivaracetam</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Brivaracetam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06154</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentaerythritol tetranitrate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Pentaerythritol tetranitrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06186</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ipilimumab</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ipilimumab which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06196</drugbank-id>
      <name>Icatibant</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Icatibant which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06209</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prasugrel</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Prasugrel which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06211</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doripenem</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Doripenem which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06228</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rivaroxaban</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Rivaroxaban which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06230</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nalmefene</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Nalmefene which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06262</drugbank-id>
      <name>Droxidopa</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Droxidopa which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06282</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levocetirizine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Levocetirizine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06335</drugbank-id>
      <name>Saxagliptin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Saxagliptin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06402</drugbank-id>
      <name>Telavancin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Telavancin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06480</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prucalopride</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Prucalopride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06623</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flupirtine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Flupirtine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06637</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dalfampridine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Dalfampridine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06695</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dabigatran etexilate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Dabigatran etexilate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06700</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desvenlafaxine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Desvenlafaxine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06705</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gadofosveset trisodium</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Gadofosveset trisodium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06710</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methyltestosterone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Methyltestosterone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06767</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ammonium chloride</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ammonium chloride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06782</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dimercaprol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Dimercaprol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06796</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mangafodipir</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Mangafodipir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06800</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylnaltrexone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Methylnaltrexone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06809</drugbank-id>
      <name>Plerixafor</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Plerixafor which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06813</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pralatrexate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Pralatrexate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06815</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pyrithione</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Pyrithione which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06823</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiopronin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Tiopronin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06824</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triethylenetetramine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Triethylenetetramine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08824</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ioflupane I-123</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ioflupane I-123 which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08826</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deferiprone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Deferiprone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08840</drugbank-id>
      <name>N-methylnicotinamide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of N-methylnicotinamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08872</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gabapentin enacarbil</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Gabapentin enacarbil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08877</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ruxolitinib</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ruxolitinib which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08894</drugbank-id>
      <name>Peginesatide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Peginesatide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08897</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aclidinium</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Aclidinium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08899</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enzalutamide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Enzalutamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08900</drugbank-id>
      <name>Teduglutide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Teduglutide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08904</drugbank-id>
      <name>Certolizumab pegol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Certolizumab pegol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08905</drugbank-id>
      <name>Formestane</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Formestane which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08907</drugbank-id>
      <name>Canagliflozin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Canagliflozin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08909</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glycerol phenylbutyrate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Glycerol phenylbutyrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08911</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trametinib</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Trametinib which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08932</drugbank-id>
      <name>Macitentan</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Macitentan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08934</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sofosbuvir</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Sofosbuvir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08964</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemeprost</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Gemeprost which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09027</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ledipasvir</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ledipasvir which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09038</drugbank-id>
      <name>Empagliflozin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Empagliflozin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09050</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftolozane</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ceftolozane which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09066</drugbank-id>
      <name>Corifollitropin alfa</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Corifollitropin alfa which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09075</drugbank-id>
      <name>Edoxaban</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Edoxaban which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09081</drugbank-id>
      <name>Idebenone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Idebenone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09082</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vilanterol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Vilanterol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09089</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimebutine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Trimebutine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09091</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tixocortol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Tixocortol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09103</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ancestim</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ancestim which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09104</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium hydroxide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Magnesium hydroxide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09106</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydroxyethyl Starch</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Hydroxyethyl Starch which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09111</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentastarch</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Pentastarch which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09121</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aurothioglucose</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Aurothioglucose which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09123</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dienogest</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Dienogest which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09129</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromic chloride</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Chromic chloride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09132</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gadoteric acid</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Gadoteric acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09133</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iothalamic acid</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Iothalamic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09134</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ioversol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ioversol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09135</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ioxilan</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Ioxilan which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09136</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isosulfan blue</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Isosulfan blue which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09137</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m mebrofenin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Technetium Tc-99m mebrofenin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09139</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m oxidronate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Technetium Tc-99m oxidronate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09148</drugbank-id>
      <name>Florbetaben (18F)</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Florbetaben (18F) which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09149</drugbank-id>
      <name>Florbetapir (18F)</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Florbetapir (18F) which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09156</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iopromide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Iopromide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09163</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m exametazime</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Technetium Tc-99m exametazime which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09164</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m disofenin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Technetium Tc-99m disofenin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09165</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m pyrophosphate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Technetium Tc-99m pyrophosphate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09185</drugbank-id>
      <name>Viloxazine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Viloxazine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09194</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etoperidone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Etoperidone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09205</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moxisylyte</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Moxisylyte which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09209</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pholcodine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Pholcodine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09210</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piracetam</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Piracetam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09219</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bisoxatin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Bisoxatin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09220</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nicorandil</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Nicorandil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09223</drugbank-id>
      <name>Blonanserin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Blonanserin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09224</drugbank-id>
      <name>Melperone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Melperone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09241</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylene blue</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Methylene blue which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09244</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pirlindole</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Pirlindole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09245</drugbank-id>
      <name>Toloxatone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Toloxatone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09255</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dextran</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Dextran which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09257</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gimeracil</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Gimeracil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09262</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imidafenacin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Imidafenacin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Idarucizumab</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Idarucizumab which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09265</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lixisenatide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Lixisenatide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09268</drugbank-id>
      <name>Picosulfuric acid</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Picosulfuric acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09276</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium aurothiomalate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Sodium aurothiomalate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09277</drugbank-id>
      <name>Choline C 11</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Choline C 11 which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09281</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium trisilicate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Magnesium trisilicate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09292</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sacubitril</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Sacubitril which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09301</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chondroitin sulfate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Chondroitin sulfate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens, A</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens, A which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09318</drugbank-id>
      <name>Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens, B</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens, B which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09320</drugbank-id>
      <name>Procaine benzylpenicillin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Procaine benzylpenicillin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09324</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulbactam</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Sulbactam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09325</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium fluoride</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Sodium fluoride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09329</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antihemophilic Factor (Recombinant), PEGylated</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Antihemophilic Factor (Recombinant), PEGylated which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09338</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mersalyl</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Mersalyl which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09344</drugbank-id>
      <name>Invert sugar</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Invert sugar which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09357</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexpanthenol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Dexpanthenol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09394</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phosphoric acid</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Phosphoric acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09395</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium acetate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Sodium acetate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09407</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium chloride</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Magnesium chloride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09418</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium perchlorate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Potassium perchlorate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09472</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium sulfate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Sodium sulfate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09477</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enalaprilat</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Enalaprilat which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09481</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium carbonate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Magnesium carbonate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09488</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acrivastine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Acrivastine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09496</drugbank-id>
      <name>Octinoxate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Octinoxate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09502</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fludeoxyglucose (18F)</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Fludeoxyglucose (18F) which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09546</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iobenguane sulfate I-123</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Iobenguane sulfate I-123 which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11077</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polyethylene glycol 400</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Polyethylene glycol 400 which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11085</drugbank-id>
      <name>Resorcinol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Resorcinol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11090</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium nitrate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Potassium nitrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11098</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium bicarbonate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Potassium bicarbonate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11102</drugbank-id>
      <name>N-acetyltyrosine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of N-acetyltyrosine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11114</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eucalyptus oil</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Eucalyptus oil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11121</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chloroxylenol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Chloroxylenol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11127</drugbank-id>
      <name>Selenious acid</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Selenious acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11135</drugbank-id>
      <name>Selenium</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Selenium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11136</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromium</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Chromium which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11145</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxyquinoline</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Oxyquinoline which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11156</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pyrantel</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Pyrantel which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11164</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bicisate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Bicisate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11251</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tocopherol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Tocopherol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11278</drugbank-id>
      <name>DL-Methylephedrine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of DL-Methylephedrine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11328</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetradecyl hydrogen sulfate (ester)</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Tetradecyl hydrogen sulfate (ester) which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11338</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clove oil</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Clove oil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11358</drugbank-id>
      <name>Evening primrose oil</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Evening primrose oil which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11364</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pidotimod</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Pidotimod which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11560</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lesinurad</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Lesinurad which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11577</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indigotindisulfonic acid</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Indigotindisulfonic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11587</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etafedrine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Etafedrine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11598</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antithrombin III human</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Antithrombin III human which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11691</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naldemedine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Naldemedine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11699</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tropisetron</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Tropisetron which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Baricitinib</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Baricitinib which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11901</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apalutamide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Apalutamide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11943</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delafloxacin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Delafloxacin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11989</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benznidazole</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Benznidazole which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12007</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isoflavone</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Isoflavone which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12107</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vaborbactam</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Vaborbactam which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12278</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propiverine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Propiverine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benserazide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Benserazide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13025</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiapride</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Tiapride which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13139</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levosalbutamol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Levosalbutamol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13145</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nedaplatin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Nedaplatin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13156</drugbank-id>
      <name>Inosine pranobex</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Inosine pranobex which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13178</drugbank-id>
      <name>Inositol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Inositol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13185</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxabolone cipionate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Oxabolone cipionate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13191</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phosphocreatine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Phosphocreatine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13269</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dichlorobenzyl alcohol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Dichlorobenzyl alcohol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Almasilate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Almasilate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13873</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenofibric acid</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Fenofibric acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13884</drugbank-id>
      <name>Albutrepenonacog alfa</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Albutrepenonacog alfa which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13909</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bismuth subgallate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Bismuth subgallate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13943</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone cypionate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Testosterone cypionate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13944</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone enanthate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Testosterone enanthate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13946</drugbank-id>
      <name>Testosterone undecanoate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Testosterone undecanoate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13967</drugbank-id>
      <name>Patent Blue</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Patent Blue which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14006</drugbank-id>
      <name>Choline salicylate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Choline salicylate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14007</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentetic acid</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Pentetic acid which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14184</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cinnamaldehyde</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Cinnamaldehyde which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14186</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cinnamyl alcohol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Cinnamyl alcohol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14498</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium acetate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Potassium acetate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14499</drugbank-id>
      <name>Potassium sulfate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Potassium sulfate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14526</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromic citrate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Chromic citrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14527</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromic nitrate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Chromic nitrate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14528</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromium gluconate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Chromium gluconate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14529</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromium nicotinate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Chromium nicotinate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14530</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chromous sulfate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Chromous sulfate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14754</drugbank-id>
      <name>Solriamfetol</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Solriamfetol which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15593</drugbank-id>
      <name>Golodirsen</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Golodirsen which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00314</drugbank-id>
      <name>Capreomycin</name>
      <description>Capreomycin may decrease the excretion rate of Givosiran which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00512</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vancomycin</name>
      <description>Vancomycin may decrease the excretion rate of Givosiran which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00515</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cisplatin</name>
      <description>Cisplatin may decrease the excretion rate of Givosiran which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01356</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium cation</name>
      <description>Lithium cation may decrease the excretion rate of Givosiran which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12615</drugbank-id>
      <name>Plazomicin</name>
      <description>Plazomicin may decrease the excretion rate of Givosiran which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14507</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium citrate</name>
      <description>Lithium citrate may decrease the excretion rate of Givosiran which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14509</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium carbonate</name>
      <description>Lithium carbonate may decrease the excretion rate of Givosiran which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00390</drugbank-id>
      <name>Digoxin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Digoxin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00813</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fentanyl</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Fentanyl which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00879</drugbank-id>
      <name>Emtricitabine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Emtricitabine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00982</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isotretinoin</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Isotretinoin which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08996</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dimetacrine</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Dimetacrine which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14506</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium hydroxide</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Lithium hydroxide which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14508</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lithium succinate</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Lithium succinate which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00781</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polymyxin B</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Givosiran is combined with Polymyxin B.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00181</drugbank-id>
      <name>Baclofen</name>
      <description>Givosiran may decrease the excretion rate of Baclofen which could result in a higher serum level.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12978</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pexidartinib</name>
      <description>Givosiran may increase the hepatotoxic activities of Pexidartinib.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00176</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluvoxamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Fluvoxamine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00184</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nicotine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Nicotine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00188</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bortezomib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Bortezomib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00195</drugbank-id>
      <name>Betaxolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Betaxolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00201</drugbank-id>
      <name>Caffeine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Caffeine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00246</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ziprasidone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ziprasidone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00261</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anagrelide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Anagrelide can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00262</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carmustine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Carmustine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00268</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ropinirole</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ropinirole can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00277</drugbank-id>
      <name>Theophylline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Theophylline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00280</drugbank-id>
      <name>Disopyramide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Disopyramide can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00281</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lidocaine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Lidocaine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00286</drugbank-id>
      <name>Conjugated estrogens</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Conjugated estrogens can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00296</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ropivacaine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ropivacaine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00299</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penciclovir</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Penciclovir can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00315</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zolmitriptan</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Zolmitriptan can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00316</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetaminophen</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Acetaminophen can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00321</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amitriptyline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amitriptyline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00334</drugbank-id>
      <name>Olanzapine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Olanzapine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00356</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorzoxazone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Chlorzoxazone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00363</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clozapine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Clozapine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00365</drugbank-id>
      <name>Grepafloxacin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Grepafloxacin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00370</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mirtazapine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Mirtazapine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00379</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mexiletine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Mexiletine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00382</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tacrine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tacrine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00384</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triamterene</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Triamterene can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00398</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sorafenib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Sorafenib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00420</drugbank-id>
      <name>Promazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Promazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00425</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zolpidem</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Zolpidem can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00442</drugbank-id>
      <name>Entecavir</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Entecavir can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00458</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imipramine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Imipramine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00461</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nabumetone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Nabumetone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00468</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Quinine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00472</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluoxetine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Fluoxetine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00476</drugbank-id>
      <name>Duloxetine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Duloxetine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00477</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorpromazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Chlorpromazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00499</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flutamide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Flutamide can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00502</drugbank-id>
      <name>Haloperidol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Haloperidol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00518</drugbank-id>
      <name>Albendazole</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Albendazole can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00530</drugbank-id>
      <name>Erlotinib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Erlotinib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00532</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mephenytoin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Mephenytoin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00533</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rofecoxib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Rofecoxib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00540</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nortriptyline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Nortriptyline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00544</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluorouracil</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Fluorouracil can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00564</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbamazepine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Carbamazepine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00568</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cinnarizine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Cinnarizine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00571</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propranolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Propranolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00575</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clonidine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Clonidine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00586</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diclofenac</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Diclofenac can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00619</drugbank-id>
      <name>Imatinib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Imatinib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00625</drugbank-id>
      <name>Efavirenz</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Efavirenz can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00629</drugbank-id>
      <name>Guanabenz</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Guanabenz can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00642</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pemetrexed</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Pemetrexed can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00655</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estrone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Estrone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00661</drugbank-id>
      <name>Verapamil</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Verapamil can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00675</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tamoxifen</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tamoxifen can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00682</drugbank-id>
      <name>Warfarin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Warfarin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00697</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tizanidine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tizanidine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00715</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paroxetine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Paroxetine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00730</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiabendazole</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Thiabendazole can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00740</drugbank-id>
      <name>Riluzole</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Riluzole can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00744</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zileuton</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Zileuton can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00758</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clopidogrel</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Clopidogrel can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00773</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etoposide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Etoposide can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Estradiol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00787</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acyclovir</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Acyclovir can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00788</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naproxen</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Naproxen can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00806</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentoxifylline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Pentoxifylline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00831</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trifluoperazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Trifluoperazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00850</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perphenazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Perphenazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00851</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dacarbazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Dacarbazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00857</drugbank-id>
      <name>Terbinafine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Terbinafine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00863</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ranitidine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ranitidine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00898</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethanol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ethanol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00924</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyclobenzaprine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Cyclobenzaprine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00934</drugbank-id>
      <name>Maprotiline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Maprotiline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00969</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alosetron</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Alosetron can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00972</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azelastine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Azelastine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00978</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lomefloxacin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Lomefloxacin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00980</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ramelteon</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ramelteon can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00993</drugbank-id>
      <name>Azathioprine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Azathioprine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00998</drugbank-id>
      <name>Frovatriptan</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Frovatriptan can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01002</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levobupivacaine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Levobupivacaine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01012</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cinacalcet</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Cinacalcet can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01037</drugbank-id>
      <name>Selegiline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Selegiline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01056</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tocainide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tocainide can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01058</drugbank-id>
      <name>Praziquantel</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Praziquantel can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01065</drugbank-id>
      <name>Melatonin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Melatonin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01087</drugbank-id>
      <name>Primaquine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Primaquine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01094</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hesperetin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Hesperetin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01097</drugbank-id>
      <name>Leflunomide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Leflunomide can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01100</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pimozide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Pimozide can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01115</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nifedipine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Nifedipine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01118</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amiodarone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amiodarone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01136</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carvedilol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Carvedilol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01142</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxepin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Doxepin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01151</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desipramine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Desipramine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01166</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cilostazol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Cilostazol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01182</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propafenone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Propafenone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01184</drugbank-id>
      <name>Domperidone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Domperidone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01191</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexfenfluramine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Dexfenfluramine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01195</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flecainide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Flecainide can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01223</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aminophylline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Aminophylline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01233</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metoclopramide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Metoclopramide can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01242</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clomipramine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Clomipramine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01254</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dasatinib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Dasatinib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01303</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxtriphylline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Oxtriphylline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01367</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rasagiline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Rasagiline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01405</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temafloxacin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Temafloxacin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01412</drugbank-id>
      <name>Theobromine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Theobromine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01418</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acenocoumarol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Acenocoumarol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01424</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aminophenazone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Aminophenazone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01435</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antipyrine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Antipyrine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01482</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fenethylline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Fenethylline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01558</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bromazepam</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Bromazepam can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01623</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiothixene</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Thiothixene can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01628</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etoricoxib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Etoricoxib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01645</drugbank-id>
      <name>Genistein</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Genistein can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01667</drugbank-id>
      <name>8-azaguanine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of 8-azaguanine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02134</drugbank-id>
      <name>Xanthine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Xanthine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02489</drugbank-id>
      <name>9-Methylguanine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of 9-Methylguanine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02568</drugbank-id>
      <name>Peldesine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Peldesine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02709</drugbank-id>
      <name>Resveratrol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Resveratrol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenacetin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Phenacetin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04076</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hypoxanthine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Hypoxanthine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04356</drugbank-id>
      <name>9-Deazaguanine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of 9-Deazaguanine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04574</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estrone sulfate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Estrone sulfate can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04841</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flunarizine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Flunarizine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04871</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lorcaserin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Lorcaserin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04889</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bicifadine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Bicifadine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04948</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lofexidine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Lofexidine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04951</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pirfenidone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Pirfenidone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05676</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apremilast</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Apremilast can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05708</drugbank-id>
      <name>GTS-21</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of GTS-21 can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06148</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mianserin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Mianserin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06210</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eltrombopag</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Eltrombopag can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06216</drugbank-id>
      <name>Asenapine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Asenapine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06235</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vadimezan</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Vadimezan can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06292</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dapagliflozin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Dapagliflozin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06479</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propentofylline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Propentofylline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06589</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pazopanib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Pazopanib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06594</drugbank-id>
      <name>Agomelatine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Agomelatine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06626</drugbank-id>
      <name>Axitinib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Axitinib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06769</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bendamustine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Bendamustine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06770</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benzyl alcohol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Benzyl alcohol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06774</drugbank-id>
      <name>Capsaicin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Capsaicin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08496</drugbank-id>
      <name>(R)-warfarin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of (R)-warfarin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08883</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perampanel</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Perampanel can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08910</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pomalidomide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Pomalidomide can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09071</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tasimelteon</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tasimelteon can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09118</drugbank-id>
      <name>Stiripentol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Stiripentol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09225</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zotepine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Zotepine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09256</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tegafur</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tegafur can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09273</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxofylline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Doxofylline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09288</drugbank-id>
      <name>Propacetamol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Propacetamol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09290</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ramosetron</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ramosetron can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11757</drugbank-id>
      <name>Istradefylline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Istradefylline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11919</drugbank-id>
      <name>6-O-benzylguanine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of 6-O-benzylguanine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11967</drugbank-id>
      <name>Binimetinib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Binimetinib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12026</drugbank-id>
      <name>Voxilaprevir</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Voxilaprevir can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12245</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triclabendazole</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Triclabendazole can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12332</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rucaparib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Rucaparib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12406</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lisofylline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Lisofylline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12531</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lobucavir</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Lobucavir can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12926</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cafedrine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Cafedrine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12927</drugbank-id>
      <name>Theodrenaline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Theodrenaline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12945</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dihydralazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Dihydralazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13203</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bamifylline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Bamifylline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13449</drugbank-id>
      <name>Proxyphylline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Proxyphylline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13573</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acefylline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Acefylline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13592</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etamiphylline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Etamiphylline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13634</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentifylline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Pentifylline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13812</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bufylline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Bufylline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13874</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enasidenib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Enasidenib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13952</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol acetate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Estradiol acetate can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13953</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol benzoate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Estradiol benzoate can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13954</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol cypionate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Estradiol cypionate can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13955</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol dienanthate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Estradiol dienanthate can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13956</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol valerate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Estradiol valerate can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14018</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bromotheophylline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Bromotheophylline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14132</drugbank-id>
      <name>8-chlorotheophylline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of 8-chlorotheophylline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00182</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amphetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amphetamine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00185</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cevimeline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Cevimeline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00187</drugbank-id>
      <name>Esmolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Esmolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00193</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tramadol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tramadol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00203</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sildenafil</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Sildenafil can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ticlopidine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ticlopidine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00215</drugbank-id>
      <name>Citalopram</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Citalopram can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00216</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eletriptan</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Eletriptan can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00238</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nevirapine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Nevirapine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00243</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ranolazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ranolazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00245</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benzatropine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Benzatropine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metoprolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Metoprolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00285</drugbank-id>
      <name>Venlafaxine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Venlafaxine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00289</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atomoxetine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Atomoxetine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00297</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bupivacaine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Bupivacaine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gefitinib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Gefitinib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00318</drugbank-id>
      <name>Codeine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Codeine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00333</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methadone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Methadone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00335</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atenolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Atenolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00342</drugbank-id>
      <name>Terfenadine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Terfenadine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00343</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diltiazem</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Diltiazem can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00344</drugbank-id>
      <name>Protriptyline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Protriptyline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00373</drugbank-id>
      <name>Timolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Timolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00377</drugbank-id>
      <name>Palonosetron</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Palonosetron can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00396</drugbank-id>
      <name>Progesterone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Progesterone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00409</drugbank-id>
      <name>Remoxipride</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Remoxipride can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00433</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prochlorperazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Prochlorperazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00454</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meperidine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Meperidine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00482</drugbank-id>
      <name>Celecoxib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Celecoxib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00489</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sotalol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Sotalol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00490</drugbank-id>
      <name>Buspirone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Buspirone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00496</drugbank-id>
      <name>Darifenacin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Darifenacin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00497</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxycodone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Oxycodone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00503</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ritonavir</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ritonavir can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00514</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dextromethorphan</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Dextromethorphan can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00521</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carteolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Carteolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00543</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amoxapine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amoxapine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00589</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lisuride</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Lisuride can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00590</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doxazosin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Doxazosin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00592</drugbank-id>
      <name>Piperazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Piperazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00598</drugbank-id>
      <name>Labetalol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Labetalol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00608</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chloroquine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Chloroquine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00637</drugbank-id>
      <name>Astemizole</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Astemizole can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00641</drugbank-id>
      <name>Simvastatin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Simvastatin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00647</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dextropropoxyphene</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Dextropropoxyphene can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00656</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trazodone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Trazodone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00674</drugbank-id>
      <name>Galantamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Galantamine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00679</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thioridazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Thioridazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00699</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nicergoline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Nicergoline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00701</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amprenavir</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Amprenavir can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00705</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delavirdine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Delavirdine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00706</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tamsulosin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tamsulosin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00726</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimipramine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Trimipramine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00731</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nateglinide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Nateglinide can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00734</drugbank-id>
      <name>Risperidone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Risperidone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00737</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meclizine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Meclizine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00738</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentamidine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Pentamidine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00751</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epinastine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Epinastine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00757</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dolasetron</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Dolasetron can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00805</drugbank-id>
      <name>Minaprine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Minaprine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00836</drugbank-id>
      <name>Loperamide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Loperamide can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00843</drugbank-id>
      <name>Donepezil</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Donepezil can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00866</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alprenolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Alprenolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00904</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ondansetron</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ondansetron can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00908</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinidine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Quinidine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00914</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenformin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Phenformin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00918</drugbank-id>
      <name>Almotriptan</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Almotriptan can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00921</drugbank-id>
      <name>Buprenorphine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Buprenorphine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00932</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tipranavir</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tipranavir can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00933</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mesoridazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Mesoridazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00956</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hydrocodone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Hydrocodone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00960</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pindolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Pindolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00964</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apraclonidine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Apraclonidine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00983</drugbank-id>
      <name>Formoterol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Formoterol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01028</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methoxyflurane</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Methoxyflurane can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01035</drugbank-id>
      <name>Procainamide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Procainamide can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01036</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tolterodine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tolterodine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01069</drugbank-id>
      <name>Promethazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Promethazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01071</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mequitazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Mequitazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01074</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perhexiline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Perhexiline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01075</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diphenhydramine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Diphenhydramine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01079</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tegaserod</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tegaserod can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01095</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fluvastatin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Fluvastatin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01104</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sertraline</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Sertraline can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01114</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorpheniramine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Chlorpheniramine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01149</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nefazodone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Nefazodone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01171</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moclobemide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Moclobemide can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01175</drugbank-id>
      <name>Escitalopram</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Escitalopram can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01177</drugbank-id>
      <name>Idarubicin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Idarubicin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01192</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxymorphone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Oxymorphone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01193</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acebutolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Acebutolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01203</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nadolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Nadolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01210</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levobunolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Levobunolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01214</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metipranolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Metipranolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01224</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quetiapine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Quetiapine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01228</drugbank-id>
      <name>Encainide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Encainide can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01238</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aripiprazole</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Aripiprazole can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01244</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bepridil</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Bepridil can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01255</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lisdexamfetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Lisdexamfetamine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01267</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paliperidone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Paliperidone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01274</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arformoterol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Arformoterol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01295</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bevantolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Bevantolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01297</drugbank-id>
      <name>Practolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Practolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01359</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penbutolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Penbutolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01392</drugbank-id>
      <name>Yohimbine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Yohimbine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01403</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methotrimeprazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Methotrimeprazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01409</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiotropium</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tiotropium can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01410</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ciclesonide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ciclesonide can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01429</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aprindine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Aprindine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01454</drugbank-id>
      <name>Midomafetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Midomafetamine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01466</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethylmorphine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ethylmorphine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01472</drugbank-id>
      <name>4-Methoxyamphetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of 4-Methoxyamphetamine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01551</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dihydrocodeine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Dihydrocodeine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01576</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dextroamphetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Dextroamphetamine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01577</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metamfetamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Metamfetamine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01580</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxprenolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Oxprenolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01591</drugbank-id>
      <name>Solifenacin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Solifenacin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01621</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pipotiazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Pipotiazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01624</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zuclopenthixol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Zuclopenthixol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02703</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fusidic acid</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Fusidic acid can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04829</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lysergic acid diethylamide</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Lysergic acid diethylamide can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04840</drugbank-id>
      <name>Debrisoquine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Debrisoquine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04844</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetrabenazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tetrabenazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04846</drugbank-id>
      <name>Celiprolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Celiprolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04861</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nebivolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Nebivolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04884</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dapoxetine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Dapoxetine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04905</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tesmilifene</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tesmilifene can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04920</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clevidipine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Clevidipine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04946</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iloperidone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Iloperidone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05109</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trabectedin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Trabectedin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05271</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rotigotine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Rotigotine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06016</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cariprazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Cariprazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06144</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sertindole</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Sertindole can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06203</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alogliptin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Alogliptin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06204</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tapentadol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tapentadol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06217</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vernakalant</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Vernakalant can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06506</drugbank-id>
      <name>Repinotan</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Repinotan can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06608</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tafenoquine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tafenoquine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06678</drugbank-id>
      <name>Esmirtazapine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Esmirtazapine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06684</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vilazodone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Vilazodone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06702</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fesoterodine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Fesoterodine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06726</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bufuralol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Bufuralol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06727</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sparteine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Sparteine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06735</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enclomiphene</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Enclomiphene can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08807</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bopindolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Bopindolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08808</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bupranolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Bupranolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08893</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mirabegron</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Mirabegron can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08901</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ponatinib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ponatinib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08918</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levomilnacipran</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Levomilnacipran can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08922</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perospirone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Perospirone can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08952</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indenolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Indenolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09013</drugbank-id>
      <name>Befunolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Befunolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09039</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eliglustat</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Eliglustat can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09048</drugbank-id>
      <name>Netupitant</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Netupitant can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09053</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibrutinib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ibrutinib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09068</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vortioxetine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Vortioxetine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09076</drugbank-id>
      <name>Umeclidinium</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Umeclidinium can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09128</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brexpiprazole</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Brexpiprazole can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09167</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dosulepin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Dosulepin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09173</drugbank-id>
      <name>Butyrfentanyl</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Butyrfentanyl can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09183</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dasabuvir</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Dasabuvir can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09195</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lorpiprazole</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Lorpiprazole can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09204</drugbank-id>
      <name>Arotinolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Arotinolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09351</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levobetaxolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Levobetaxolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09555</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexchlorpheniramine maleate</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Dexchlorpheniramine maleate can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09570</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ixazomib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ixazomib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11130</drugbank-id>
      <name>Opium</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Opium can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11586</drugbank-id>
      <name>Asunaprevir</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Asunaprevir can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11614</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rupatadine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Rupatadine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11642</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pitolisant</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Pitolisant can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11718</drugbank-id>
      <name>Encorafenib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Encorafenib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11770</drugbank-id>
      <name>Talinolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Talinolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11785</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anisodamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Anisodamine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11855</drugbank-id>
      <name>Revefenacin</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Revefenacin can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11915</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valbenazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Valbenazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11963</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dacomitinib</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Dacomitinib can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11979</drugbank-id>
      <name>Elagolix</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Elagolix can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12070</drugbank-id>
      <name>Letermovir</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Letermovir can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12161</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deutetrabenazine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Deutetrabenazine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12212</drugbank-id>
      <name>Landiolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Landiolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12752</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bucindolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Bucindolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12930</drugbank-id>
      <name>Opipramol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Opipramol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13293</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ipecac</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ipecac can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13443</drugbank-id>
      <name>Esatenolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Esatenolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13508</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cloranolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Cloranolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13530</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mepindolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Mepindolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13679</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dexchlorpheniramine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Dexchlorpheniramine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13757</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epanolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Epanolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13775</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tertatolol</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Tertatolol can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14010</drugbank-id>
      <name>5-methoxy-N,N-dimethyltryptamine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of 5-methoxy-N,N-dimethyltryptamine can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14185</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aripiprazole lauroxil</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Aripiprazole lauroxil can be increased when it is combined with Givosiran.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Weight</kind>
      <value>16300.0</value>
      <source/>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Formula</kind>
      <value>C524 H694 F16 N173 O316 P43 S6</value>
      <source/>
    </property>
  </experimental-properties>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Wikipedia</resource>
      <identifier>Givosiran</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets>
    <target position="1">
      <id>BE0009790</id>
      <name>ALAS1 mRNA</name>
      <organism>Humans</organism>
      <actions>
        <action>cleavage</action>
      </actions>
      <references>
        <articles/>
        <textbooks/>
        <links>
          <link>
            <ref-id>L10202</ref-id>
            <title>FDA Approved Drug Products: Givlaari subcutaneous injection</title>
            <url>https://www.accessdata.fda.gov/drugsatfda_docs/label/2019/0212194s000lbl.pdf</url>
          </link>
        </links>
        <attachments>
          <attachment>
            <ref-id>F4727</ref-id>
            <title>Study Protocol for Phase 1 trial of an RNA interference therapy for acute intermittent porphyria</title>
            <url>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/cite_this/attachments/files/000/004/727/original/protocol_for_phase_1_trial.pdf?1574375964</url>
          </attachment>
        </attachments>
      </references>
      <known-action>yes</known-action>
    </target>
  </targets>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>