<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2018-12-21" updated="2019-11-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB14730</drugbank-id>
  <name>Calaspargase pegol</name>
  <description>Asparaginase is an important agent used to treat acute lymphoblastic leukemia (ALL) [A40270].  Asparagine is incorporated into most proteins, and the synthesis of proteins is stopped when asparagine is absent, which inhibits RNA and DNA synthesis, resulting in a halt in cellular proliferation.  This forms the basis of asparaginase treatment in ALL [A40270], [A40273], [F2432].&#13;
&#13;
Calaspargase pegol, also known as _asparlas_, is an asparagine specific enzyme which is indicated as a part of a multi-agent chemotherapy regimen for the treatment of ALL [L4890]. The asparagine specific enzyme is derived from Escherichia coli, as a conjugate of L-asparaginase (L-asparagine amidohydrolase) and monomethoxypolyethylene glycol (mPEG) with a succinimidyl carbonate (SC) linker to create a stable molecule which increases the half-life and decreases the dosing frequency [FDA label], [A40270].&#13;
&#13;
Calaspargase pegol, by _Shire_ pharmaceuticals,  was approved by the FDA on December 20, 2018 for acute lymphoblastic anemia (ALL) [L4890].</description>
  <cas-number>941577-06-6</cas-number>
  <unii>T9FVH03HMZ</unii>
  <state>liquid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A40270</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25348002</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Angiolillo AL, Schore RJ, Devidas M, Borowitz MJ, Carroll AJ, Gastier-Foster JM, Heerema NA, Keilani T, Lane AR, Loh ML, Reaman GH, Adamson PC, Wood B, Wood C, Zheng HW, Raetz EA, Winick NJ, Carroll WL, Hunger SP: Pharmacokinetic and pharmacodynamic properties of calaspargase pegol Escherichia coli L-asparaginase in the treatment of patients with acute lymphoblastic leukemia: results from Children's Oncology Group Study AALL07P4. J Clin Oncol. 2014 Dec 1;32(34):3874-82. doi: 10.1200/JCO.2014.55.5763. Epub 2014 Oct 27.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A40273</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>18580955</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Appel IM, Kazemier KM, Boos J, Lanvers C, Huijmans J, Veerman AJ, van Wering E, den Boer ML, Pieters R: Pharmacokinetic, pharmacodynamic and intracellular effects of PEG-asparaginase in newly diagnosed childhood acute lymphoblastic leukemia: results from a single agent window study. Leukemia. 2008 Sep;22(9):1665-79. doi: 10.1038/leu.2008.165. Epub 2008 Jun 26.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L4890</ref-id>
        <title>Asparlas Approval History</title>
        <url>https://www.drugs.com/history/asparlas.html</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L4891</ref-id>
        <title>NCI: Calaspargase Pegol</title>
        <url>https://www.cancer.gov/publications/dictionaries/cancer-drug/def/calaspargase-pegol</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L4892</ref-id>
        <title>Blood Journal: Randomized Study of Pegaspargase (SS-PEG) and Calaspargase Pegol (SPC-PEG) in Pediatric Patients with Newly Diagnosed Acute Lymphoblastic Leukemia or Lymphoblastic Lymphoma: Results of DFCI ALL Consortium Protocol 11-001</title>
        <url>http://www.bloodjournal.org/content/128/22/175?sso-checked=true</url>
      </link>
    </links>
    <attachments>
      <attachment>
        <ref-id>F2432</ref-id>
        <title>Medsafe NZ: Erwinaze inj</title>
        <url>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/cite_this/attachments/files/000/002/432/original/Erwinaseinjm_Medsafe_NZ.pdf?1545430492</url>
      </attachment>
    </attachments>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>This drug is is an asparagine specific enzyme indicated as a component of a multi-agent chemotherapeutic regimen for the treatment of acute lymphoblastic leukemia in pediatric and young adult patients age 1 month to 21 years [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
The pharmacokinetics of calaspargase pegol were examined when given in combination with multiagent chemotherapy in 124 patients with B-cell lineage ALL [L4890]. The FDA approval of this drug was based on the achievement and maintenance of nadir serum asparaginase activity above the level of 0.1 U/mL when administering calaspargase, 2500 U/m2 intravenously, at 3-week intervals. </indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>The effect of this drug is believed to occur by selective killing of leukemic cells due to depletion of plasma L-asparagine. Leukemic cells with low expression of asparagine synthetase are less capable of producing L-asparagine, and therefore rely on exogenous L-asparagine for survival [FDA label].  When asparagine is depleted, tumor cells cannot proliferate [F2432].&#13;
&#13;
During remission induction, one dose of SC-PEG (2500 IU/m2) results in a sustained therapeutic serum asparaginase activity (SAA) without excessive toxicity or marked differences in the proportion of patients with low end-induction minimum residual disease (MRD) [L4892].&#13;
&#13;
Pharmacodynamic (PD) response was studied through measurement of plasma and cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) asparagine concentrations with an LC-MS/MS assay (liquid chromatography–mass spectrometry). Asparagine concentration in plasma was sustained below the assay limit of quantification for more than 18 days after one dose of calaspargase pegol, 2,500 U/m2, during the induction phase of treatment. Average cerebrospinal asparagine concentrations decreased from a pretreatment concentration of 0.8 μg/mL (N=10) to 0.2 μg/mL on Day 4 (N=37) and stayed decreased at 0.2 μg/mL (N=35) 25 days after the administration of one of 2,500 U/m2 in the induction phase [FDA label].</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>L-asparaginase (the main component of this drug) is an enzyme that catalyzes the conversion of the amino acid L-asparagine into both aspartic acid and ammonia [FDA label], [A40273]. This process depletes malignant cells of their required asparagine. The depletion of asparagine then blocks protein synthesis and tumor cell proliferation, especially in the G1 phase of the cell cycle. As a result,  tumor cell death occurs. Asparagine is important in protein synthesis in acute lymphoblastic leukemia (ALL) cells which, unlike normal cells, cannot produce this amino acid due to lack of the enzyme _asparagine synthase_ [A40273], [FDA label]. &#13;
&#13;
Pegylation decreases enzyme antigenicity and increases its half-life. Succinimidyl carbamate (SC) is used as a PEG linker to facilitate attachment to asparaginase and enhances the stability of the formulation [L4891], [A40270].  SC-PEG urethane linkages formed with lysine groups are more hydrolytically stable [A40273].&#13;
</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity>Pancreatitis, hepatotoxicity, hemorrhage, and thrombosis have been observed with calaspargase pegol use [FDA label].&#13;
 &#13;
**Pancreatitis**:&#13;
Discontinue this drug in patients with pancreatitis, and monitor blood glucose.  &#13;
&#13;
**Hepatotoxicity**:&#13;
Hepatic function should be tested regularly, and trough levels of this drug should be measured during the recovery phase of the drug cycle [FDA label]. &#13;
&#13;
**Hemorrhage or Thrombosis**: Discontinue this drug in serious or life-threatening hemorrhage or thrombosis. In cases of hemorrhage, identify the cause of hemorrhage and treat appropriately. Administer anticoagulant therapy as indicated in thrombotic events [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
**A note on hypersensitivity**:&#13;
&#13;
Observe the patient for 1 hour after administration of calaspargase pegol for possible hypersensitivity [FDA label]. In cases of previous hypersensitivity to this drug, discontinue this drug immediately.&#13;
&#13;
**Lactation:** Advise women not to breastfeed while taking this drug [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
**Pregnancy**: There are no available data on the use of calaspargase pegol in pregnant women to confirm a risk of drug-associated major birth defects and miscarriage. Published literature studies in pregnant animals suggest asparagine depletion can cause harm to the animal offspring. It is therefore advisable to inform women of childbearing age of this risk. The background risk of major birth defects and miscarriage for humans is unknown at this time [FDA label].&#13;
&#13;
Pregnancy testing should occur before initiating treatment.  Advise females of reproductive potential to avoid becoming pregnant while taking this drug. Females should use effective contraceptive methods, including a barrier methods, during treatment and for at least 3 months after the last dose. There is a risk for an interaction between calaspargase pegol and oral contraceptives. The concurrent use of this drug with oral contraceptives should be avoided. Other non-oral contraceptive methods should be used in women of childbearing potential [FDA label].&#13;
</toxicity>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption>Mean Tmax (1 h): 1.7 [FDA label].</absorption>
  <half-life>16.1 days [FDA label]</half-life>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution>Vss (L):  2.96 [FDA label]</volume-of-distribution>
  <clearance>0.147 L/day [FDA label]</clearance>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="inn/usan">Calaspargase pegol</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">calaspargase pegol-mknl</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>Asparlas</name>
      <labeller>Servier Pharmaceuticals LLC</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>72694-515</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2019-09-27</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>750 U/1mL</strength>
      <route>Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>BLA761102</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>Asparlas</name>
      <ingredients>Calaspargase pegol</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Alcohols</category>
      <mesh-id>D000438</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Amidohydrolases</category>
      <mesh-id>D000581</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Asparagine-specific Enzyme</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Compounds used in a research, industrial, or household setting</category>
      <mesh-id>D020313</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Enzymes</category>
      <mesh-id>D004798</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Enzymes and Coenzymes</category>
      <mesh-id>D045762</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Ethylene Glycols</category>
      <mesh-id>D005026</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Glycols</category>
      <mesh-id>D006018</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Hydrolases</category>
      <mesh-id>D006867</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Macromolecular Substances</category>
      <mesh-id>D046911</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Polymers</category>
      <mesh-id>D011108</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Injection, solution</form>
      <route>Intravenous</route>
      <strength>750 U/1mL</strength>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <fda-label>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/fda_labels/DB14730.pdf?1545413128</fda-label>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00304</drugbank-id>
      <name>Desogestrel</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Desogestrel can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00351</drugbank-id>
      <name>Megestrol acetate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Megestrol acetate can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00367</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levonorgestrel</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Levonorgestrel can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00603</drugbank-id>
      <name>Medroxyprogesterone acetate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Medroxyprogesterone acetate can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00717</drugbank-id>
      <name>Norethisterone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Norethisterone can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Estradiol can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00823</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethynodiol diacetate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ethynodiol diacetate can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00834</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mifepristone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Mifepristone can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00957</drugbank-id>
      <name>Norgestimate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Norgestimate can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00977</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethinylestradiol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ethinylestradiol can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01395</drugbank-id>
      <name>Drospirenone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Drospirenone can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04839</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cyproterone acetate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Cyproterone acetate can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06730</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gestodene</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Gestodene can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09123</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dienogest</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Dienogest can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09371</drugbank-id>
      <name>Norethynodrel</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Norethynodrel can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09389</drugbank-id>
      <name>Norgestrel</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Norgestrel can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11619</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gestrinone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Gestrinone can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12474</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lynestrenol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Lynestrenol can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13310</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ormeloxifene</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ormeloxifene can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13528</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlormadinone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Chlormadinone can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13563</drugbank-id>
      <name>Norgestrienone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Norgestrienone can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13685</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quingestanol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Quingestanol can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13857</drugbank-id>
      <name>Demegestone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Demegestone can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13981</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nomegestrol acetate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Nomegestrol acetate can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14678</drugbank-id>
      <name>Norethindrone enanthate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Norethindrone enanthate can be decreased when used in combination with Calaspargase pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Wikipedia</resource>
      <identifier>Calaspargase_pegol-mknl</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets>
    <target position="1">
      <id>BE0004798</id>
      <name>L-asparagine</name>
      <organism>Humans</organism>
      <actions>
        <action>degradation</action>
      </actions>
      <references>
        <articles>
          <article>
            <ref-id>A40270</ref-id>
            <pubmed-id>25348002</pubmed-id>
            <citation>Angiolillo AL, Schore RJ, Devidas M, Borowitz MJ, Carroll AJ, Gastier-Foster JM, Heerema NA, Keilani T, Lane AR, Loh ML, Reaman GH, Adamson PC, Wood B, Wood C, Zheng HW, Raetz EA, Winick NJ, Carroll WL, Hunger SP: Pharmacokinetic and pharmacodynamic properties of calaspargase pegol Escherichia coli L-asparaginase in the treatment of patients with acute lymphoblastic leukemia: results from Children's Oncology Group Study AALL07P4. J Clin Oncol. 2014 Dec 1;32(34):3874-82. doi: 10.1200/JCO.2014.55.5763. Epub 2014 Oct 27.</citation>
          </article>
          <article>
            <ref-id>A40273</ref-id>
            <pubmed-id>18580955</pubmed-id>
            <citation>Appel IM, Kazemier KM, Boos J, Lanvers C, Huijmans J, Veerman AJ, van Wering E, den Boer ML, Pieters R: Pharmacokinetic, pharmacodynamic and intracellular effects of PEG-asparaginase in newly diagnosed childhood acute lymphoblastic leukemia: results from a single agent window study. Leukemia. 2008 Sep;22(9):1665-79. doi: 10.1038/leu.2008.165. Epub 2008 Jun 26.</citation>
          </article>
        </articles>
        <textbooks/>
        <links>
          <link>
            <ref-id>L4892</ref-id>
            <title>Blood Journal: Randomized Study of Pegaspargase (SS-PEG) and Calaspargase Pegol (SPC-PEG) in Pediatric Patients with Newly Diagnosed Acute Lymphoblastic Leukemia or Lymphoblastic Lymphoma: Results of DFCI ALL Consortium Protocol 11-001</title>
            <url>http://www.bloodjournal.org/content/128/22/175?sso-checked=true</url>
          </link>
        </links>
        <attachments/>
      </references>
      <known-action>yes</known-action>
    </target>
  </targets>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>