<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2019-12-20" updated="2019-12-24">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB15595</drugbank-id>
  <name>Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated)</name>
  <description>Ebola virus vaccine is a vaccine used to prevent Ebola virus disease caused by _Zaire ebolavirus_ in adults, prevent outbreaks, and reduce the extent of the virus spreading in case of outbreaks.[L10854] Ebola virus disease, formerly known as Ebola hemorrhagic fever, is a rare but severe and often deadly disease. It is highly contagious: human to human transmission occurs from contact with body fluids from infected patients.[A189024] It is characterized by fever, headache, myalgia, and gastrointestinal symptoms. These may be accompanied by hypotension and respiratory, kidney and liver failure, as well as internal and external bleeding.[A188994,A188997] In the _Filoviridae_ family, there are five unique Ebolavirus species that are each named after the geographical region where it was first identified. The mortality rate of the Zaire species is about 80%.[A188997]&#13;
&#13;
Confirmed outbreaks of Ebola virus disease have been documented since the 1970s, mostly in Sub-Saharan Africa, where Ebola first appeared in 1976 near the Ebola River in Zaire (presently referred to as the Democratic Republic of the Congo) and Sudan.[A188994] Between 2014 and 2016, Ebola outbreaks occurred in West Africa, leading to more than 11,310 total deaths during this time in Guinea, Liberia, and Sierra Leone.[A188997] In 2016, this epidemic was exhausted after these countries were declared Ebola-free by 2016, and the World Health Organization (WHO) lifted the Public Health Emergency of International Concern (PHEIC) status on the West Africa Ebola outbreak.[L10884]&#13;
&#13;
The first live, attenuated Ebola virus vaccine was developed by a team of Canadian researchers at Canada’s National Microbiology Laboratory and was later patented by the Canadian government.[L10866] In non-human primate clinical trials, the vaccine was effective in inducing an immune response against the Ebola viruses.[A189018] This vaccine was later sold to NewLink Genetics, a biotech company that held the license to the vaccine from 2010 to 2014, although the vaccine was not marketed.[L10866] In 2014, Merck Inc. signed a licensing agreement with NewLink for further development and marketing. Ervebo, the marketed Ebola virus vaccine by Merck, was first approved by the European Commission in November 2019 after the European Medicines Agency recommended it be licensed. In December 2019, Ervebo was approved by the FDA in the United States. Ervebo consists of an envelope glycoprotein of the Zaire ebolavirus (Kikwit 1995 strain) fused into a vesicular stomatitis virus (VSV) backbone.[L10854] By introducing the relatively inactive viral protein to the patient, the patient’s immune system learns to recognize and attack the virus if he or she is exposed to it in the future.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A188994</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25285105</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Laupland KB, Valiquette L: Ebola virus disease. Can J Infect Dis Med Microbiol. 2014 May;25(3):128-9. doi: 10.1155/2014/527378.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A188997</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>28791241</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Khalafallah MT, Aboshady OA, Moawed SA, Ramadan MS: Ebola virus disease: Essential clinical knowledge. Avicenna J Med. 2017 Jul-Sep;7(3):96-102. doi: 10.4103/ajm.AJM_150_16.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A189018</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>15937495</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Jones SM, Feldmann H, Stroher U, Geisbert JB, Fernando L, Grolla A, Klenk HD, Sullivan NJ, Volchkov VE, Fritz EA, Daddario KM, Hensley LE, Jahrling PB, Geisbert TW: Live attenuated recombinant vaccine protects nonhuman primates against Ebola and Marburg viruses. Nat Med. 2005 Jul;11(7):786-90. doi: 10.1038/nm1258. Epub 2005 Jun 5.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A189024</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25497512</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Beeching NJ, Fenech M, Houlihan CF: Ebola virus disease. BMJ. 2014 Dec 10;349:g7348. doi: 10.1136/bmj.g7348.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A39899</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>21739679</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Pulendran B, Ahmed R: Immunological mechanisms of vaccination. Nat Immunol. 2011 Jun;12(6):509-17.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L10854</ref-id>
        <title>ERVEBO® (Ebola Zaire Vaccine, Live) - FDA Label</title>
        <url>https://www.fda.gov/media/133748/download</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L10857</ref-id>
        <title>ERVEBO, INN-Ebola Zaire Vaccine - Summary of Product Characteristics - EMA</title>
        <url>https://www.ema.europa.eu/en/documents/product-information/ervebo-epar-product-information_en.pdf</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L10866</ref-id>
        <title>How the new Ebola vaccine was made in Canada - CBC News</title>
        <url>https://www.cbc.ca/news/health/second-opinion-ebola-vaccine-1.4672807</url>
      </link>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L10884</ref-id>
        <title>2014-2016 Ebola Outbreak in West Africa | History | Ebola (Ebola Virus Disease) | CDC</title>
        <url>https://www.cdc.gov/vhf/ebola/history/2014-2016-outbreak/index.html</url>
      </link>
    </links>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Ebola Zaire vaccine is indicated for active immunization of individuals 18 years of age or older to protect against Ebola Virus Disease (EVD) caused by _Zaire Ebolavirus_.[L10857]</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>Ebola Zaire vaccine protects against the Ebola virus infection and disease by introducing a protein produced by the _Zaire ebolavirus_ and initiating the body's normal immune responses against the virus. In clinical trials consisting of subjects receiving the Ebola virus vaccine, the vaccine virus RNA was detected in the plasma samples of most subjects within the first week after intramuscular injection.[L10854]</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>Ebola virus disease occurs when the virus comes into contact with the host tissue and invades the tissue by breaking in the mucosa or skin. Exposure can occur through animal-to-human or human-to-human transmission from blood and other bodily fluids of the virus-infected animal or human.[A189024] The viral genome then replicates inside the cell, causing gene modulation in host cells - including monocytes, macrophages, and dendritic cells - and promote cell apoptosis, releasing the viral particles to extracellular tissue.[A188997] The virus can further disseminate the infection by migrating to the regional lymph nodes, liver, and spleen to cause lymphadenopathy, hepatocellular necrosis, and lymphopenia.[A188997,A189024] Ebola virus can cause dysregulation of the host immune system by inducing the host expression and release of pro-inflammatory mediators, including interferons, interleukins (IL-2, IL- 6, IL-8, and IL-10), and tumour necrosis factor α (TNF-α).[A189024] These inflammatory processes promote endothelial activation and reduced vascular integrity. Furthermore, the release of tissue factors and increased nitric oxide levels lead to disseminated intravascular coagulation (DIC) and hypotension seen in the Ebola virus disease, respectively.[A188997,A189024] The incubation period after the Ebola virus infection is 1-21 days.[A189024]&#13;
&#13;
By introducing the attenuated viral protein to the patient, the Ebola Zaire vaccine elicits strong cellular and antibody responses against the virus. The vaccine produces a long-term immunity and protects the patient from Ebola virus infection and disease when he or she is exposed to  _Zaire ebolavirus_  in the future.[A39899] However, the relative contributions of innate, humoral and cell-mediated immunity to protection from Zaire ebolavirus is not fully understood.[L10854]</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity>There is limited information on the overdose and LD&lt;sub&gt;50&lt;/sub&gt; of Ebola Zaire vaccine.</toxicity>
  <metabolism>As with other live attenuated vaccines, Ebola virus vaccine is speculated to undergo nonspecific cellular degradation.</metabolism>
  <absorption>There is limited pharmacokinetic information on Ebola virus vaccine.</absorption>
  <half-life>There is limited pharmacokinetic information on Ebola virus vaccine.</half-life>
  <protein-binding>There is limited pharmacokinetic information on Ebola virus vaccine.</protein-binding>
  <route-of-elimination>Although there is limited information on the main route of elimination of Ebola virus vaccine, vaccine virus RNA was detected in the in the urine or saliva samples of the subjects in clinical trials who received intramuscular injections.[L10854]</route-of-elimination>
  <volume-of-distribution>There is limited pharmacokinetic information on Ebola virus vaccine.</volume-of-distribution>
  <clearance>There is limited pharmacokinetic information on Ebola virus vaccine.</clearance>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Ebola Zaire vaccine (live)</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Ebola Zaire Vaccine (rVSV∆G-ZEBOV-GP, live)</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Recombinant Vesicular Stomatitis Virus (rVSV) strain Indiana with a deletion of the VSV envelope glycoprotein (G) replaced with the Zaire Ebola Virus (ZEBOV) Kikwit 1995 strain surface glycoprotein (GP)</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Immunization</category>
      <mesh-id>D007114</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Immunologic Factors</category>
      <mesh-id>D007155</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Vaccines</category>
      <mesh-id>D014612</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Viral Vaccines</category>
      <mesh-id>D014765</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <fda-label>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/fda_labels/DB15595.pdf?1576877522</fda-label>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB10317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rubella virus vaccine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Rubella virus vaccine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB10318</drugbank-id>
      <name>Varicella Zoster Vaccine (Live/attenuated)</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Varicella Zoster Vaccine (Live/attenuated).</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB10343</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bacillus calmette-guerin substrain tice live antigen</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Bacillus calmette-guerin substrain tice live antigen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB10804</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bacillus calmette-guerin substrain connaught live antigen</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Bacillus calmette-guerin substrain connaught live antigen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB10805</drugbank-id>
      <name>Yellow Fever Vaccine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Yellow Fever Vaccine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11003</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anthrax vaccine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Anthrax vaccine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12386</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bacillus calmette-guerin substrain danish 1331 live antigen</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Bacillus calmette-guerin substrain danish 1331 live antigen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12768</drugbank-id>
      <name>BCG vaccine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with BCG vaccine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14409</drugbank-id>
      <name>Human adenovirus e serotype 4 strain cl-68578 antigen</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Human adenovirus e serotype 4 strain cl-68578 antigen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14443</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vibrio cholerae CVD 103-HgR strain live antigen</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Vibrio cholerae CVD 103-HgR strain live antigen.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00002</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cetuximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Cetuximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00028</drugbank-id>
      <name>Human immunoglobulin G</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Human immunoglobulin G.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00043</drugbank-id>
      <name>Omalizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Omalizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00051</drugbank-id>
      <name>Adalimumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Adalimumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00054</drugbank-id>
      <name>Abciximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Abciximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00056</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemtuzumab ozogamicin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Gemtuzumab ozogamicin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00057</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indium In-111 satumomab pendetide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Indium In-111 satumomab pendetide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00065</drugbank-id>
      <name>Infliximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Infliximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00072</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trastuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Trastuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00073</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rituximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Rituximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00074</drugbank-id>
      <name>Basiliximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Basiliximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00075</drugbank-id>
      <name>Muromonab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Muromonab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00076</drugbank-id>
      <name>Digoxin Immune Fab (Ovine)</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Digoxin Immune Fab (Ovine).</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00078</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibritumomab tiuxetan</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ibritumomab tiuxetan.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00081</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tositumomab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Tositumomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00087</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alemtuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Alemtuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00089</drugbank-id>
      <name>Capromab pendetide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Capromab pendetide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00095</drugbank-id>
      <name>Efalizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Efalizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00098</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antithymocyte immunoglobulin (rabbit)</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Antithymocyte immunoglobulin (rabbit).</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00108</drugbank-id>
      <name>Natalizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Natalizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00110</drugbank-id>
      <name>Palivizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Palivizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00111</drugbank-id>
      <name>Daclizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Daclizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00112</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bevacizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Bevacizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00113</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m arcitumomab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Technetium Tc-99m arcitumomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01257</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eculizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Eculizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01269</drugbank-id>
      <name>Panitumumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Panitumumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01270</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ranibizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ranibizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04901</drugbank-id>
      <name>Galiximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Galiximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04949</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pexelizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Pexelizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04956</drugbank-id>
      <name>Afelimomab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Afelimomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04958</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epratuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Epratuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04962</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bectumomab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Bectumomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04964</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oregovomab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Oregovomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04988</drugbank-id>
      <name>IGN311</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with IGN311.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05006</drugbank-id>
      <name>Adecatumumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Adecatumumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05097</drugbank-id>
      <name>Labetuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Labetuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05101</drugbank-id>
      <name>Matuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Matuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05111</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fontolizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Fontolizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05136</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bavituximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Bavituximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05139</drugbank-id>
      <name>CR002</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with CR002.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05209</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rozrolimupab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Rozrolimupab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05304</drugbank-id>
      <name>Girentuximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Girentuximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05336</drugbank-id>
      <name>Obiltoxaximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Obiltoxaximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05405</drugbank-id>
      <name>XTL-001</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with XTL-001.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05437</drugbank-id>
      <name>NAV 1800</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with NAV 1800.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05459</drugbank-id>
      <name>Briakinumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Briakinumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05496</drugbank-id>
      <name>Otelixizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Otelixizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05545</drugbank-id>
      <name>AMG 108</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with AMG 108.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05550</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iratumumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Iratumumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05555</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enokizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Enokizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05578</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ramucirumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ramucirumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Farletuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Farletuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05656</drugbank-id>
      <name>Veltuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Veltuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05679</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ustekinumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ustekinumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05773</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trastuzumab emtansine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Trastuzumab emtansine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05793</drugbank-id>
      <name>PRO-542</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with PRO-542.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05797</drugbank-id>
      <name>TNX-901</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with TNX-901.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05889</drugbank-id>
      <name>Inotuzumab ozogamicin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Inotuzumab ozogamicin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05892</drugbank-id>
      <name>RI 624</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with RI 624.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05915</drugbank-id>
      <name>MYO-029</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with MYO-029.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05916</drugbank-id>
      <name>CT-011</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with CT-011.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05941</drugbank-id>
      <name>Leronlimab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Leronlimab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05996</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glembatumumab vedotin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Glembatumumab vedotin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06043</drugbank-id>
      <name>Olaratumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Olaratumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06049</drugbank-id>
      <name>IPH 2101</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with IPH 2101.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06050</drugbank-id>
      <name>TB-402</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with TB-402.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06081</drugbank-id>
      <name>Caplacizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Caplacizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06101</drugbank-id>
      <name>IMC-1C11</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with IMC-1C11.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06116</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eldelumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Eldelumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06162</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lumiliximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Lumiliximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06168</drugbank-id>
      <name>Canakinumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Canakinumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06186</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ipilimumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ipilimumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06192</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nimotuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Nimotuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06241</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clenoliximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Clenoliximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06273</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tocilizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Tocilizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06304</drugbank-id>
      <name>BIIB015</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with BIIB015.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06305</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sonepcizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Sonepcizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06310</drugbank-id>
      <name>Motavizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Motavizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Elotuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Elotuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06318</drugbank-id>
      <name>AVE9633</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with AVE9633.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06322</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carotuximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Carotuximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06324</drugbank-id>
      <name>XmAb 2513</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with XmAb 2513.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06342</drugbank-id>
      <name>Coltuximab ravtansine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Coltuximab ravtansine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06343</drugbank-id>
      <name>Teprotumumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Teprotumumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06360</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lucatumumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Lucatumumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06366</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pertuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Pertuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06371</drugbank-id>
      <name>Siplizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Siplizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06467</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apolizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Apolizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06474</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sibrotuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Sibrotuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06550</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bivatuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Bivatuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06557</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lerdelimumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Lerdelimumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06599</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lexatumumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Lexatumumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06602</drugbank-id>
      <name>Reslizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Reslizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06606</drugbank-id>
      <name>Teplizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Teplizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06607</drugbank-id>
      <name>Catumaxomab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Catumaxomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06612</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mepolizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Mepolizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06643</drugbank-id>
      <name>Denosumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Denosumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06647</drugbank-id>
      <name>Volociximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Volociximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06650</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ofatumumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ofatumumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06674</drugbank-id>
      <name>Golimumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Golimumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08870</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brentuximab vedotin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Brentuximab vedotin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08879</drugbank-id>
      <name>Belimumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Belimumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08902</drugbank-id>
      <name>Raxibacumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Raxibacumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08904</drugbank-id>
      <name>Certolizumab pegol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Certolizumab pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08935</drugbank-id>
      <name>Obinutuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Obinutuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09029</drugbank-id>
      <name>Secukinumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Secukinumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09033</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vedolizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Vedolizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09035</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nivolumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Nivolumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09036</drugbank-id>
      <name>Siltuximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Siltuximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09037</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pembrolizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Pembrolizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09045</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dulaglutide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Dulaglutide.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09052</drugbank-id>
      <name>Blinatumomab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Blinatumomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09057</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anthrax immune globulin human</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Anthrax immune globulin human.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09077</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dinutuximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Dinutuximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09105</drugbank-id>
      <name>Asfotase alfa</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Asfotase alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Idarucizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Idarucizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09302</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alirocumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Alirocumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09303</drugbank-id>
      <name>Evolocumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Evolocumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09312</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antilymphocyte immunoglobulin (horse)</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Antilymphocyte immunoglobulin (horse).</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09331</drugbank-id>
      <name>Daratumumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Daratumumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09559</drugbank-id>
      <name>Necitumumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Necitumumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11569</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ixekizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ixekizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11580</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ravulizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ravulizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atezolizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Atezolizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11604</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetanus Immune Globulin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Tetanus Immune Globulin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11608</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eftrenonacog alfa</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Eftrenonacog alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11621</drugbank-id>
      <name>Human Varicella-Zoster Immune Globulin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Human Varicella-Zoster Immune Globulin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11646</drugbank-id>
      <name>Conatumumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Conatumumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11657</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tabalumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Tabalumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11680</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ficlatuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ficlatuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11685</drugbank-id>
      <name>Figitumumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Figitumumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11714</drugbank-id>
      <name>Durvalumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Durvalumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11715</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bapineuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Bapineuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11731</drugbank-id>
      <name>Depatuxizumab mafodotin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Depatuxizumab mafodotin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11746</drugbank-id>
      <name>Onartuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Onartuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11756</drugbank-id>
      <name>Solanezumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Solanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11767</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sarilumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Sarilumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11771</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tremelimumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Tremelimumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11776</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brodalumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Brodalumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11803</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sirukumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Sirukumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11826</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lampalizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Lampalizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11834</drugbank-id>
      <name>Guselkumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Guselkumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11840</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dalotuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Dalotuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11849</drugbank-id>
      <name>Emibetuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Emibetuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11850</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ublituximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ublituximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11856</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ligelizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ligelizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11857</drugbank-id>
      <name>Seribantumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Seribantumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11862</drugbank-id>
      <name>Landogrozumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Landogrozumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11866</drugbank-id>
      <name>Romosozumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Romosozumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11884</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vadastuximab Talirine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Vadastuximab Talirine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11914</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lebrikizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Lebrikizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11930</drugbank-id>
      <name>Varlilumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Varlilumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11945</drugbank-id>
      <name>Avelumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Avelumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11959</drugbank-id>
      <name>Crenezumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Crenezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11972</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rilotumumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Rilotumumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11976</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anifrolumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Anifrolumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11988</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ocrelizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ocrelizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12023</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benralizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Benralizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12034</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gantenerumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Gantenerumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12053</drugbank-id>
      <name>Visilizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Visilizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12077</drugbank-id>
      <name>Urelumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Urelumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12089</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lorvotuzumab mertansine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Lorvotuzumab mertansine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12090</drugbank-id>
      <name>Patritumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Patritumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12102</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fulranumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Fulranumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12104</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tarextumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Tarextumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12118</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sotatercept</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Sotatercept.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12119</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gevokizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Gevokizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12142</drugbank-id>
      <name>Duligotuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Duligotuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12152</drugbank-id>
      <name>Simtuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Simtuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12157</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fasinumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Fasinumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12159</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dupilumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Dupilumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12169</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tralokinumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Tralokinumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12189</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etrolizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Etrolizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12202</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zalutumumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Zalutumumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12205</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ganitumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ganitumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etaracizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Etaracizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12240</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polatuzumab vedotin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Polatuzumab vedotin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12246</drugbank-id>
      <name>Inclacumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Inclacumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12250</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cixutumumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Cixutumumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12261</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ascrinvacumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ascrinvacumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12274</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aducanumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Aducanumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12281</drugbank-id>
      <name>Luspatercept</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Luspatercept.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12296</drugbank-id>
      <name>GS-5745</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with GS-5745.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vanucizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Vanucizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12331</drugbank-id>
      <name>Labetuzumab govitecan</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Labetuzumab govitecan.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12335</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tanezumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Tanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12342</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ensituximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ensituximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12344</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fezakinumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Fezakinumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12363</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dusigitumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Dusigitumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12396</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fresolimumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Fresolimumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12413</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indusatumab vedotin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Indusatumab vedotin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12456</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bococizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Bococizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12489</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mirvetuximab Soravtansine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Mirvetuximab Soravtansine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12498</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mogamulizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Mogamulizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12520</drugbank-id>
      <name>Plozalizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Plozalizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12530</drugbank-id>
      <name>Inebilizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Inebilizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12534</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mavrilimumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Mavrilimumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12560</drugbank-id>
      <name>Blosozumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Blosozumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12584</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bimagrumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Bimagrumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12589</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dacetuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Dacetuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12609</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tovetumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Tovetumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12683</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lumretuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Lumretuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12698</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibalizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ibalizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12701</drugbank-id>
      <name>Intetumumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Intetumumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12718</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carlumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Carlumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12734</drugbank-id>
      <name>Demcizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Demcizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12773</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sifalimumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Sifalimumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12775</drugbank-id>
      <name>Abituzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Abituzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12797</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ecromeximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ecromeximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12807</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naptumomab Estafenatox</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Naptumomab Estafenatox.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12815</drugbank-id>
      <name>Crotedumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Crotedumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12820</drugbank-id>
      <name>Concizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Concizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12826</drugbank-id>
      <name>Depatuxizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Depatuxizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12844</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rontalizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Rontalizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12845</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amatuximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Amatuximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12849</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clazakizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Clazakizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12891</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ozanezumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ozanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12893</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sacituzumab govitecan</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Sacituzumab govitecan.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12917</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bimekizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Bimekizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12943</drugbank-id>
      <name>Milatuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Milatuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12976</drugbank-id>
      <name>Robatumumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Robatumumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13017</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rovalpituzumab Tesirine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Rovalpituzumab Tesirine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13037</drugbank-id>
      <name>Namilumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Namilumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13045</drugbank-id>
      <name>Racotumomab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Racotumomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13073</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tregalizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Tregalizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13127</drugbank-id>
      <name>Olokizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Olokizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13140</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bezlotoxumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Bezlotoxumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13375</drugbank-id>
      <name>Edrecolomab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Edrecolomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13535</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nebacumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Nebacumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13886</drugbank-id>
      <name>Human cytomegalovirus immune globulin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Human cytomegalovirus immune globulin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13923</drugbank-id>
      <name>Emicizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Emicizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13976</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulesomab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Sulesomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13979</drugbank-id>
      <name>Besilesomab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Besilesomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14004</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tildrakizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Tildrakizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14012</drugbank-id>
      <name>Burosumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Burosumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14039</drugbank-id>
      <name>Erenumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Erenumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14040</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eptinezumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Eptinezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14041</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fremanezumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Fremanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14042</drugbank-id>
      <name>Galcanezumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14211</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fanolesomab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Fanolesomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14580</drugbank-id>
      <name>BAN-2401</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with BAN-2401.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14597</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lanadelumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Lanadelumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14707</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cemiplimab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Cemiplimab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14724</drugbank-id>
      <name>Emapalumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Emapalumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14762</drugbank-id>
      <name>Risankizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Risankizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14776</drugbank-id>
      <name>Camrelizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Camrelizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14778</drugbank-id>
      <name>Setrusumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Setrusumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14784</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gancotamab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Gancotamab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14809</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anetumab ravtansine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Anetumab ravtansine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14811</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isatuximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Isatuximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14824</drugbank-id>
      <name>Icrucumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Icrucumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14843</drugbank-id>
      <name>Codrituzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Codrituzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14864</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brolucizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Brolucizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14871</drugbank-id>
      <name>Xentuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Xentuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14877</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lintuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Lintuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14891</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vobarilizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Vobarilizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14897</drugbank-id>
      <name>Parsatuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Parsatuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14905</drugbank-id>
      <name>Emactuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Emactuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14907</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bevacizumab zirconium Zr-89</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Bevacizumab zirconium Zr-89.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14908</drugbank-id>
      <name>Refanezumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Refanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14919</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rozanolixizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Rozanolixizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14947</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bermekimab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Bermekimab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14952</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pamrevlumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Pamrevlumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14959</drugbank-id>
      <name>Opicinumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Opicinumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14962</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trastuzumab deruxtecan</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Trastuzumab deruxtecan.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14967</drugbank-id>
      <name>Margetuximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Margetuximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14988</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dalantercept</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Dalantercept.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14997</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pateclizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Pateclizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15014</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gremubamab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Gremubamab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15022</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apomab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Apomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15044</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tafasitamab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Tafasitamab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15045</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ipafricept</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ipafricept.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15076</drugbank-id>
      <name>Abrilumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Abrilumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15089</drugbank-id>
      <name>Frovocimab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Frovocimab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15090</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tezepelumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Tezepelumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15101</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tigatuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Tigatuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15104</drugbank-id>
      <name>Telisotuzumab vedotin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Telisotuzumab vedotin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15113</drugbank-id>
      <name>Utomilumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Utomilumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15118</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zolbetuximab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Zolbetuximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15135</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ponezumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ponezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15160</drugbank-id>
      <name>Asunercept</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Asunercept.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15172</drugbank-id>
      <name>Suvratoxumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Suvratoxumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15225</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mitazalimab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Mitazalimab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15252</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nemolizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Nemolizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15253</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bleselumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Bleselumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15277</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gedivumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Gedivumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15336</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valanafusp alfa</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Valanafusp alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15349</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sofituzumab vedotin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Sofituzumab vedotin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15354</drugbank-id>
      <name>Evinacumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Evinacumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15363</drugbank-id>
      <name>Istiratumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Istiratumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15383</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pidilizumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Pidilizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15397</drugbank-id>
      <name>GMA-161</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with GMA-161.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15409</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ladiratuzumab vedotin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Ladiratuzumab vedotin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15415</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tomaralimab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Tomaralimab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15428</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vesencumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Vesencumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15432</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pinatuzumab vedotin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Pinatuzumab vedotin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15441</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lulizumab pegol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Lulizumab pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15443</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lorukafusp alfa</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Lorukafusp alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15453</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naratuximab emtansine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Naratuximab emtansine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15559</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zenocutuzumab</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Zenocutuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers/>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>