<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2013-07-31" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB08917</drugbank-id>
  <name>Ferric carboxymaltose</name>
  <description>Ferric Carboxymaltose is an iron replacement product and chemically, an iron carbohydrate complex. FDA approved on July 25, 2013.</description>
  <cas-number>9007-72-1</cas-number>
  <unii>6897GXD6OE</unii>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Ferric carboxymaltose is a iron replacement product indicated for the treatment of iron deficiency anemia in adult patients who have intolerance to oral iron or have had unsatisfactory response to oral iron or those who have non-dialysis dependent chronic kidney disease. </indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>When measured using positron emission tomography (PET), the red cell uptake of 59-Fe and 52-Fe from INJECTAFER ranged from 61% to 99%. In patients with iron deficiency, the red cell uptake ranged from 91% to 99%. In patients with renal anemia, the red cell uptake ranged from 61% to 84%. </pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>Ferric carboxymaltose is a colloidal iron (III) hydroxide in complex with carboxymaltose, a carbohydrate polymer that release iron. </mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity>The most common adverse reactions (&gt;2%) are nausea, hypertension,&#13;
flushing, hypophosphatemia, and dizziness. </toxicity>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption>When a single dose of 100 to 1000 mg of iron was given to iron deficient patients, the maximum serum concentration (Cmax) was 37 μg/mL to 333 μg/mL. These levels were obtained 15 minutes to 1.21 hours post dose (Tmax). </absorption>
  <half-life>7 to 12 hours. </half-life>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination>Renal elimination of iron was negligible. </route-of-elimination>
  <volume-of-distribution>3 L</volume-of-distribution>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="inn/usan">Ferric carboxymaltose</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Iron carboxymaltose</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Iron dextri-maltose</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>Injectafer</name>
      <labeller>AMERICAN REGENT, INC.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>0517-0650</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2013-08-12</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>50 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Intravenous</route>
      <fda-application-number>NDA203565</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>Injectafer</name>
      <ingredients>Ferric carboxymaltose</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Biopolymers</category>
      <mesh-id>D001704</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Carbohydrates</category>
      <mesh-id>D002241</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Compounds used in a research, industrial, or household setting</category>
      <mesh-id>D020313</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Disaccharides</category>
      <mesh-id>D004187</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Glucans</category>
      <mesh-id>D005936</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Iron Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D058085</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Macromolecular Substances</category>
      <mesh-id>D046911</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Oligosaccharides</category>
      <mesh-id>D009844</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Organometallic Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D009942</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Parenteral Iron Replacement</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Phosphate Binder</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Polymers</category>
      <mesh-id>D011108</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Polysaccharides</category>
      <mesh-id>D011134</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Injection, solution</form>
      <route>Intravenous</route>
      <strength>50 mg/1mL</strength>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <fda-label>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/fda_labels/DB08917.pdf?1375337673</fda-label>
  <patents>
    <patent>
      <number>8895612</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2014-11-25</approved>
      <expires>2027-01-08</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
    <patent>
      <number>7754702</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2010-07-13</approved>
      <expires>2027-02-13</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
    <patent>
      <number>7612109</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2009-11-03</approved>
      <expires>2024-02-05</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
    <patent>
      <number>9376505</number>
      <country>United States</country>
      <approved>2016-06-28</approved>
      <expires>2023-10-20</expires>
      <pediatric-extension>false</pediatric-extension>
    </patent>
  </patents>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moxifloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Moxifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00365</drugbank-id>
      <name>Grepafloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Grepafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00467</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enoxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Enoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00487</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pefloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pefloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00537</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ciprofloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ciprofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00685</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trovafloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Trovafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00779</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nalidixic acid</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Nalidixic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rosoxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rosoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00827</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cinoxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Cinoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00978</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lomefloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Lomefloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01044</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gatifloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Gatifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01059</drugbank-id>
      <name>Norfloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Norfloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01137</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levofloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Levofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01155</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemifloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Gemifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01165</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ofloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sparfloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sparfloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01405</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temafloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Temafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04576</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fleroxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Fleroxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05488</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m ciprofloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Technetium Tc-99m ciprofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06160</drugbank-id>
      <name>Garenoxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Garenoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06600</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nemonoxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Nemonoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08972</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flumequine</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Flumequine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11404</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enrofloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Enrofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11443</drugbank-id>
      <name>Orbifloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Orbifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11491</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sarafloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sarafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11511</drugbank-id>
      <name>Difloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Difloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11774</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pazufloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pazufloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11892</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prulifloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Prulifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11943</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delafloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Delafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13261</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sitafloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sitafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13627</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxolinic acid</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Oxolinic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13772</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rufloxacin</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rufloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13823</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pipemidic acid</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pipemidic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06782</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dimercaprol</name>
      <description>Dimercaprol may increase the nephrotoxic activities of Ferric carboxymaltose.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08826</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deferiprone</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Deferiprone can be decreased when it is combined with Ferric carboxymaltose.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00968</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methyldopa</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Methyldopa resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06824</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triethylenetetramine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ferric carboxymaltose can be decreased when it is combined with Triethylenetetramine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02369</drugbank-id>
      <name>3-Aza-2,3-Dihydrogeranyl Diphosphate</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of 3-Aza-2,3-Dihydrogeranyl Diphosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02423</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiopyrophosphate</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Thiopyrophosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02552</drugbank-id>
      <name>Geranyl Diphosphate</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Geranyl Diphosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04160</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pyrophosphoric acid</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pyrophosphoric acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05143</drugbank-id>
      <name>OXI-4503</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of OXI-4503 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07841</drugbank-id>
      <name>Geranylgeranyl diphosphate</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Geranylgeranyl diphosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09147</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric pyrophosphate</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferric pyrophosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09413</drugbank-id>
      <name>Monopotassium phosphate</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Monopotassium phosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09414</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dipotassium phosphate</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dipotassium phosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09449</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium phosphate, monobasic</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sodium phosphate, monobasic resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11348</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium Phosphate</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Calcium Phosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11493</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sodium tripolyphosphate</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sodium tripolyphosphate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13995</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ferric pyrophosphate citrate</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ferric pyrophosphate citrate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14481</drugbank-id>
      <name>Calcium phosphate dihydrate</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Calcium phosphate dihydrate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14523</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phosphate ion</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Phosphate ion resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09139</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m oxidronate</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Technetium Tc-99m oxidronate resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00338</drugbank-id>
      <name>Omeprazole</name>
      <description>The absorption of Ferric carboxymaltose can be decreased when combined with Omeprazole.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00190</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbidopa</name>
      <description>Ferric carboxymaltose can cause a decrease in the absorption of Carbidopa resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910386</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>KEGG Drug</resource>
      <identifier>D08920</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Wikipedia</resource>
      <identifier>Iron_supplement</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEMBL</resource>
      <identifier>CHEMBL2108597</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links>
    <external-link>
      <resource>Drugs.com</resource>
      <url>http://www.drugs.com/international/ferric-carboxymaltose.html</url>
    </external-link>
  </external-links>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>