<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2018-05-18" updated="2020-01-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB14042</drugbank-id>
  <name>Galcanezumab</name>
  <description>LY2951742/galcanezumab is a fully humanized monoclonal antibody against human calcitonin gene-related peptide (CGRP) that is developed by ELi Lilly and Company.[A33105] This therapy is given as a single subcutaneous injection twice a month and ongoing clinical trials for the agent are for episodic and chronic migraine as well as cluster headaches.[A33114]&#13;
&#13;
Although various small-molecule CGRP receptor antagonists have also been developed, humanized monoclonal antibodies like galcanezumab are specifically designed to potently and selectively bind to the CGRP entities directly.[A33112] Given this target specificity, lack of off-target toxicity, and characteristic proteolysis profile of immunoglobulin antibodies to not undergo metabolism by liver enzymes, galcanezumab possesses favourable and promising safety and tolerability.[A33112]&#13;
&#13;
Galcanezumab was given FDA approval on 27 September 2018.[L4894]</description>
  <cas-number>1578199-75-3</cas-number>
  <unii>55KHL3P693</unii>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A33105</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>28409893</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Pellesi L, Guerzoni S, Pini LA: Spotlight on Anti-CGRP Monoclonal Antibodies in Migraine: The Clinical Evidence to Date. Clin Pharmacol Drug Dev. 2017 Nov;6(6):534-547. doi: 10.1002/cpdd.345. Epub 2017 Apr 14.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A33106</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>29019093</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Benemei S, Cortese F, Labastida-Ramirez A, Marchese F, Pellesi L, Romoli M, Vollesen AL, Lampl C, Ashina M: Triptans and CGRP blockade - impact on the cranial vasculature. J Headache Pain. 2017 Oct 10;18(1):103. doi: 10.1186/s10194-017-0811-5.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A33112</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>29089894</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Monteith D, Collins EC, Vandermeulen C, Van Hecken A, Raddad E, Scherer JC, Grayzel D, Schuetz TJ, de Hoon J: Safety, Tolerability, Pharmacokinetics, and Pharmacodynamics of the CGRP Binding Monoclonal Antibody LY2951742 (Galcanezumab) in Healthy Volunteers. Front Pharmacol. 2017 Oct 17;8:740. doi: 10.3389/fphar.2017.00740. eCollection 2017.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A33108</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>25297013</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Dodick DW, Goadsby PJ, Silberstein SD, Lipton RB, Olesen J, Ashina M, Wilks K, Kudrow D, Kroll R, Kohrman B, Bargar R, Hirman J, Smith J: Safety and efficacy of ALD403, an antibody to calcitonin gene-related peptide, for the prevention of frequent episodic migraine: a randomised, double-blind, placebo-controlled, exploratory phase 2 trial. Lancet Neurol. 2014 Nov;13(11):1100-1107. doi: 10.1016/S1474-4422(14)70209-1. Epub 2014 Oct 5.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A33114</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>24867844</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Vollbracht S, Rapoport AM: New treatments for headache. Neurol Sci. 2014 May;35 Suppl 1:89-97. doi: 10.1007/s10072-014-1747-z.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A33090</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>28948500</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Deen M, Correnti E, Kamm K, Kelderman T, Papetti L, Rubio-Beltran E, Vigneri S, Edvinsson L, Maassen Van Den Brink A: Blocking CGRP in migraine patients - a review of pros and cons. J Headache Pain. 2017 Sep 25;18(1):96. doi: 10.1186/s10194-017-0807-1.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links>
      <link>
        <ref-id>L4894</ref-id>
        <title>FDA Label: Apadaz</title>
        <url>https://www.accessdata.fda.gov/drugsatfda_docs/label/2018/208653s002s003lbl.pdf</url>
      </link>
    </links>
    <attachments>
      <attachment>
        <ref-id>F94</ref-id>
        <title>Presentation on CGRP, MONOCLONAL ANTIBODIES AND SMALL MOLECULES (-GEPANTS)</title>
        <url>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/cite_this/attachments/files/000/000/094/original/Diener-Hans-Christoph_CGRP-M.pdf?1527011193</url>
      </attachment>
    </attachments>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Galcanezumab is a humanized monoclonal antibody that is indicated for migraine prophylaxis and treatment of episodic cluster headaches in adults by binding endogenous human calcitonin gene-related peptide (CGRP).[A33112,Label]</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>Galcanezumab is administered as a subcutaneous injection.[A33112,A33114,Label] During clinical trials, it was noted that galcanezumab therapy resulted in a significant reduction in the mean number of migraine headache days and a good tolerability profile.[A33105] Additionally, post hoc efficacy analyses showed that 32% in the galcanezumab group versus 18% in the placebo group were complete responders.[A33105] Finally, the most commonly reported adverse events associated with galcanezumab use are headache, nasopharyngitis, hematuria, dermatitis, diarrhea, toothache, and increased alanine aminotransferase (ALT).[A33112]</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>Galcanezumab is a fully humanized monoclonal antibody designed and manufactured specifically against calcitonin gene-related peptide (CGRP).[A33105,Label] It binds avidly to human CGRP, with a binding affinity (Kd) of 31 pM (4.5 ng/mL).&#13;
&#13;
Studies since 1985 have demonstrated that CGRP levels increase during acute migraine attacks in migraine-suffering patients but normalize after efficacious sumatriptan therapy.[A33090] Moreover, research has also shown that intravenous administration of CGRP can induce migraine-like attacks in migraine-suffering patients.[A33090] For all these reasons, the binding of CGRP to interfere with its activity was specifically designed to be the mechanism of action for galcanezumab to take advantage of in reversing the migraine-inducing activity of natural CGRP. The binding of galcanezumab to natural endogenous CGRP subsequently interferes with its activities, such as its binding to CGRP receptors, for example.&#13;
&#13;
Studies have also shown that humanized monoclonal antibodies against CGRP have proven successful in reducing the frequency of migraine headaches in early clinical trials as a preventative therapeutic.[A33112]</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity>Overdose and LD&lt;sub&gt;50&lt;/sub&gt; date are not readily available.[Label]&#13;
&#13;
The most common adverse effects associated with galcanezumab during clinical trials include headache, nasopharyngitis, hematuria, and contact dermatitis [A33112]. However, with the exception of hematuria which was not present in placebo treatment arms, the frequencies of these events were similar to placebo [A33112]. Additional frequently reported adverse effects in subjects receiving galcanezumab were diarrhea, toothache, and increased alanine aminotransferase (ALT) [A33112].&#13;
&#13;
The pharmacokinetics of galcanezumab were not affected by age, sex, race, or subtypes of migraine spectrum (episodic or chronic migraine), based on a population pharmacokinetic analysis [FDA Label]. Body weight has no clinically relevant effect on the pharmacokinetics of galcanezumab [FDA Label].&#13;
&#13;
Renal and hepatic impairment are not expected to affect the pharmacokinetics of galcanezumab [FDA Label]. Population pharmacokinetic analysis of integrated data from the galcanezumab clinical studies revealed that creatinine clearance did not affect the pharmacokinetics of galcanezumab in patients with mild or moderate renal impairment [FDA Label]. Patients with severe renal impairment (creatinine clearance &lt;30 mL/min) have not been studied [FDA Label]. Based on a population PK analysis, bilirubin concentration did not significantly influence the CL/F of galcanezumab [FDA Label].&#13;
&#13;
Studies regarding the carcinogenic potential and genetic toxicology of galcanezumab have not yet been conducted [FDA Label].&#13;
&#13;
When galcanezumab (0, 30, or 250 mg/kg) was administered to male rats by subcutaneous injection prior to and during mating, no adverse effects on fertility was observed [FDA Label]. The higher dose tested was associated with a plasma exposure (Cave, ss) 8 times that in humans at the recommended human dose (RHD) of 120 mg [FDA Label]. When galcanezumab was administered to female rats by subcutaneous injection in two studies (0, 30, or 100 mg/kg; 0 or 250 mg/kg) prior to and during mating and continuing throughout organogenesis, no adverse effects on fertility were observed [FDA Label]. The highest dose tested (250 mg/kg) was associated with a plasma Cave, ss 38 times that in humans at the RHD [FDA Label].</toxicity>
  <metabolism>Monoclonal antibody agents like galcanezumab are not expected to generate toxic metabolites as they generally undergo proteolysis to their constituent amino acids.[F94] In particular, after administration galcanezumab is specifically expected to be degraded into small peptides and amino acids via catabolic pathways in the same manner as endogenous immunoglobulins.[Label] Galcanezumab is also not believed to be metabolized by liver enzymes - making drug-drug interactions relatively unlikely.[Label]</metabolism>
  <absorption>Following single dose subcutaneous administration, the time to maximum concentration was recorded as 5 days.[Label] The injection site location did not appear to significantly influence the absorption of galcanezumab.[Label]&#13;
&#13;
The Cmax and the area under the concentration-time curve from dosing to infinity (AUC (0-∞)) are generally considered to be dose proportional over a dose range.[A33112]</absorption>
  <half-life>The mean serum half-life of galcanezumab is similar at all dose levels at about 25-30 days.[A33112] The elimination half-life of galcanezumab was ultimately approximately 27 days.[Label]</half-life>
  <protein-binding>Readily accessible data regarding the protein binding of galcanezumab is not available.</protein-binding>
  <route-of-elimination>Monoclonal antibody agents like galcanezumab are generally not eliminated via hepatic, renal, or biliary routes.[F94]&#13;
&#13;
</route-of-elimination>
  <volume-of-distribution>The apparent volume of distribution of galcanezumab is documented to be 7.3 L, with 34% inter-individual variability.[Label]</volume-of-distribution>
  <clearance>It is noted that the clearance of galcanezumab is by proteolysis.[A33112] The apparent clearance of galcanezumab was recorded as 0.008 L/h.[Label]</clearance>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Galcanezumab-gnlm</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>Emgality</name>
      <labeller>Eli Lilly &amp; Co. Ltd.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>02491060</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2019-10-07</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>120 mg</strength>
      <route>Subcutaneous</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Emgality</name>
      <labeller>Eli Lilly &amp; Co. Ltd.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>02491087</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2019-10-02</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>120 mg</strength>
      <route>Subcutaneous</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Emgality</name>
      <labeller>Eli Lilly and Company</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>0002-1436</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2018-09-27</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>120 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Subcutaneous</route>
      <fda-application-number>BLA761063</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Emgality</name>
      <labeller>Eli Lilly and Company</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>0002-2377</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2018-09-27</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>120 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Subcutaneous</route>
      <fda-application-number>BLA761063</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Emgality</name>
      <labeller>Eli Lilly and Company</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>0002-3115</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2019-06-04</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Injection, solution</dosage-form>
      <strength>100 mg/1mL</strength>
      <route>Subcutaneous</route>
      <fda-application-number>BLA761063</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>Emgality</name>
      <ingredients>Galcanezumab</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Emgality</name>
      <ingredients>Galcanezumab</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Emgality</name>
      <ingredients>Galcanezumab</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Emgality</name>
      <ingredients>Galcanezumab</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Emgality</name>
      <ingredients>Galcanezumab</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Proteins</category>
      <mesh-id>D000602</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Analgesics</category>
      <mesh-id>D000700</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Antibodies</category>
      <mesh-id>D000906</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Antibodies, Monoclonal</category>
      <mesh-id>D000911</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Antibodies, Monoclonal, Humanized</category>
      <mesh-id>D061067</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Antimigraine Preparations</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Blood Proteins</category>
      <mesh-id>D001798</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Calcitonin Gene-Related Peptide Receptor Antagonists</category>
      <mesh-id>D000077221</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Calcitonin-gene-related Peptide (Cgrp) Antagonists</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Central Nervous System Agents</category>
      <mesh-id>D002491</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Globulins</category>
      <mesh-id>D005916</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Immunoglobulins</category>
      <mesh-id>D007136</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Immunoproteins</category>
      <mesh-id>D007162</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Nervous System</category>
      <mesh-id>D009420</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Peripheral Nervous System Agents</category>
      <mesh-id>D018373</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Proteins</category>
      <mesh-id>D011506</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Sensory System Agents</category>
      <mesh-id>D018689</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Serum Globulins</category>
      <mesh-id>D012712</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms>
    <affected-organism>Humans and other mammals</affected-organism>
  </affected-organisms>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Injection, solution</form>
      <route>Subcutaneous</route>
      <strength>100 mg/1mL</strength>
    </dosage>
    <dosage>
      <form>Injection, solution</form>
      <route>Subcutaneous</route>
      <strength>120 mg/1mL</strength>
    </dosage>
    <dosage>
      <form>Solution</form>
      <route>Subcutaneous</route>
      <strength>120 mg</strength>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes>
    <atc-code code="N02CX08">
      <level code="N02CX">Other antimigraine preparations</level>
      <level code="N02C">ANTIMIGRAINE PREPARATIONS</level>
      <level code="N02">ANALGESICS</level>
      <level code="N">NERVOUS SYSTEM</level>
    </atc-code>
  </atc-codes>
  <ahfs-codes>
    <ahfs-code>28:32.12</ahfs-code>
  </ahfs-codes>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <fda-label>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/fda_labels/DB14042.pdf?1560281796</fda-label>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00255</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diethylstilbestrol</name>
      <description>Diethylstilbestrol may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00269</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chlorotrianisene</name>
      <description>Chlorotrianisene may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00286</drugbank-id>
      <name>Conjugated estrogens</name>
      <description>Conjugated estrogens may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00655</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estrone</name>
      <description>Estrone may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00783</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol</name>
      <description>Estradiol may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00890</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dienestrol</name>
      <description>Dienestrol may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00977</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethinylestradiol</name>
      <description>Ethinylestradiol may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01357</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mestranol</name>
      <description>Mestranol may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04573</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estriol</name>
      <description>Estriol may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04574</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estrone sulfate</name>
      <description>Estrone sulfate may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04575</drugbank-id>
      <name>Quinestrol</name>
      <description>Quinestrol may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB07931</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hexestrol</name>
      <description>Hexestrol may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09070</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tibolone</name>
      <description>Tibolone may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens, A</name>
      <description>Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens, A may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09318</drugbank-id>
      <name>Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens, B</name>
      <description>Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens, B may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09369</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polyestradiol phosphate</name>
      <description>Polyestradiol phosphate may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09381</drugbank-id>
      <name>Esterified estrogens</name>
      <description>Esterified estrogens may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11478</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zeranol</name>
      <description>Zeranol may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11674</drugbank-id>
      <name>Equol</name>
      <description>Equol may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12487</drugbank-id>
      <name>Promestriene</name>
      <description>Promestriene may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13143</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methallenestril</name>
      <description>Methallenestril may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13386</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epimestrol</name>
      <description>Epimestrol may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13418</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moxestrol</name>
      <description>Moxestrol may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13952</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol acetate</name>
      <description>Estradiol acetate may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13953</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol benzoate</name>
      <description>Estradiol benzoate may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13954</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol cypionate</name>
      <description>Estradiol cypionate may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13956</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estradiol valerate</name>
      <description>Estradiol valerate may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15334</drugbank-id>
      <name>Biochanin A</name>
      <description>Biochanin A may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15335</drugbank-id>
      <name>Formononetin</name>
      <description>Formononetin may increase the thrombogenic activities of Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00002</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cetuximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Cetuximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00028</drugbank-id>
      <name>Human immunoglobulin G</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Human immunoglobulin G is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00043</drugbank-id>
      <name>Omalizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Omalizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00051</drugbank-id>
      <name>Adalimumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Adalimumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00054</drugbank-id>
      <name>Abciximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Abciximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00056</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemtuzumab ozogamicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Gemtuzumab ozogamicin is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00057</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indium In-111 satumomab pendetide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Indium In-111 satumomab pendetide is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00065</drugbank-id>
      <name>Infliximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Infliximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00072</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trastuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Trastuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00073</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rituximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Rituximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00074</drugbank-id>
      <name>Basiliximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Basiliximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00075</drugbank-id>
      <name>Muromonab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Muromonab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00076</drugbank-id>
      <name>Digoxin Immune Fab (Ovine)</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Digoxin Immune Fab (Ovine) is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00078</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibritumomab tiuxetan</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ibritumomab tiuxetan is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00081</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tositumomab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tositumomab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00087</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alemtuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Alemtuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00089</drugbank-id>
      <name>Capromab pendetide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Capromab pendetide is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00095</drugbank-id>
      <name>Efalizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Efalizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00098</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antithymocyte immunoglobulin (rabbit)</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Antithymocyte immunoglobulin (rabbit) is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00108</drugbank-id>
      <name>Natalizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Natalizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00110</drugbank-id>
      <name>Palivizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Palivizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00111</drugbank-id>
      <name>Daclizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Daclizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00112</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bevacizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Bevacizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00113</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m arcitumomab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Technetium Tc-99m arcitumomab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01257</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eculizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Eculizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01269</drugbank-id>
      <name>Panitumumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Panitumumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01270</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ranibizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ranibizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04901</drugbank-id>
      <name>Galiximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galiximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04949</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pexelizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Pexelizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04956</drugbank-id>
      <name>Afelimomab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Afelimomab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04958</drugbank-id>
      <name>Epratuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Epratuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04962</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bectumomab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Bectumomab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04964</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oregovomab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Oregovomab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04988</drugbank-id>
      <name>IGN311</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when IGN311 is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05006</drugbank-id>
      <name>Adecatumumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Adecatumumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05097</drugbank-id>
      <name>Labetuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Labetuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05101</drugbank-id>
      <name>Matuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Matuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05111</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fontolizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Fontolizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05136</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bavituximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Bavituximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05139</drugbank-id>
      <name>CR002</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when CR002 is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05209</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rozrolimupab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Rozrolimupab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05304</drugbank-id>
      <name>Girentuximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Girentuximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05336</drugbank-id>
      <name>Obiltoxaximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Obiltoxaximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05405</drugbank-id>
      <name>XTL-001</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when XTL-001 is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05437</drugbank-id>
      <name>NAV 1800</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when NAV 1800 is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05459</drugbank-id>
      <name>Briakinumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Briakinumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05496</drugbank-id>
      <name>Otelixizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Otelixizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05545</drugbank-id>
      <name>AMG 108</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when AMG 108 is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05550</drugbank-id>
      <name>Iratumumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Iratumumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05555</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enokizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Enokizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05578</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ramucirumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ramucirumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Farletuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Farletuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05656</drugbank-id>
      <name>Veltuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Veltuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05679</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ustekinumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ustekinumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05773</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trastuzumab emtansine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Trastuzumab emtansine is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05793</drugbank-id>
      <name>PRO-542</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when PRO-542 is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05797</drugbank-id>
      <name>TNX-901</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when TNX-901 is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05889</drugbank-id>
      <name>Inotuzumab ozogamicin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Inotuzumab ozogamicin is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05892</drugbank-id>
      <name>RI 624</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when RI 624 is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05915</drugbank-id>
      <name>MYO-029</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when MYO-029 is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05916</drugbank-id>
      <name>CT-011</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when CT-011 is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05941</drugbank-id>
      <name>Leronlimab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Leronlimab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05996</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glembatumumab vedotin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Glembatumumab vedotin is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06043</drugbank-id>
      <name>Olaratumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Olaratumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06049</drugbank-id>
      <name>IPH 2101</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when IPH 2101 is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06050</drugbank-id>
      <name>TB-402</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when TB-402 is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06081</drugbank-id>
      <name>Caplacizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Caplacizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06101</drugbank-id>
      <name>IMC-1C11</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when IMC-1C11 is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06116</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eldelumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Eldelumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06162</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lumiliximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Lumiliximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06168</drugbank-id>
      <name>Canakinumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Canakinumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06186</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ipilimumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ipilimumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06192</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nimotuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Nimotuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06241</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clenoliximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Clenoliximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06273</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tocilizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tocilizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06304</drugbank-id>
      <name>BIIB015</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when BIIB015 is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06305</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sonepcizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sonepcizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06310</drugbank-id>
      <name>Motavizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Motavizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Elotuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Elotuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06318</drugbank-id>
      <name>AVE9633</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when AVE9633 is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06322</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carotuximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Carotuximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06324</drugbank-id>
      <name>XmAb 2513</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when XmAb 2513 is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06342</drugbank-id>
      <name>Coltuximab ravtansine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Coltuximab ravtansine is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06343</drugbank-id>
      <name>Teprotumumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Teprotumumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06360</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lucatumumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Lucatumumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06366</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pertuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Pertuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06371</drugbank-id>
      <name>Siplizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Siplizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06467</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apolizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Apolizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06474</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sibrotuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sibrotuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06550</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bivatuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Bivatuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06557</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lerdelimumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Lerdelimumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06599</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lexatumumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Lexatumumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06602</drugbank-id>
      <name>Reslizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Reslizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06606</drugbank-id>
      <name>Teplizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Teplizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06607</drugbank-id>
      <name>Catumaxomab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Catumaxomab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06612</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mepolizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Mepolizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06643</drugbank-id>
      <name>Denosumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Denosumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06647</drugbank-id>
      <name>Volociximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Volociximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06650</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ofatumumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ofatumumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06674</drugbank-id>
      <name>Golimumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Golimumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08870</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brentuximab vedotin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Brentuximab vedotin is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08879</drugbank-id>
      <name>Belimumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Belimumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08902</drugbank-id>
      <name>Raxibacumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Raxibacumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08904</drugbank-id>
      <name>Certolizumab pegol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Certolizumab pegol is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08935</drugbank-id>
      <name>Obinutuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Obinutuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09029</drugbank-id>
      <name>Secukinumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Secukinumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09033</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vedolizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Vedolizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09035</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nivolumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Nivolumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09036</drugbank-id>
      <name>Siltuximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Siltuximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09037</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pembrolizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Pembrolizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09045</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dulaglutide</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Dulaglutide is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09052</drugbank-id>
      <name>Blinatumomab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Blinatumomab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09057</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anthrax immune globulin human</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Anthrax immune globulin human is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09077</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dinutuximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Dinutuximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09105</drugbank-id>
      <name>Asfotase alfa</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Asfotase alfa is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Idarucizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Idarucizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09302</drugbank-id>
      <name>Alirocumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Alirocumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09303</drugbank-id>
      <name>Evolocumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Evolocumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09312</drugbank-id>
      <name>Antilymphocyte immunoglobulin (horse)</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Antilymphocyte immunoglobulin (horse) is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09331</drugbank-id>
      <name>Daratumumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Daratumumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09559</drugbank-id>
      <name>Necitumumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Necitumumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11569</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ixekizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ixekizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11580</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ravulizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ravulizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Atezolizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Atezolizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11604</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetanus Immune Globulin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tetanus Immune Globulin is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11608</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eftrenonacog alfa</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Eftrenonacog alfa is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11621</drugbank-id>
      <name>Human Varicella-Zoster Immune Globulin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Human Varicella-Zoster Immune Globulin is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11646</drugbank-id>
      <name>Conatumumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Conatumumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11657</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tabalumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tabalumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11680</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ficlatuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ficlatuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11685</drugbank-id>
      <name>Figitumumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Figitumumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11714</drugbank-id>
      <name>Durvalumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Durvalumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11715</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bapineuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Bapineuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11731</drugbank-id>
      <name>Depatuxizumab mafodotin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Depatuxizumab mafodotin is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11746</drugbank-id>
      <name>Onartuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Onartuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11756</drugbank-id>
      <name>Solanezumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Solanezumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11767</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sarilumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sarilumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11771</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tremelimumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tremelimumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11776</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brodalumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Brodalumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11803</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sirukumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sirukumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11826</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lampalizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Lampalizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11834</drugbank-id>
      <name>Guselkumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Guselkumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11840</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dalotuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Dalotuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11849</drugbank-id>
      <name>Emibetuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Emibetuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11850</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ublituximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ublituximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11856</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ligelizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ligelizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11857</drugbank-id>
      <name>Seribantumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Seribantumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11862</drugbank-id>
      <name>Landogrozumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Landogrozumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11866</drugbank-id>
      <name>Romosozumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Romosozumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11884</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vadastuximab Talirine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Vadastuximab Talirine is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11914</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lebrikizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Lebrikizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11930</drugbank-id>
      <name>Varlilumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Varlilumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11945</drugbank-id>
      <name>Avelumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Avelumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11959</drugbank-id>
      <name>Crenezumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Crenezumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11972</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rilotumumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Rilotumumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11976</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anifrolumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Anifrolumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11988</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ocrelizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ocrelizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12023</drugbank-id>
      <name>Benralizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Benralizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12034</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gantenerumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Gantenerumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12053</drugbank-id>
      <name>Visilizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Visilizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12077</drugbank-id>
      <name>Urelumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Urelumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12089</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lorvotuzumab mertansine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Lorvotuzumab mertansine is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12090</drugbank-id>
      <name>Patritumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Patritumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12102</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fulranumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Fulranumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12104</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tarextumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tarextumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12118</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sotatercept</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sotatercept is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12119</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gevokizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Gevokizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12142</drugbank-id>
      <name>Duligotuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Duligotuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12152</drugbank-id>
      <name>Simtuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Simtuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12157</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fasinumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Fasinumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12159</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dupilumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Dupilumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12169</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tralokinumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tralokinumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12189</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etrolizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Etrolizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12202</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zalutumumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Zalutumumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12205</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ganitumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ganitumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12213</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etaracizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Etaracizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12240</drugbank-id>
      <name>Polatuzumab vedotin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Polatuzumab vedotin is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12246</drugbank-id>
      <name>Inclacumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Inclacumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12250</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cixutumumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Cixutumumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12261</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ascrinvacumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ascrinvacumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12274</drugbank-id>
      <name>Aducanumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Aducanumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12281</drugbank-id>
      <name>Luspatercept</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Luspatercept is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12296</drugbank-id>
      <name>GS-5745</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when GS-5745 is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12317</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vanucizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Vanucizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12331</drugbank-id>
      <name>Labetuzumab govitecan</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Labetuzumab govitecan is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12335</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tanezumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tanezumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12342</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ensituximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ensituximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12344</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fezakinumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Fezakinumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12363</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dusigitumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Dusigitumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12396</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fresolimumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Fresolimumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12413</drugbank-id>
      <name>Indusatumab vedotin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Indusatumab vedotin is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12456</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bococizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Bococizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12489</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mirvetuximab Soravtansine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Mirvetuximab Soravtansine is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12498</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mogamulizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Mogamulizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12520</drugbank-id>
      <name>Plozalizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Plozalizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12530</drugbank-id>
      <name>Inebilizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Inebilizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12534</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mavrilimumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Mavrilimumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12560</drugbank-id>
      <name>Blosozumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Blosozumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12584</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bimagrumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Bimagrumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12589</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dacetuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Dacetuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12609</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tovetumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tovetumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12683</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lumretuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Lumretuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12698</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ibalizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ibalizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12701</drugbank-id>
      <name>Intetumumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Intetumumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12718</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carlumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Carlumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12734</drugbank-id>
      <name>Demcizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Demcizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12773</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sifalimumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sifalimumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12775</drugbank-id>
      <name>Abituzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Abituzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12797</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ecromeximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ecromeximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12807</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naptumomab Estafenatox</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Naptumomab Estafenatox is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12815</drugbank-id>
      <name>Crotedumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Crotedumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12820</drugbank-id>
      <name>Concizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Concizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12826</drugbank-id>
      <name>Depatuxizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Depatuxizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12844</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rontalizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Rontalizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12845</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amatuximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Amatuximab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12849</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clazakizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Clazakizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12891</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ozanezumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Ozanezumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12893</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sacituzumab govitecan</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sacituzumab govitecan is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12917</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bimekizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Bimekizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12943</drugbank-id>
      <name>Milatuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Milatuzumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12976</drugbank-id>
      <name>Robatumumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Robatumumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13017</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rovalpituzumab Tesirine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Rovalpituzumab Tesirine is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13037</drugbank-id>
      <name>Namilumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Namilumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13045</drugbank-id>
      <name>Racotumomab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Racotumomab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13073</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tregalizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tregalizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13127</drugbank-id>
      <name>Olokizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Olokizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13140</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bezlotoxumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Bezlotoxumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13375</drugbank-id>
      <name>Edrecolomab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Edrecolomab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13535</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nebacumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Nebacumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13886</drugbank-id>
      <name>Human cytomegalovirus immune globulin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Human cytomegalovirus immune globulin is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13923</drugbank-id>
      <name>Emicizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Emicizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13976</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulesomab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Sulesomab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13979</drugbank-id>
      <name>Besilesomab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Besilesomab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14004</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tildrakizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Tildrakizumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14012</drugbank-id>
      <name>Burosumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Burosumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14039</drugbank-id>
      <name>Erenumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Erenumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14040</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eptinezumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Eptinezumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14041</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fremanezumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Fremanezumab is combined with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14211</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fanolesomab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Fanolesomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14580</drugbank-id>
      <name>BAN-2401</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with BAN-2401.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14597</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lanadelumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Lanadelumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14707</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cemiplimab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Cemiplimab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14724</drugbank-id>
      <name>Emapalumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Emapalumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14762</drugbank-id>
      <name>Risankizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Risankizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14776</drugbank-id>
      <name>Camrelizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Camrelizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14778</drugbank-id>
      <name>Setrusumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Setrusumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14784</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gancotamab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Gancotamab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14809</drugbank-id>
      <name>Anetumab ravtansine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Anetumab ravtansine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14811</drugbank-id>
      <name>Isatuximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Isatuximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14824</drugbank-id>
      <name>Icrucumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Icrucumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14843</drugbank-id>
      <name>Codrituzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Codrituzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14864</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brolucizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Brolucizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14871</drugbank-id>
      <name>Xentuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Xentuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14877</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lintuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Lintuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14891</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vobarilizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Vobarilizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14897</drugbank-id>
      <name>Parsatuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Parsatuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14905</drugbank-id>
      <name>Emactuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Emactuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14907</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bevacizumab zirconium Zr-89</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Bevacizumab zirconium Zr-89.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14908</drugbank-id>
      <name>Refanezumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Refanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14919</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rozanolixizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Rozanolixizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14947</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bermekimab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Bermekimab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14952</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pamrevlumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Pamrevlumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14959</drugbank-id>
      <name>Opicinumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Opicinumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14962</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trastuzumab deruxtecan</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Trastuzumab deruxtecan.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14967</drugbank-id>
      <name>Margetuximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Margetuximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14988</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dalantercept</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Dalantercept.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14997</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pateclizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Pateclizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15014</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gremubamab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Gremubamab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15022</drugbank-id>
      <name>Apomab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Apomab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15044</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tafasitamab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Tafasitamab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15045</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ipafricept</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Ipafricept.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15076</drugbank-id>
      <name>Abrilumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Abrilumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15089</drugbank-id>
      <name>Frovocimab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Frovocimab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15090</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tezepelumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Tezepelumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15101</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tigatuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Tigatuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15104</drugbank-id>
      <name>Telisotuzumab vedotin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Telisotuzumab vedotin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15113</drugbank-id>
      <name>Utomilumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Utomilumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15118</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zolbetuximab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Zolbetuximab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15135</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ponezumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Ponezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15160</drugbank-id>
      <name>Asunercept</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Asunercept.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15172</drugbank-id>
      <name>Suvratoxumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Suvratoxumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15225</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mitazalimab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Mitazalimab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15252</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nemolizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Nemolizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15253</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bleselumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Bleselumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15277</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gedivumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Gedivumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15336</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valanafusp alfa</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Valanafusp alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15349</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sofituzumab vedotin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Sofituzumab vedotin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15354</drugbank-id>
      <name>Evinacumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Evinacumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15363</drugbank-id>
      <name>Istiratumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Istiratumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15383</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pidilizumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Pidilizumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15397</drugbank-id>
      <name>GMA-161</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with GMA-161.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15409</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ladiratuzumab vedotin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Ladiratuzumab vedotin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15415</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tomaralimab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Tomaralimab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15428</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vesencumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Vesencumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15432</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pinatuzumab vedotin</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Pinatuzumab vedotin.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15441</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lulizumab pegol</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Lulizumab pegol.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15443</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lorukafusp alfa</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Lorukafusp alfa.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15453</drugbank-id>
      <name>Naratuximab emtansine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Naratuximab emtansine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15559</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zenocutuzumab</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of adverse effects can be increased when Galcanezumab is combined with Zenocutuzumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated)</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ebola Zaire vaccine (live, attenuated) can be decreased when used in combination with Galcanezumab.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <sequences>
    <sequence format="FASTA">&gt;galcanezumab|Heavy
QVQLVQSGAEVKKPGSSVKVSCKASGYTFGNYWMQWVRQAPGQGLEWMGAIYEGTGKTVY
IQKFADRVTITADKSTSTAYMELSSLRSEDTAVYYCARLSDYVSGFGYWGQGTTVTVSSA
STKGPSVFPLAPCSRSTSESTAALGCLVKDYFPEPVTVSWNSGALTSGVHTFPAVLQSSG
LYSLSSVVTVPSSSLGTKTYTCNVDHKPSNTKVDKRVESKYGPPCPPCPAPEAAGGPSVF
LFPPKPKDTLMISRTPEVTCVVVDVSQEDPEVQFNWYVDGVEVHNAKTKPREEQFNSTYR
VVSVLTVLHQDWLNGKEYKCKVSNKGLPSSIEKTISKAKGQPREPQVYTLPPSQEEMTKN
QVSLTCLVKGFYPSDIAVEWESNGQPENNYKTTPPVLDSDGSFFLYSRLTVDKSRWQEGN
VFSCSVMHEALHNHYTQKSLSLSLG</sequence>
    <sequence format="FASTA">&gt;galcanezumab|Light
DIQMTQSPSSLSASVGDRVTITCRASKDISKYLNWYQQKPGKAPKLLIYYTSGYHSGVPS
RFSGSGSGTDFTLTISSLQPEDFATYYCQQGDALPPTFGGGTKVEIKRTVAAPSVFIFPP
SDEQLKSGTASVVCLLNNFYPREAKVQWKVDNALQSGNSQESVTEQDSKDSTYSLSSTLT
LSKADYEKHKVYACEVTHQGLSSPVTKSFNRGEC</sequence>
  </sequences>
  <experimental-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Weight</kind>
      <value>147000.0</value>
      <source/>
    </property>
  </experimental-properties>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Drugs Product Database (DPD)</resource>
      <identifier>23343</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Wikipedia</resource>
      <identifier>Galcanezumab</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets>
    <target position="1">
      <id>BE0001103</id>
      <name>Calcitonin gene-related peptide 1</name>
      <organism>Humans</organism>
      <actions>
        <action>antibody</action>
      </actions>
      <references>
        <articles>
          <article>
            <ref-id>A33112</ref-id>
            <pubmed-id>29089894</pubmed-id>
            <citation>Monteith D, Collins EC, Vandermeulen C, Van Hecken A, Raddad E, Scherer JC, Grayzel D, Schuetz TJ, de Hoon J: Safety, Tolerability, Pharmacokinetics, and Pharmacodynamics of the CGRP Binding Monoclonal Antibody LY2951742 (Galcanezumab) in Healthy Volunteers. Front Pharmacol. 2017 Oct 17;8:740. doi: 10.3389/fphar.2017.00740. eCollection 2017.</citation>
          </article>
        </articles>
        <textbooks/>
        <links/>
        <attachments/>
      </references>
      <known-action>yes</known-action>
      <polypeptide id="P06881" source="Swiss-Prot">
        <name>Calcitonin gene-related peptide 1</name>
        <general-function>Receptor binding</general-function>
        <specific-function>CGRP induces vasodilation. It dilates a variety of vessels including the coronary, cerebral and systemic vasculature. Its abundance in the CNS also points toward a neurotransmitter or neuromodulator role. It also elevates platelet cAMP.</specific-function>
        <gene-name>CALCA</gene-name>
        <locus>11p15.2-p15.1</locus>
        <cellular-location>Secreted</cellular-location>
        <transmembrane-regions/>
        <signal-regions>1-25</signal-regions>
        <theoretical-pi>9.4</theoretical-pi>
        <molecular-weight>13897.755</molecular-weight>
        <chromosome-location/>
        <organism ncbi-taxonomy-id="9606">Humans</organism>
        <external-identifiers>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>HUGO Gene Nomenclature Committee (HGNC)</resource>
            <identifier>HGNC:1437</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>GenAtlas</resource>
            <identifier>CALCA</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>GenBank Gene Database</resource>
            <identifier>M12667</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>GenBank Protein Database</resource>
            <identifier>179828</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>UniProtKB</resource>
            <identifier>P06881</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>UniProt Accession</resource>
            <identifier>CALCA_HUMAN</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
        </external-identifiers>
        <synonyms>
          <synonym>Alpha-type CGRP</synonym>
          <synonym>CALC1</synonym>
          <synonym>Calcitonin gene-related peptide I</synonym>
          <synonym>CGRP-I</synonym>
        </synonyms>
        <amino-acid-sequence format="FASTA">&gt;lcl|BSEQ0037124|Calcitonin gene-related peptide 1
MGFQKFSPFLALSILVLLQAGSLHAAPFRSALESSPADPATLSEDEARLLLAALVQNYVQ
MKASELEQEQEREGSRIIAQKRACDTATCVTHRLAGLLSRSGGVVKNNFVPTNVGSKAFG
RRRRDLQA</amino-acid-sequence>
        <gene-sequence format="FASTA">&gt;lcl|BSEQ0002194|387 bp
ATGGGCTTCCAAAAGTTCTCCCCCTTCCTGGCTCTCAGCATCTTGGTCCTGTTGCAGGCA
GGCAGCCTCCATGCAGCACCATTCAGGTCTGCCCTGGAGAGCAGCCCAGCAGACCCGGCC
ACGCTCAGTGAGGACGAAGCGCGCCTCCTGCTGGCTGCACTGGTGCAGGACTATGTGCAG
ATGAAGGCCAGTGAGCTGGAGCAGGAGCAAGAGAGAGAGGGCTCCAGAATCATTGCCCAG
AAGAGAGCCTGTGACACTGCCACCTGTGTGACTCATCGGCTGGCAGGCTTGCTGAGCAGA
TCAGGGGGTGTGGTGAAGAACAACTTTGTGCCCACCAATGTGGGTTCCAAAGCCTTTGGC
AGGCGCCGCAGGGACCTTCAAGCCTGA</gene-sequence>
        <pfams>
          <pfam>
            <identifier>PF00214</identifier>
            <name>Calc_CGRP_IAPP</name>
          </pfam>
        </pfams>
        <go-classifiers>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>component</category>
            <description>cytoplasm</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>component</category>
            <description>cytosol</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>component</category>
            <description>extracellular region</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>component</category>
            <description>extracellular space</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>function</category>
            <description>protein complex binding</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>function</category>
            <description>receptor binding</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>activation of adenylate cyclase activity</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>antibacterial humoral response</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>antifungal humoral response</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>cell-cell signaling</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>cytosolic calcium ion homeostasis</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>defense response to Gram-negative bacterium</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>defense response to Gram-positive bacterium</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>endothelial cell migration</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>endothelial cell proliferation</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>G-protein coupled receptor internalization</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>innate immune response</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>leukocyte cell-cell adhesion</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>negative regulation of blood pressure</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>negative regulation of bone resorption</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>negative regulation of calcium ion transport into cytosol</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>negative regulation of osteoclast differentiation</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>neurological system process involved in regulation of systemic arterial blood pressure</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>positive regulation of cAMP biosynthetic process</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>positive regulation of cytosolic calcium ion concentration involved in phospholipase C-activating G-protein coupled signaling pathway</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>positive regulation of interleukin-1 alpha production</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>positive regulation of interleukin-8 production</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>positive regulation of macrophage differentiation</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>positive regulation of vasodilation</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>protein phosphorylation</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>receptor internalization</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>regulation of blood pressure</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>response to yeast</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>vasculature development</description>
          </go-classifier>
        </go-classifiers>
      </polypeptide>
    </target>
    <target position="2">
      <id>BE0002370</id>
      <name>Calcitonin gene-related peptide 2</name>
      <organism>Humans</organism>
      <actions>
        <action>antibody</action>
      </actions>
      <references>
        <articles>
          <article>
            <ref-id>A33112</ref-id>
            <pubmed-id>29089894</pubmed-id>
            <citation>Monteith D, Collins EC, Vandermeulen C, Van Hecken A, Raddad E, Scherer JC, Grayzel D, Schuetz TJ, de Hoon J: Safety, Tolerability, Pharmacokinetics, and Pharmacodynamics of the CGRP Binding Monoclonal Antibody LY2951742 (Galcanezumab) in Healthy Volunteers. Front Pharmacol. 2017 Oct 17;8:740. doi: 10.3389/fphar.2017.00740. eCollection 2017.</citation>
          </article>
        </articles>
        <textbooks/>
        <links/>
        <attachments/>
      </references>
      <known-action>yes</known-action>
      <polypeptide id="P10092" source="Swiss-Prot">
        <name>Calcitonin gene-related peptide 2</name>
        <general-function>Neuropeptide hormone activity</general-function>
        <specific-function>CGRP induces vasodilation. It dilates a variety of vessels including the coronary, cerebral and systemic vasculature. Its abundance in the CNS also points toward a neurotransmitter or neuromodulator role.</specific-function>
        <gene-name>CALCB</gene-name>
        <locus>11p15.2-p15.1</locus>
        <cellular-location>Secreted</cellular-location>
        <transmembrane-regions/>
        <signal-regions>1-25</signal-regions>
        <theoretical-pi>10.73</theoretical-pi>
        <molecular-weight>13705.56</molecular-weight>
        <chromosome-location>11</chromosome-location>
        <organism ncbi-taxonomy-id="9606">Humans</organism>
        <external-identifiers>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>HUGO Gene Nomenclature Committee (HGNC)</resource>
            <identifier>HGNC:1438</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>GenAtlas</resource>
            <identifier>CALCB</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>GenBank Gene Database</resource>
            <identifier>BC092468</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>UniProtKB</resource>
            <identifier>P10092</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
          <external-identifier>
            <resource>UniProt Accession</resource>
            <identifier>CALCB_HUMAN</identifier>
          </external-identifier>
        </external-identifiers>
        <synonyms>
          <synonym>Beta-CGRP</synonym>
          <synonym>Beta-type CGRP</synonym>
          <synonym>CALC2</synonym>
          <synonym>Calcitonin gene-related peptide II</synonym>
          <synonym>CGRP-II</synonym>
        </synonyms>
        <amino-acid-sequence format="FASTA">&gt;lcl|BSEQ0011700|Calcitonin gene-related peptide 2
MGFRKFSPFLALSILVLYQAGSLQAAPFRSALESSPDPATLSKEDARLLLAALVQDYVQM
KASELKQEQETQGSSSAAQKRACNTATCVTHRLAGLLSRSGGMVKSNFVPTNVGSKAFGR
RRRDLQA</amino-acid-sequence>
        <gene-sequence format="FASTA">&gt;lcl|BSEQ0011701|Calcitonin gene-related peptide 2 (CALCB)
ATGGGTTTCCGGAAGTTCTCCCCCTTCCTGGCTCTCAGTATCTTGGTCCTGTACCAGGCG
GGCAGCCTCCAGGCGGCGCCATTCAGGTCTGCCCTGGAGAGCAGCCCAGACCCGGCCACA
CTCAGTAAAGAGGACGCGCGCCTCCTGCTGGCTGCACTGGTGCAGGACTATGTGCAGATG
AAGGCCAGTGAGCTGAAGCAGGAGCAGGAGACACAGGGCTCCAGCTCCGCTGCCCAGAAG
AGAGCCTGCAACACTGCCACCTGTGTGACTCATCGGCTGGCAGGCTTGCTGAGCAGATCA
GGGGGCATGGTGAAGAGCAACTTCGTGCCCACCAATGTGGGTTCCAAAGCCTTTGGCAGG
CGCCGCAGGGACCTTCAAGCCTGA</gene-sequence>
        <pfams>
          <pfam>
            <identifier>PF00214</identifier>
            <name>Calc_CGRP_IAPP</name>
          </pfam>
        </pfams>
        <go-classifiers>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>component</category>
            <description>cell</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>component</category>
            <description>extracellular region</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>function</category>
            <description>neuropeptide hormone activity</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>cellular calcium ion homeostasis</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>mitophagy in response to mitochondrial depolarization</description>
          </go-classifier>
          <go-classifier>
            <category>process</category>
            <description>signal transduction</description>
          </go-classifier>
        </go-classifiers>
      </polypeptide>
    </target>
  </targets>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>