<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2017-06-23" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB13854</drugbank-id>
  <name>Gamolenic acid</name>
  <description>Gamolenic acid, or gamma-linolenic acid (γ-Linolenic acid) or GLA, is an essential fatty acid (EFA) comprised of 18 carbon atoms with three double bonds [F27] that is most commonly found in human milk and other botanical sources [A32848]. It is an omega-6 polyunsaturated fatty acid (PUFA) also referred to as 18:3n-6; 6,9,12-octadecatrienoic acid; and cis-6, cis-9, cis-12- octadecatrienoic acid [F27]. Gamolenic acid is produced minimally in the body as the delta 6-desaturase metabolite of [DB00132]. It is converted to [DB00154], a biosynthetic precursor of monoenoic prostaglandins such as PGE1. While Gamolenic acid is found naturally in the fatty acid fractions of some plant seed oils [F27], [DB11358] and [DB11238] are rich sources of gamolenic acid. Evening primrose oil has been investigated for clinical use in menopausal syndrome, diabetic neuropathy, and breast pain, where gamolenic acid is present at concentrations of 7-14% [F27]. Gamolenic acid may be found in over-the-counter dietary supplements. Gamolenic acid is also found in some fungal sources and also present naturally in the form of triglycerides [F27]. Various clinical indications of gamolenic acid have been studied, including rheumatoid arthritis, atopic eczema, acute respiratory distress syndrome, asthma, premenstrual syndrome, cardiovascular disease, ulcerative colitis, ADHD, cancer, osteoporosis, diabetic neuropathy, and insomnia.</description>
  <cas-number>506-26-3</cas-number>
  <unii>78YC2MAX4O</unii>
  <average-mass>278.4296</average-mass>
  <monoisotopic-mass>278.224580204</monoisotopic-mass>
  <state>liquid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A32848</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>27083549</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Sergeant S, Rahbar E, Chilton FH: Gamma-linolenic acid, Dihommo-gamma linolenic, Eicosanoids and Inflammatory Processes. Eur J Pharmacol. 2016 Aug 15;785:77-86. doi: 10.1016/j.ejphar.2016.04.020. Epub 2016 Apr 12.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A32849</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>9732298</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Fan YY, Chapkin RS: Importance of dietary gamma-linolenic acid in human health and nutrition. J Nutr. 1998 Sep;128(9):1411-4. doi: 10.1093/jn/128.9.1411.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A32850</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>23074118</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Kim DH, Yoo TH, Lee SH, Kang HY, Nam BY, Kwak SJ, Kim JK, Park JT, Han SH, Kang SW: Gamma linolenic acid exerts anti-inflammatory and anti-fibrotic effects in diabetic nephropathy. Yonsei Med J. 2012 Nov 1;53(6):1165-75. doi: 10.3349/ymj.2012.53.6.1165.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A32852</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>26101612</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Chamberlin AJ, Bauer JE: Dietary gamma-linolenic acid supports arachidonic acid accretion and associated Delta-5 desaturase activity in feline uterine but not ovarian tissues. J Nutr Sci. 2014 Oct 13;3:e43. doi: 10.1017/jns.2014.41. eCollection 2014.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A32860</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>8753781</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Hrelia S, Bordoni A, Biagi P, Rossi CA, Bernardi L, Horrobin DF, Pession A: gamma-Linolenic acid supplementation can affect cancer cell proliferation via modification of fatty acid composition. Biochem Biophys Res Commun. 1996 Aug 14;225(2):441-7. doi: 10.1006/bbrc.1996.1192.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A32862</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>9932142</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Kruger MC, Coetzer H, de Winter R, Gericke G, van Papendorp DH: Calcium, gamma-linolenic acid and eicosapentaenoic acid supplementation in senile osteoporosis. Aging (Milano). 1998 Oct;10(5):385-94.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A32863</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>24435467</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Simon D, Eng PA, Borelli S, Kagi R, Zimmermann C, Zahner C, Drewe J, Hess L, Ferrari G, Lautenschlager S, Wuthrich B, Schmid-Grendelmeier P: Gamma-linolenic acid levels correlate with clinical efficacy of evening primrose oil in patients with atopic dermatitis. Adv Ther. 2014 Feb;31(2):180-8. doi: 10.1007/s12325-014-0093-0. Epub 2014 Jan 17.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments>
      <attachment>
        <ref-id>F27</ref-id>
        <title>Gamma-Linolenic Acid (GLA) Monograph - Semantic Scholar</title>
        <url>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/cite_this/attachments/files/000/000/027/original/496215cecef1f527d4787e065f20ccf1e3fe.pdf?1525205244</url>
      </attachment>
    </attachments>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Indicated as a dietary supplement for over-the-counter uses. </indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>Gamolenic acid is converted to PGE1, which exhibits anti-inflammatory, antithrombotic, antiproliferative, and lipid-lowering effects [F27]. PGE1 also induces smooth muscle relaxation and vasodilation. Gamolenic acid is an essential component of membrane phospholipids, including the mitochondrial membrane, where it enhances the the integrity and the fluidity of the membrane [F27]. &#13;
&#13;
**Bone and joint health:** In a pilot study of women with a mean age of 79.5 years and senile osteoporosis, the use of gamolenic acid in combination with calcium and eicosapentaenoic acid was associated with an increase in femoral bone density and lumbar spine density in comparison to placebo, where there were no observable changes [A32862]. In clinical studies of patients with rheumatoid arthritis, treatment with gamolenic acid-containing oils resulted in an improvement in symptoms, measured by joint tenderness counts and scores, joint swelling scores, physician global assessment, and pain [F27]. &#13;
&#13;
**Inflammation:** A study demonstrated that oral administration of gamolenic acid suppressed human T-cell proliferation and activation by interfering with early events in the TcR/CD3-receptor–mediated signal transduction cascade [A32849]. &#13;
&#13;
**Atherosclerosis:** In ApoE genetic knock-out mice, dietary gamolenic acid was shown to reduce the average medial layer thickness of the vessel wall and reduces the size of atherosclerotic lesions [A32849]. &#13;
&#13;
**Diabetic complications:** In a clinical trial of patients with mild diabetic neuropathy or distal diabetic neuropathy, treatment with gamolenic acid was associated with improved symptoms in hot and cold threshold, sensation, tendon reflexes, and muscle strength [F27]. GLA ameliorated the inflammatory profile in diabetic nephropathy in rat studies [A32850]. &#13;
&#13;
**Cancer:** In three human tumor cell lines (the neuroblastoma CHP-212, the tubal carcinoma TG, and the colon carcinoma SW-620), gamolenic acid elicited cytotoxic effects in tumours by blocking cell proliferation following incorporation into malignant cells [A32860]. In both clinical and animal studies of breast cancer, gamolenic acid, in combination with tamoxifen, down-regulated the expression of estrogen receptors [F27]. &#13;
&#13;
**Skin disorders:** In an open study of patients with atopic dermatitis, which is a disorder related to a deficiency of delta-6-desaturase and inefficient conversion of linoleic acid to gamolenic acid, daily administration of gamolenic acid was associated with a significant increase in plasma GLA and DGLA levels in combination with an improvement of clinical signs of atopic dermatitis [A32863].  &#13;
&#13;
**Respiratory disorders:** In patients with acute lung injury or acute respiratory distress syndrome, gamolenic acid was shown to reduce cytokine production and neutrophil recruitment into the lung [A32848]. In patients with atopic asthma, gamolenic acid blocked _ex vivo_ synthesis of leukotrienes from whole blood and isolated neutrophils compared to the placebo group [A32848]. </pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action>Once gamolenic acid (GLA) is absorbed and converted to dihomo-gamolenic acid (DGLA), circulating DGLA fatty acids are converted to several lipid mediators with predominantly anti-inflammatory properties, such as prostaglandin-E1 (PGE1) and 15-HETrE. The anti-inflammatory effects of DGLA are attributed to both the anti-inflammatory properties of DGLA-derived metabolites and the ability of DGLA and its products to compete with arachidonic acid (AA) in the synthesis of pro-inflammatory potent eicosanoid products, such as prostaglandins, thromboxane and leukotrienes [A32848]. Both PGE1 and 15-HETrE are known to suppress inflammation, promote vasodilation, lower blood pressure, inhibit smooth muscle cell proliferation, inhibit platelet aggregation, and exert anti-neoplastic activities [A32848]. PGE1 is a potent vasodilator that binds to surface receptors on smooth muscle cells, increasing intracellular cAMP [F27]. PGE1 is binds to G protein coupled surface PGE (EP) receptors and prostacyclin (IP) receptors as a natural ligand [A32849]. &#13;
&#13;
GLA is proposed to enhance calcium absorption, reduce excretion and increase calcium deposition in bone [A32862]. It is proposed that GLA may suppress tumor growth _in vivo_ by increasing the expression of E-cadherin, a cell-to-cell adhesion molecule that acts as a suppressor of metastasis. Another possible mechanism of tumour suppression is that GLA also reduces tumor-endothelium adhesion, which is a key factor in the establishment of distant metastases, partly by improving gap junction communication within the endothelium [A32849]. By targeting the inflammatory process involved in the pathogenesis of diabetic nephropathy, GLA inhibits the expression of inflammatory mediators that tend be elevated in diabetes, intracellular adhesion molecule-1 (ICAM-1) and monocyte chemoattractant protein-1 (MCP-1), thereby attenuates the recruitment and infiltration of monocytes or macrophages [A32850]. </mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity>Oral TDLO reported in man is 3.14 mg/kg/42D (intermittent) [MSDS]. While limited cases of soft stool, belching, and abdominal bloating have been reported from dietary supplements containing gamolenic acid, daily doses up to 2.8 g were well tolerated [F27]. </toxicity>
  <metabolism>Via elongation mediated by elongase (ELOVL5), gamolenic acid is rapidly converted to dihomo-gamma-linolenic acid (DGLA), which is further cyclooxygenated to prostaglandin E1 (PGE1) via COX-1 or COX-2 enzymatic activity depending on the cell type [A32848]. PGE1 may be metabolized to smaller prostaglandin remnants, primarily dicarboxylic acids, which undergo renal excretion [F27]. DGLA may be converted to 15-(S)-hydroxy-8,11,13-eicosatrienoic acid (15-HETrE) by 15-lipoxygenase enzyme [A32848]. &#13;
&#13;
Although the enzymatic pathway is less predominant relative to ELOVL5 in most cells, DGLA may also be converted to arachidonic acid (AA) via delta-5-desaturate activity [A32852], where hydrogen atoms are selectively removed to create new double bonds F27]. Arachidonic acid is a precursor in the biosynthesis of prostaglandin E2, thromboxanes, and leukotrienes, which are potent inflammatory mediators and play an important role in inflammatory pathways. </metabolism>
  <absorption>The findings from a pharmacokinetic study suggest that therapeutic levels of GLA can be achieved within a week. The fasting plasma GLA levels plateaued within seven days of beginning treatment, regardless of dose [F27]. </absorption>
  <half-life>No pharmacokinetic data available.</half-life>
  <protein-binding>No pharmacokinetic data available.</protein-binding>
  <route-of-elimination>The metabolites of gamolenic acid is expected to undergo renal excretion [F27].</route-of-elimination>
  <volume-of-distribution>No pharmacokinetic data available.</volume-of-distribution>
  <clearance>No pharmacokinetic data available.</clearance>
  <classification>
    <description>This compound belongs to the class of organic compounds known as lineolic acids and derivatives. These are derivatives of lineolic acid. Lineolic acid is a polyunsaturated omega-6 18 carbon long fatty acid, with two CC double bonds at the 9- and 12-positions.</description>
    <direct-parent>Lineolic acids and derivatives</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Lipids and lipid-like molecules</superclass>
    <class>Fatty Acyls</class>
    <subclass>Lineolic acids and derivatives</subclass>
    <alternative-parent>Carbonyl compounds</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Carboxylic acids</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Hydrocarbon derivatives</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Long-chain fatty acids</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Monocarboxylic acids and derivatives</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Organic oxides</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Straight chain fatty acids</alternative-parent>
    <alternative-parent>Unsaturated fatty acids</alternative-parent>
    <substituent>Aliphatic acyclic compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Carbonyl group</substituent>
    <substituent>Carboxylic acid</substituent>
    <substituent>Carboxylic acid derivative</substituent>
    <substituent>Fatty acid</substituent>
    <substituent>Hydrocarbon derivative</substituent>
    <substituent>Long-chain fatty acid</substituent>
    <substituent>Monocarboxylic acid or derivatives</substituent>
    <substituent>Octadecanoid</substituent>
    <substituent>Organic oxide</substituent>
    <substituent>Organic oxygen compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Organooxygen compound</substituent>
    <substituent>Straight chain fatty acid</substituent>
    <substituent>Unsaturated fatty acid</substituent>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">(6,9,12)-linolenic acid</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">(6Z,9Z,12Z)-Octadecatrienoic acid</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">(Z,Z,Z)-6,9,12-octadecatrienoic acid</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">18:3 (n-6)</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">6-cis,9-cis,12-cis-octadecatrienoic acid</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">6,9,12-Octadecatrienoic acid</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">all-cis-6,9,12-octadecatrienoic acid</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">gamma-Linolenic acid</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">gamoleic acid</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">GLA</synonym>
    <synonym language="german" coder="">Octadeca-6,9,12-triensäure</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">γ-linolenic acid</synonym>
    <synonym language="german" coder="">γ-Linolensäure</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>Beta-carotene 10000I.U. With Borage Oil Cap</name>
      <labeller>Jamieson Laboratories Ltd</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>02011425</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1993-12-31</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>1997-08-13</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Capsule</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Oral</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>true</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Bio-efa Borage Gla 240 Cap</name>
      <labeller>Pge Canada (86) Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>00756407</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1989-12-31</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2006-06-19</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Capsule</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Oral</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>true</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Bio-efa Borage Gla 90 Cap</name>
      <labeller>Pge Canada (86) Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>00756385</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1989-12-31</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2006-06-19</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Capsule</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Oral</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>true</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Borage Oil Capsules</name>
      <labeller>Bioforce Canada Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>01986333</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1994-12-31</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>1999-10-14</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Capsule</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Oral</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>true</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Borage Oil Capsules</name>
      <labeller>General Nutrition Canada Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>02183226</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2001-10-15</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2009-08-05</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Capsule</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Oral</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>true</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Evening Primrose Oil Cap 500mg W Vit E</name>
      <labeller>Stanley Pharmaceuticals, A Division Of Vita Health Products Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>00689076</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1990-12-31</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2002-07-31</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Capsule</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Oral</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>true</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Gla 130 Primrose Oil</name>
      <labeller>Seroyal International Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>02148137</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1996-01-31</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2007-08-02</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Capsule</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Oral</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>true</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Hi-GA Evening Primerose Oil Liq</name>
      <labeller>Hi Ga Health Inc.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>01923765</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1991-12-31</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>1997-06-10</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Liquid</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Oral</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>true</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Nuprimol Cap</name>
      <labeller>Nu Life Nutrition Ltd.</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>02010666</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1997-09-15</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2005-03-15</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Capsule</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Oral</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>true</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
    <product>
      <name>Pro-gla Caps</name>
      <labeller>Professional Health Products</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code/>
      <dpd-id>00757551</dpd-id>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>1989-12-31</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on>2003-08-25</ended-marketing-on>
      <dosage-form>Capsule</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Oral</route>
      <fda-application-number/>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>true</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>Canada</country>
      <source>DPD</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>Pro-gla Caps</name>
      <ingredients>Gamolenic acid + Vitamin E</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Evening Primrose Oil Cap 500mg W Vit E</name>
      <ingredients>Gamolenic acid + Linoleic acid + Vitamin E</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Hi-GA Evening Primerose Oil Liq</name>
      <ingredients>Gamolenic acid + Linoleic acid</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Beta-carotene 10000I.U. With Borage Oil Cap</name>
      <ingredients>Beta carotene + Gamolenic acid</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Borage Oil Capsules</name>
      <ingredients>Borage oil + Gamolenic acid + Linoleic acid</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Nuprimol Cap</name>
      <ingredients>D-alpha-Tocopherol acetate + Gamolenic acid + Linoleic acid + Oleic Acid</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Gla 130 Primrose Oil</name>
      <ingredients>Gamolenic acid + Linoleic acid + Oleic Acid</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Borage Oil Capsules</name>
      <ingredients>Gamolenic acid + Linoleic acid + Oleic Acid + Palmitic Acid</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Bio-efa Borage Gla 90 Cap</name>
      <ingredients>alpha-Linolenic acid + Gamolenic acid + Linoleic acid + Vitamin E</ingredients>
    </mixture>
    <mixture>
      <name>Bio-efa Borage Gla 240 Cap</name>
      <ingredients>Gamolenic acid + Linoleic acid + Vitamin E</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Agents that reduce seizure threshold</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Dermatologicals</category>
      <mesh-id>D003879</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Fatty Acids</category>
      <mesh-id>D005227</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Fatty Acids, Essential</category>
      <mesh-id>D005228</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Fatty Acids, Omega-6</category>
      <mesh-id>D043371</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Fatty Acids, Unsaturated</category>
      <mesh-id>D005231</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Linolenic Acids</category>
      <mesh-id>D008042</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Lipids</category>
      <mesh-id>D008055</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Liquid</form>
      <route>Oral</route>
      <strength/>
    </dosage>
    <dosage>
      <form>Capsule</form>
      <route>Oral</route>
      <strength/>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes>
    <atc-code code="D11AX02">
      <level code="D11AX">Other dermatologicals</level>
      <level code="D11A">OTHER DERMATOLOGICAL PREPARATIONS</level>
      <level code="D11">OTHER DERMATOLOGICAL PREPARATIONS</level>
      <level code="D">DERMATOLOGICALS</level>
    </atc-code>
    <atc-code code="D11AX52">
      <level code="D11AX">Other dermatologicals</level>
      <level code="D11A">OTHER DERMATOLOGICAL PREPARATIONS</level>
      <level code="D11">OTHER DERMATOLOGICAL PREPARATIONS</level>
      <level code="D">DERMATOLOGICALS</level>
    </atc-code>
  </atc-codes>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <msds>//s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/drugbank/msds/DB13854.pdf?1525275038</msds>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00186</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lorazepam</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Lorazepam can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00230</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pregabalin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Pregabalin can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00241</drugbank-id>
      <name>Butalbital</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Butalbital can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00252</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenytoin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Phenytoin can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00273</drugbank-id>
      <name>Topiramate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Topiramate can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00312</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pentobarbital</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Pentobarbital can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00313</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valproic acid</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Valproic acid can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00347</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trimethadione</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Trimethadione can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00349</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clobazam</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Clobazam can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00418</drugbank-id>
      <name>Secobarbital</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Secobarbital can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00463</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metharbital</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Metharbital can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00474</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methohexital</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Methohexital can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00532</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mephenytoin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Mephenytoin can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00555</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lamotrigine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Lamotrigine can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00564</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbamazepine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Carbamazepine can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00593</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethosuximide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ethosuximide can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00599</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiopental</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Thiopental can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00617</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paramethadione</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Paramethadione can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00628</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clorazepic acid</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Clorazepic acid can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00653</drugbank-id>
      <name>Magnesium sulfate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Magnesium sulfate can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00697</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tizanidine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Tizanidine can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00740</drugbank-id>
      <name>Riluzole</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Riluzole can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00754</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethotoin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ethotoin can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00776</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxcarbazepine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Oxcarbazepine can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00794</drugbank-id>
      <name>Primidone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Primidone can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00819</drugbank-id>
      <name>Acetazolamide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Acetazolamide can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00829</drugbank-id>
      <name>Diazepam</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Diazepam can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00832</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phensuximide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Phensuximide can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00837</drugbank-id>
      <name>Progabide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Progabide can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00849</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylphenobarbital</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Methylphenobarbital can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00906</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiagabine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Tiagabine can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00909</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zonisamide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Zonisamide can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00949</drugbank-id>
      <name>Felbamate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Felbamate can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00962</drugbank-id>
      <name>Zaleplon</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Zaleplon can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00996</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gabapentin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Gabapentin can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01068</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clonazepam</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Clonazepam can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01080</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vigabatrin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Vigabatrin can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01121</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenacemide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Phenacemide can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01154</drugbank-id>
      <name>Thiamylal</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Thiamylal can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01174</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenobarbital</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Phenobarbital can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01202</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levetiracetam</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Levetiracetam can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01215</drugbank-id>
      <name>Estazolam</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Estazolam can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01320</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fosphenytoin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Fosphenytoin can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01351</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amobarbital</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Amobarbital can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01355</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hexobarbital</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Hexobarbital can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01483</drugbank-id>
      <name>Barbital</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Barbital can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01511</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delorazepam</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Delorazepam can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nitrazepam</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Nitrazepam can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02207</drugbank-id>
      <name>7-Nitroindazole</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of 7-Nitroindazole can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04165</drugbank-id>
      <name>Valpromide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Valpromide can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04841</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flunarizine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Flunarizine can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04953</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ezogabine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ezogabine can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05246</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methsuximide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Methsuximide can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05541</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brivaracetam</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Brivaracetam can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06201</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rufinamide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Rufinamide can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lacosamide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Lacosamide can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06458</drugbank-id>
      <name>Remacemide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Remacemide can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06470</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clomethiazole</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Clomethiazole can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06512</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deramciclane</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Deramciclane can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06527</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tramiprosate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Tramiprosate can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06554</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gaboxadol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Gaboxadol can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08329</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sulthiame</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Sulthiame can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08883</drugbank-id>
      <name>Perampanel</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Perampanel can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08954</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ifenprodil</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ifenprodil can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09001</drugbank-id>
      <name>Barbexaclone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Barbexaclone can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09011</drugbank-id>
      <name>Beclamide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Beclamide can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09061</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cannabidiol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Cannabidiol can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09117</drugbank-id>
      <name>Paraldehyde</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Paraldehyde can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09118</drugbank-id>
      <name>Stiripentol</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Stiripentol can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB09119</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eslicarbazepine acetate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eslicarbazepine acetate can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11400</drugbank-id>
      <name>Doramectin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Doramectin can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11549</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tiletamine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Tiletamine can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11859</drugbank-id>
      <name>Brexanolone</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Brexanolone can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11868</drugbank-id>
      <name>Etiracetam</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Etiracetam can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12131</drugbank-id>
      <name>Vinpocetine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Vinpocetine can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12338</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carisbamate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Carisbamate can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13362</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pheneturide</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Pheneturide can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13396</drugbank-id>
      <name>Neocitrullamon</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Neocitrullamon can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13437</drugbank-id>
      <name>Medazepam</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Medazepam can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13455</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenibut</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Phenibut can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13799</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ethadione</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Ethadione can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14050</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cannabidivarin</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Cannabidivarin can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB14575</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eslicarbazepine</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Eslicarbazepine can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB15203</drugbank-id>
      <name>JNJ-26489112</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of JNJ-26489112 can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06119</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cenobamate</name>
      <description>The therapeutic efficacy of Cenobamate can be decreased when used in combination with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11640</drugbank-id>
      <name>Amifampridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of seizure can be increased when Gamolenic acid is combined with Amifampridine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06637</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dalfampridine</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of seizure can be increased when Gamolenic acid is combined with Dalfampridine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01156</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bupropion</name>
      <description>The risk or severity of seizure can be increased when Bupropion is combined with Gamolenic acid.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <calculated-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>6.59</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logS</kind>
      <value>-6</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Water Solubility</kind>
      <value>2.54e-04 g/l</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>6.06</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>(6Z,9Z,12Z)-octadeca-6,9,12-trienoic acid</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Traditional IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>gamma linolenic acid</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Weight</kind>
      <value>278.4296</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Monoisotopic Weight</kind>
      <value>278.224580204</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>SMILES</kind>
      <value>CCCCC\C=C/C\C=C/C\C=C/CCCCC(O)=O</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Formula</kind>
      <value>C18H30O2</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChI</kind>
      <value>InChI=1S/C18H30O2/c1-2-3-4-5-6-7-8-9-10-11-12-13-14-15-16-17-18(19)20/h6-7,9-10,12-13H,2-5,8,11,14-17H2,1H3,(H,19,20)/b7-6-,10-9-,13-12-</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChIKey</kind>
      <value>VZCCETWTMQHEPK-QNEBEIHSSA-N</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polar Surface Area (PSA)</kind>
      <value>37.3</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Refractivity</kind>
      <value>89.64</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polarizability</kind>
      <value>33.8</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rotatable Bond Count</kind>
      <value>13</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Acceptor Count</kind>
      <value>2</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Donor Count</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest acidic)</kind>
      <value>4.92</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Physiological Charge</kind>
      <value>-1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Number of Rings</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Bioavailability</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rule of Five</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Ghose Filter</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>MDDR-Like Rule</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
  </calculated-properties>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Drugs Product Database (DPD)</resource>
      <identifier>1350</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEBI</resource>
      <identifier>28661</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>KEGG Compound</resource>
      <identifier>C06426</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>KEGG Drug</resource>
      <identifier>D07213</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChemSpider</resource>
      <identifier>4444436</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>BindingDB</resource>
      <identifier>50269532</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>Wikipedia</resource>
      <identifier>Gamma-Linolenic_acid</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChEMBL</resource>
      <identifier>CHEMBL464982</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions>
    <reaction>
      <sequence>1</sequence>
      <left-element>
        <drugbank-id>DB13854</drugbank-id>
        <name>Gamolenic acid</name>
      </left-element>
      <right-element>
        <drugbank-id>DB00154</drugbank-id>
        <name>Dihomo-gamma-linolenic acid</name>
      </right-element>
      <enzymes>
        <enzyme>
          <drugbank-id>BE0009375</drugbank-id>
          <name>Elongation of very long chain fatty acids protein 5</name>
          <uniprot-id>Q9NYP7</uniprot-id>
        </enzyme>
      </enzymes>
    </reaction>
    <reaction>
      <sequence>2</sequence>
      <left-element>
        <drugbank-id>DB00154</drugbank-id>
        <name>Dihomo-gamma-linolenic acid</name>
      </left-element>
      <right-element>
        <drugbank-id>DBMET02086</drugbank-id>
        <name>Prostaglandin E1</name>
      </right-element>
      <enzymes>
        <enzyme>
          <drugbank-id>BE0000309</drugbank-id>
          <name>Arachidonate 15-lipoxygenase</name>
          <uniprot-id>P16050</uniprot-id>
        </enzyme>
        <enzyme>
          <drugbank-id>BE0000017</drugbank-id>
          <name>Prostaglandin G/H synthase 1</name>
          <uniprot-id>P23219</uniprot-id>
        </enzyme>
        <enzyme>
          <drugbank-id>BE0000262</drugbank-id>
          <name>Prostaglandin G/H synthase 2</name>
          <uniprot-id>P35354</uniprot-id>
        </enzyme>
      </enzymes>
    </reaction>
    <reaction>
      <sequence>2</sequence>
      <left-element>
        <drugbank-id>DB00154</drugbank-id>
        <name>Dihomo-gamma-linolenic acid</name>
      </left-element>
      <right-element>
        <drugbank-id>DBMET02087</drugbank-id>
        <name>15-HETrE</name>
      </right-element>
      <enzymes>
        <enzyme>
          <drugbank-id>BE0000309</drugbank-id>
          <name>Arachidonate 15-lipoxygenase</name>
          <uniprot-id>P16050</uniprot-id>
        </enzyme>
        <enzyme>
          <drugbank-id>BE0000017</drugbank-id>
          <name>Prostaglandin G/H synthase 1</name>
          <uniprot-id>P23219</uniprot-id>
        </enzyme>
        <enzyme>
          <drugbank-id>BE0000262</drugbank-id>
          <name>Prostaglandin G/H synthase 2</name>
          <uniprot-id>P35354</uniprot-id>
        </enzyme>
      </enzymes>
    </reaction>
    <reaction>
      <sequence>2</sequence>
      <left-element>
        <drugbank-id>DB00154</drugbank-id>
        <name>Dihomo-gamma-linolenic acid</name>
      </left-element>
      <right-element>
        <drugbank-id>DB04557</drugbank-id>
        <name>Arachidonic Acid</name>
      </right-element>
      <enzymes>
        <enzyme>
          <drugbank-id>BE0000888</drugbank-id>
          <name>Fatty acid desaturase 1</name>
          <uniprot-id>O60427</uniprot-id>
        </enzyme>
      </enzymes>
    </reaction>
    <reaction>
      <sequence>3</sequence>
      <left-element>
        <drugbank-id>DB04557</drugbank-id>
        <name>Arachidonic Acid</name>
      </left-element>
      <right-element>
        <drugbank-id>DB00917</drugbank-id>
        <name>Dinoprostone</name>
      </right-element>
      <enzymes>
        <enzyme>
          <drugbank-id>BE0000017</drugbank-id>
          <name>Prostaglandin G/H synthase 1</name>
          <uniprot-id>P23219</uniprot-id>
        </enzyme>
        <enzyme>
          <drugbank-id>BE0000262</drugbank-id>
          <name>Prostaglandin G/H synthase 2</name>
          <uniprot-id>P35354</uniprot-id>
        </enzyme>
        <enzyme>
          <drugbank-id>BE0001640</drugbank-id>
          <name>Phospholipase A2, membrane associated</name>
          <uniprot-id>P14555</uniprot-id>
        </enzyme>
      </enzymes>
    </reaction>
  </reactions>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>