<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2018-07-03" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB14193</drugbank-id>
  <name>Ditiocarb Zinc</name>
  <description>Ditiocarb Zinc, also known as Diethyldithiocarbamic acid zinc salt, is a known chelator for copper and zinc. It also a dermatological sensitizer and allergen.&#13;
&#13;
Sensitivity to Ditiocarb Zinc may be identified with a clinical patch test.</description>
  <cas-number>14324-55-1</cas-number>
  <unii>ICW4708Z8G</unii>
  <average-mass>365.94</average-mass>
  <monoisotopic-mass>364.011375</monoisotopic-mass>
  <groups>
    <group>approved</group>
    <group>experimental</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Ditiocarb Zinc is approved for use within allergenic epicutaneous patch tests which are indicated for use as an aid in the diagnosis of allergic contact dermatitis (ACD) in persons 6 years of age and older.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action/>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Bis(diethyldithiocarbamato)zinc</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">DEDTC</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Diethyldithiocarbamic acid zinc salt</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Ethazate</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Ethyl cymate</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Ethyl zimate</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Ethyl Ziram</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Ethylzimate</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Zinc Diethyldithiocarbamate</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Zinc N,N-diethyldithiocarbamate</synonym>
    <synonym language="english" coder="">Zinc, bis(diethylcarbamodithioato-S,S')-</synonym>
  </synonyms>
  <products>
    <product>
      <name>T.R.U.E. Test Thin-Layer Rapid Use Patch Test</name>
      <labeller>SmartPractice Denmark ApS</labeller>
      <ndc-id/>
      <ndc-product-code>67334-0457</ndc-product-code>
      <dpd-id/>
      <ema-product-code/>
      <ema-ma-number/>
      <started-marketing-on>2012-03-01</started-marketing-on>
      <ended-marketing-on/>
      <dosage-form>Kit</dosage-form>
      <strength/>
      <route>Cutaneous</route>
      <fda-application-number>BLA103738</fda-application-number>
      <generic>false</generic>
      <over-the-counter>false</over-the-counter>
      <approved>true</approved>
      <country>US</country>
      <source>FDA NDC</source>
    </product>
  </products>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures>
    <mixture>
      <name>T.R.U.E. Test Thin-Layer Rapid Use Patch Test</name>
      <ingredients>2-mercaptobenzothiazole + 2,2'-Dibenzothiazyl disulfide + 4-(Isopropylamino)diphenylamine + alpha-Amyl cinnamaldehyde + Bacitracin + Balsam of Peru + Benzocaine + Benzylparaben + Bisphenol A diglycidyl ether + Bromothalonil + Bronopol + Budesonide + Butylparaben + Chlorquinaldol + Cinchocaine + Cinnamaldehyde + Cinnamyl alcohol + Clioquinol + Cobalt chloride + Diazolidinylurea + Dichromate + Dipentamethylenethiuram disulfide + Diphenylguanidine + Disperse Blue 106 + Disulfiram + Ditiocarb Zinc + Ethyl hydroxybenzoate + Ethylenediamine + Eugenol + Evernia prunastri + Formaldehyde + Geraniol + Hydrocortisone butyrate + Hydroxycitronellal + Imidurea + Isoeugenol + Lanolin alcohols + Methylchloroisothiazolinone + Methylparaben + Morpholinylmercaptobenzothiazole + N-Cyclohexyl-N'-phenyl-1,4-phenylenediamine + N,N'-diphenyl-1,4-phenylenediamine + Neomycin + Nickel sulfate + p-Phenylenediamine + P-Tert-Butylphenol-Formaldehyde Resin (Low Molecular Weight) + Parthenolide + Propylparaben + Quaternium-15 + Rosin + Sodium aurotiosulfate + Tetracaine + Tetramethylthiuram monosulfide + Thimerosal + Thiohexam + Thiram + Tixocortol + Zinc Dibutyldithiocarbamate</ingredients>
    </mixture>
  </mixtures>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories>
    <category>
      <category>Agents for Treatment of Hemorrhoids and Anal Fissures for Topical Use</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Allergens</category>
      <mesh-id>D000485</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Cell-mediated Immunity</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Compounds used in a research, industrial, or household setting</category>
      <mesh-id>D020313</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Increased Histamine Release</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Metal cations</category>
      <mesh-id>D002412</mesh-id>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Metal divalent cations</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Standardized Chemical Allergen</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Vasoprotectives</category>
      <mesh-id/>
    </category>
    <category>
      <category>Zinc Compounds</category>
      <mesh-id>D017967</mesh-id>
    </category>
  </categories>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages>
    <dosage>
      <form>Kit</form>
      <route>Cutaneous</route>
      <strength/>
    </dosage>
  </dosages>
  <atc-codes>
    <atc-code code="C05AX04">
      <level code="C05AX">Other agents for treatment of hemorrhoids and anal fissures for topical use</level>
      <level code="C05A">AGENTS FOR TREATMENT OF HEMORRHOIDS AND ANAL FISSURES FOR TOPICAL USE</level>
      <level code="C05">VASOPROTECTIVES</level>
      <level code="C">CARDIOVASCULAR SYSTEM</level>
    </atc-code>
  </atc-codes>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01586</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ursodeoxycholic acid</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ursodeoxycholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02123</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glycochenodeoxycholic Acid</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Glycochenodeoxycholic Acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02659</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cholic Acid</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Cholic Acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB02691</drugbank-id>
      <name>Glycocholic acid</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Glycocholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB03619</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deoxycholic acid</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Deoxycholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04348</drugbank-id>
      <name>Taurocholic acid</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Taurocholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05990</drugbank-id>
      <name>Obeticholic acid</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Obeticholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06777</drugbank-id>
      <name>Chenodeoxycholic acid</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Chenodeoxycholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08833</drugbank-id>
      <name>Taurochenodeoxycholic acid</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Taurochenodeoxycholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08834</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tauroursodeoxycholic acid</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Tauroursodeoxycholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08857</drugbank-id>
      <name>Bamet-UD2</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Bamet-UD2 resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11622</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dehydrocholic acid</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dehydrocholic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11789</drugbank-id>
      <name>Hyodeoxycholic Acid</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Hyodeoxycholic Acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06210</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eltrombopag</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Eltrombopag resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Raltegravir</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Raltegravir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Halofantrine</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Halofantrine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06824</drugbank-id>
      <name>Triethylenetetramine</name>
      <description>The serum concentration of Ditiocarb Zinc can be decreased when it is combined with Triethylenetetramine.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00218</drugbank-id>
      <name>Moxifloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Moxifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00365</drugbank-id>
      <name>Grepafloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Grepafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00467</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enoxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Enoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00487</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pefloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pefloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00537</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ciprofloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ciprofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00685</drugbank-id>
      <name>Trovafloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Trovafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00779</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nalidixic acid</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Nalidixic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00817</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rosoxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rosoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00827</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cinoxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Cinoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00978</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lomefloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Lomefloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01044</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gatifloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Gatifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01059</drugbank-id>
      <name>Norfloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Norfloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01137</drugbank-id>
      <name>Levofloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Levofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01155</drugbank-id>
      <name>Gemifloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Gemifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01165</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ofloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01208</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sparfloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sparfloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01405</drugbank-id>
      <name>Temafloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Temafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB04576</drugbank-id>
      <name>Fleroxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Fleroxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB05488</drugbank-id>
      <name>Technetium Tc-99m ciprofloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Technetium Tc-99m ciprofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06160</drugbank-id>
      <name>Garenoxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Garenoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB06600</drugbank-id>
      <name>Nemonoxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Nemonoxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08972</drugbank-id>
      <name>Flumequine</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Flumequine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11404</drugbank-id>
      <name>Enrofloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Enrofloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11443</drugbank-id>
      <name>Orbifloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Orbifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11491</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sarafloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sarafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11511</drugbank-id>
      <name>Difloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Difloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11774</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pazufloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pazufloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11892</drugbank-id>
      <name>Prulifloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Prulifloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB11943</drugbank-id>
      <name>Delafloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Delafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13261</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sitafloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sitafloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13627</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxolinic acid</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Oxolinic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13772</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rufloxacin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rufloxacin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13823</drugbank-id>
      <name>Pipemidic acid</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Pipemidic acid resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00256</drugbank-id>
      <name>Lymecycline</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Lymecycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00453</drugbank-id>
      <name>Clomocycline</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Clomocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00560</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tigecycline</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Tigecycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00595</drugbank-id>
      <name>Oxytetracycline</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Oxytetracycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00618</drugbank-id>
      <name>Demeclocycline</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Demeclocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00759</drugbank-id>
      <name>Tetracycline</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Tetracycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00931</drugbank-id>
      <name>Metacycline</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Metacycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01017</drugbank-id>
      <name>Minocycline</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Minocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01301</drugbank-id>
      <name>Rolitetracycline</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Rolitetracycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12035</drugbank-id>
      <name>Sarecycline</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Sarecycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12329</drugbank-id>
      <name>Eravacycline</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Eravacycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB12455</drugbank-id>
      <name>Omadacycline</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Omadacycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13092</drugbank-id>
      <name>Meclocycline</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Meclocycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB13264</drugbank-id>
      <name>Penimepicycline</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Penimepicycline resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00252</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenytoin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Phenytoin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00532</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mephenytoin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Mephenytoin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00564</drugbank-id>
      <name>Carbamazepine</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Carbamazepine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00849</drugbank-id>
      <name>Methylphenobarbital</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Methylphenobarbital resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01174</drugbank-id>
      <name>Phenobarbital</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Phenobarbital resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01415</drugbank-id>
      <name>Ceftibuten</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Ceftibuten resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB00567</drugbank-id>
      <name>Cephalexin</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Cephalexin resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08826</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deferiprone</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Deferiprone resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB08930</drugbank-id>
      <name>Dolutegravir</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Dolutegravir resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01609</drugbank-id>
      <name>Deferasirox</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Deferasirox resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
    <drug-interaction>
      <drugbank-id>DB01071</drugbank-id>
      <name>Mequitazine</name>
      <description>Ditiocarb Zinc can cause a decrease in the absorption of Mequitazine resulting in a reduced serum concentration and potentially a decrease in efficacy.</description>
    </drug-interaction>
  </drug-interactions>
  <calculated-properties>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>2.52</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logS</kind>
      <value>-1.3</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Water Solubility</kind>
      <value>1.92e+01 g/l</value>
      <source>ALOGPS</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>logP</kind>
      <value>2.52</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>2,6-bis(diethylamino)-1lambda4,3,5lambda4,7-tetrathia-4-zincaspiro[3.3]hepta-1,5-diene-4,4-bis(ylium)-3,7-diuide</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Traditional IUPAC Name</kind>
      <value>2,6-bis(diethylamino)-1lambda4,3,5lambda4,7-tetrathia-4-zincaspiro[3.3]hepta-1,5-diene-4,4-bis(ylium)-3,7-diuide</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Weight</kind>
      <value>365.94</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Monoisotopic Weight</kind>
      <value>364.011375</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>SMILES</kind>
      <value>CCN(CC)C1=S[Zn++]2([SH-]1)[SH-]C(=S2)N(CC)CC</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Molecular Formula</kind>
      <value>C10H24N2S4Zn</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChI</kind>
      <value>InChI=1S/2C5H11NS2.Zn/c2*1-3-6(4-2)5(7)8;/h2*3-4H2,1-2H3,(H,7,8);/q;;-2/p+2</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>InChIKey</kind>
      <value>NRKWVSAGIOWUJK-UHFFFAOYSA-P</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polar Surface Area (PSA)</kind>
      <value>6.48</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Refractivity</kind>
      <value>80</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Polarizability</kind>
      <value>37.64</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rotatable Bond Count</kind>
      <value>4</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Acceptor Count</kind>
      <value>2</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>H Bond Donor Count</kind>
      <value>4</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest acidic)</kind>
      <value>-1.3</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>pKa (strongest basic)</kind>
      <value>17</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Physiological Charge</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Number of Rings</kind>
      <value>2</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Bioavailability</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Rule of Five</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>Ghose Filter</kind>
      <value>1</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
    <property>
      <kind>MDDR-Like Rule</kind>
      <value>0</value>
      <source>ChemAxon</source>
    </property>
  </calculated-properties>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>ChemSpider</resource>
      <identifier>60597427</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>