<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-11-18" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB06129</drugbank-id>
  <name>SVV-001</name>
  <description>SVV-001 is investigated for use/treatment in cancer/tumors and lung cancer. SVV-001 is a solid. SVV-001 (Seneca Valley Virus) is a novel native picornavirus being developed as a systemically deliverable oncolytic virus for treatment of human cancers with neuroendocrine features. SVV-001 has also demonstrated cancer-killing specificity 10,000 times higher than that of traditional chemotherapeutics with no overt toxicity at doses one million times higher than effective doses in mice.&#13;
</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3975</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>18006805</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Wadhwa L, Hurwitz MY, Chevez-Barrios P, Hurwitz RL: Treatment of invasive retinoblastoma in a murine model using an oncolytic picornavirus. Cancer Res. 2007 Nov 15;67(22):10653-6.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3976</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17971529</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Reddy PS, Burroughs KD, Hales LM, Ganesh S, Jones BH, Idamakanti N, Hay C, Li SS, Skele KL, Vasko AJ, Yang J, Watkins DN, Rudin CM, Hallenbeck PL: Seneca Valley virus, a systemically deliverable oncolytic picornavirus, and the treatment of neuroendocrine cancers. J Natl Cancer Inst. 2007 Nov 7;99(21):1623-33. Epub 2007 Oct 30.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in cancer/tumors (unspecified) and lung cancer.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>SVV-001 has oncolytic activity against adult tumors with neuroendocrine features but is not harmful to normal human cells. It has potent cytolytic activity and high selectivity for tumor cell lines having neuroendocrine properties versus adult normal cells. Systemically administered SVV-001 has potential for the treatment of metastatic neuroendocrine cancers.</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action/>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910338</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>