<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="biotech" created="2007-11-18" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05776</drugbank-id>
  <name>IC41</name>
  <description>IC41 is a therapeutic peptide vaccine. It is being devloped by Intercell AG for the treatment of hepatitis C. The vaccine consists of five synthetic peptides (IPEP83, 84, 87, 89,1426) harboring HCV CD4 and CD8 T-cell epitopes and the synthetic adjuvant poly-L-arginine. </description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3767</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>17686555</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Schlaphoff V, Klade CS, Jilma B, Jelovcan SB, Cornberg M, Tauber E, Manns MP, Wedemeyer H: Functional and phenotypic characterization of peptide-vaccine-induced HCV-specific CD8+ T cells in healthy individuals and chronic hepatitis C patients. Vaccine. 2007 Sep 17;25(37-38):6793-806. Epub 2007 Jun 29.</citation>
      </article>
      <article>
        <ref-id>A3768</ref-id>
        <pubmed-id>16581161</pubmed-id>
        <citation>Firbas C, Jilma B, Tauber E, Buerger V, Jelovcan S, Lingnau K, Buschle M, Frisch J, Klade CS: Immunogenicity and safety of a novel therapeutic hepatitis C virus (HCV) peptide vaccine: a randomized, placebo controlled trial for dose optimization in 128 healthy subjects. Vaccine. 2006 May 15;24(20):4343-53. Epub 2006 Mar 20.</citation>
      </article>
    </articles>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in hepatitis (viral, C).</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics>IC41 is able of inducing a significant proliferative response in chronic HCV patients. IC41 can induce interferon gamma secreting T-cells in chronic HCV patients. Interferon gamma secretion is a hallmark of type I T-cell responses. Such responses are seen during the acute phase of infection in the subset of HCV patients, who eliminate the virus and do not proceed to chronic infection.  Induction of type I T-cell responses as achieved by IC41 is a primary goal of therapeutic vaccination against HCV.</pharmacodynamics>
  <mechanism-of-action/>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <classification>
    <description/>
    <direct-parent>Peptides</direct-parent>
    <kingdom>Organic Compounds</kingdom>
    <superclass>Organic Acids</superclass>
    <class>Carboxylic Acids and Derivatives</class>
    <subclass>Amino Acids, Peptides, and Analogues</subclass>
  </classification>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <sequences/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910226</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>