<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<drug type="small molecule" created="2007-11-18" updated="2019-12-02">
  <drugbank-id primary="true">DB05919</drugbank-id>
  <name>DDP-200</name>
  <description>DDP200 is developed by Dynogen for the treatment of non-incontinent form of overactive bladder (OAB) with particular focus on both male and female patients with urinary frequency, urinary urgency and nocturia.</description>
  <cas-number/>
  <unii/>
  <state>solid</state>
  <groups>
    <group>investigational</group>
  </groups>
  <general-references>
    <articles/>
    <textbooks/>
    <links/>
    <attachments/>
  </general-references>
  <synthesis-reference/>
  <indication>Investigated for use/treatment in urinary incontinence.</indication>
  <pharmacodynamics/>
  <mechanism-of-action>DDP200 is an oral, fixed dose, combination of gabapentin and oxybutynin. Oxybutynin is prescribed to treat symptoms of lower urinary tract disorders such as overactive bladder (OAB), while gabapentin is prescribed for the management of postherpetic neuralgia and epilepsy. Dynogen’s combination of the two drugs has shown statistically significant synergy in Dynogen’s preclinical models of OAB, suggesting that a low dose combination of the two drugs will have improved efficacy over oxybutynin alone, without the side effects seen at higher doses. The combination of the two drugs has important characteristics: it affects both the afferent and efferent neurological pathways serving the bladder, and therefore may have benefits for both the sensory and motor aspects of OAB. Dynogen expects the synergy between the two compounds to increase the efficacy and tolerability profiles compared to market leading drugs for OAB.</mechanism-of-action>
  <toxicity/>
  <metabolism/>
  <absorption/>
  <half-life/>
  <protein-binding/>
  <route-of-elimination/>
  <volume-of-distribution/>
  <clearance/>
  <salts/>
  <synonyms/>
  <products/>
  <international-brands/>
  <mixtures/>
  <packagers/>
  <manufacturers/>
  <prices/>
  <categories/>
  <affected-organisms/>
  <dosages/>
  <atc-codes/>
  <ahfs-codes/>
  <pdb-entries/>
  <patents/>
  <food-interactions/>
  <drug-interactions/>
  <calculated-properties/>
  <experimental-properties/>
  <external-identifiers>
    <external-identifier>
      <resource>PubChem Substance</resource>
      <identifier>347910314</identifier>
    </external-identifier>
  </external-identifiers>
  <external-links/>
  <pathways/>
  <reactions/>
  <snp-effects/>
  <snp-adverse-drug-reactions/>
  <targets/>
  <enzymes/>
  <carriers/>
  <transporters/>
</drug>